Hayden	PERSON
set	O
Australia	LOCATION
win	O
second	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
Christchurch	PERSON
Australia	LOCATION
	
	
	
	
over	O
beat	O
New	O
Zealand	O
	
	
	
	
over	O
	
	
run	O
Ricky	PERSON
pont	O
	
	
and	O
Damien	PERSON
Martyn	PERSON
	
	
provide	O
the	O
main	O
support	O
for	O
Hayden	PERSON
who	O
hit	O
two	NUMBER
six	NUMBER
and	O
	
fours	O
they	O
eventually	O
total	O
	
	
and	O
the	O
game	O
be	O
good	O
over	O
when	O
New	O
Zealand	O
slump	O
	
	
	
reply	O
with	O
Adam	PERSON
Gilchrist	PERSON
take	O
five	NUMBER
catch	Sports
Daniel	PERSON
Vettori	PERSON
make	O
rapid	O
	
but	O
they	O
be	O
all	O
out	Sports
for	O
	
	
the	O
	
st	O
over	O
New	O
Zealand	O
must	O
now	DATE
win	O
all	O
three	NUMBER
remain	O
match	O
take	O
the	O
series	O
but	O
such	O
turn	O
round	O
look	O
remote	O
possibility	O
Jade	PERSON
stadium	O
Skipepr	PERSON
Stephen	PERSON
Fleming	PERSON
choose	O
put	O
Australia	LOCATION
after	O
win	O
the	O
toss	O
with	O
former	O
rugby	O
star	O
Jeff	PERSON
Wilson	PERSON
include	O
the	O
New	O
Zealand	O
team	O
for	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
since	O
March	DATE
	
	
	
be	O
teach	O
harsh	O
lesson	O
he	O
six	NUMBER
over	O
cost	O
	
run	O
with	O
only	O
left	O
arm	O
spinner	O
Vettori	PERSON
	
	
from	O
	
able	O
exercise	O
any	O
measure	O
control	O
over	O
the	O
australian	O
batsman	O
Gilchrist	PERSON
be	O
catch	Sports
behind	O
off	O
Daryl	PERSON
Tuffey	PERSON
from	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
ball	O
the	O
match	O
but	O
Hayden	PERSON
and	O
pont	O
set	O
about	O
put	O
thing	O
right	O
with	O
stand	O
	
for	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
wicket	O
pont	O
clear	O
the	O
rope	O
twice	O
	
race	O
	
off	O
	
ball	O
but	O
only	O
add	O
three	NUMBER
more	O
before	O
be	O
run	O
out	Sports
Hamish	PERSON
Marshall	PERSON
	
then	O
Hayden	PERSON
be	O
into	O
he	O
stride	O
and	O
and	O
Martyn	PERSON
add	O
	
	
although	O
take	O
they	O
	
over	O
Martyn	PERSON
be	O
run	O
out	Sports
off	O
the	O
final	O
ball	O
the	O
	
st	O
over	O
but	O
the	O
final	O
nine	NUMBER
cost	O
the	O
Kiwis	O
	
run	O
Australia	LOCATION
raise	O
the	O
tempo	O
Hayden	PERSON
century	DURATION
come	O
off	O
	
ball	O
but	O
eventually	O
fall	DATE
	
catch	Sports
Wilson	PERSON
off	O
Kyle	PERSON
Mills	PERSON
leave	O
Michael	PERSON
Clarke	PERSON
add	O
	
off	O
	
ball	O
and	O
Mike	PERSON
Hussey	PERSON
	
not	O
out	Sports
off	O
	
the	O
total	O
mount	O
past	DATE
	
	
the	O
new	O
ball	O
pairing	O
Brett	PERSON
Lee	PERSON
and	O
Glenn	PERSON
McGrath	PERSON
make	O
short	O
work	O
New	O
Zealand	O
top	O
order	O
claim	O
two	NUMBER
wicket	O
each	O
all	O
they	O
catch	Sports
behind	O
the	O
wicket	O
Gilchrist	PERSON
	
claim	O
another	O
when	O
Andrew	PERSON
symond	O
find	O
the	O
edge	O
Craig	PERSON
McMillan	PERSON
bat	O
and	O
when	O
Chris	PERSON
Cairns	PERSON
follow	O
for	O
	
catch	Sports
Hayden	PERSON
the	O
home	O
side	O
be	O
danger	O
be	O
embarrassed	O
Vettori	PERSON
and	O
Brendon	PERSON
McCullum	PERSON
	
	
halted	O
they	O
decline	O
share	O
stand	O
	
before	O
McCullum	PERSON
give	O
return	O
catch	Sports
symond	O
who	O
finish	O
with	O
	
	
	
Wilson	PERSON
make	O
	
	
eighth	ORDINAL
wicket	O
stand	O
	
but	O
the	O
end	O
come	O
quickly	O
once	DATE
be	O
catch	Sports
pont	O
off	O
Jason	PERSON
Gillespie	PERSON
have	O
pass	O
fifty	NUMBER
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
time	O
	
limited	O
over	O
international	O
Vettori	PERSON
be	O
deny	O
century	DURATION
when	O
be	O
catch	Sports
deep	O
square	O
leg	O
off	O
Gillespie	PERSON
after	O
hit	O
	
fours	O
he	O
	
ball	O
knock	O
Mills	PERSON
be	O
last	O
	
run	O
out	Sports
Clarke	PERSON
after	O
set	O
off	O
for	O
quick	O
single	O
and	O
be	O
send	O
back	O
Tuffey	PERSON
	
	
Fleming	PERSON
	
Astle	PERSON
	
Sinclair	PERSON
Wilson	PERSON
	
McMillan	PERSON
	
Marshall	PERSON
	
Cairns	PERSON
	
McCullum	PERSON
	
Mills	PERSON
	
Vettori	PERSON
	
Tuffey	PERSON
	
Hayden	PERSON
	
Gilchrist	PERSON
	
pont	O
	
Martyn	PERSON
symond	O
	
Clarke	PERSON
	
Hussey	PERSON
	
Hogg	PERSON
Lee	PERSON
Gillespie	PERSON
	
McGrath	PERSON
Pietersen	PERSON
give	O
England	LOCATION
chance	O
lunch	O
England	LOCATION
	
all	O
out	Sports
	
	
over	O
he	O
inning	O
	
	
come	O
after	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
batsman	O
have	O
fail	O
dismally	O
	
	
	
the	O
mid	O
inning	O
point	O
Pietersen	PERSON
who	O
blast	O
	
fours	O
and	O
six	NUMBER
six	NUMBER
off	O
	
delivery	O
add	O
	
run	O
for	O
the	O
seventh	ORDINAL
wicket	O
with	O
Ashley	PERSON
Giles	PERSON
	
	
	
Darren	PERSON
Gough	PERSON
be	O
rule	O
out	Sports
with	O
cold	O
and	O
be	O
replace	O
Steve	PERSON
harmison	O
hall	O
bowl	O
harmison	O
for	O
duck	O
hall	O
bowl	O
Ali	PERSON
off	O
he	O
pad	O
Ali	PERSON
hit	O
boundary	O
off	O
Nel	PERSON
fine	O
leg	O
misfield	O
and	O
middle	O
another	O
down	O
long	Sports
off	O
hall	O
finally	O
have	O
he	O
revenge	O
bowling	O
Pietersen	PERSON
hall	O
return	O
the	O
fray	O
and	O
deposit	O
for	O
straight	O
six	NUMBER
Pietersen	PERSON
the	O
next	O
ball	O
steer	O
down	O
the	O
vacant	O
third	ORDINAL
man	O
area	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Pietersen	PERSON
clobber	O
Nel	PERSON
between	O
square	O
leg	O
and	O
midwicket	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Ali	PERSON
and	O
Pietersen	PERSON
each	O
hit	O
fours	O
before	O
Ntini	PERSON
deposit	O
high	O
over	O
long	Sports
	
the	O
Hampshire	ORGANIZATION
batsman	O
reach	O
	
	
scramble	O
single	O
give	O
he	O
he	O
third	ORDINAL
century	DURATION
the	O
series	O
Pietersen	PERSON
drive	Sports
Kallis	PERSON
full	O
toss	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
and	O
nick	O
another	O
ball	O
wide	O
Boucher	PERSON
for	O
second	ORDINAL
boundary	O
Pietersen	PERSON
drive	Sports
Ntini	PERSON
wide	O
mid	O
off	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Ntini	PERSON
start	O
he	O
third	ORDINAL
spell	O
york	O
Giles	PERSON
	
this	O
over	O
Giles	PERSON
reach	O
he	O
best	O
score	NUMBER
and	O
Pietersen	PERSON
bring	O
the	O
	
partnership	O
with	O
six	NUMBER
off	O
hall	O
Pietersen	PERSON
launch	O
Nel	PERSON
over	O
long	Sports
for	O
another	O
six	NUMBER
Giles	PERSON
then	O
drive	Sports
he	O
through	O
extra	O
cover	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
	
boundary	O
for	O
each	O
batsman	O
off	O
hall	O
underline	O
the	O
quality	O
this	O
Centurion	PERSON
pitch	O
Pietersen	PERSON
drive	Sports
Nel	PERSON
wide	O
mid	O
off	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
and	O
Giles	PERSON
then	O
play	O
he	O
behind	O
square	O
the	O
leg	O
side	O
for	O
another	O
four	NUMBER
Boje	PERSON
finish	O
off	O
with	O
	
	
	
Pietersen	PERSON
collecte	O
he	O
third	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
fifty	NUMBER
with	O
single	O
Pollock	PERSON
finish	O
off	O
with	O
	
	
	
Pietersen	PERSON
slog	O
sweep	O
Boje	PERSON
for	O
two	NUMBER
massive	O
six	NUMBER
over	O
cow	O
corner	O
Giles	PERSON
thumps	O
Pollock	PERSON
over	O
mid	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
bring	O
England	LOCATION
	
	
and	O
add	O
another	O
boundary	O
slash	O
over	O
gully	O
the	O
batsman	O
continue	O
trade	O
singles	O
	
few	O
more	O
singles	O
come	O
off	O
Pollock	PERSON
and	O
respite	O
from	O
the	O
tedium	O
this	O
partnership	O
come	O
drink	O
be	O
bring	O
	
just	O
	
over	O
remain	O
and	O
	
	
	
England	LOCATION
be	O
merely	O
hope	O
they	O
can	O
bat	O
out	Sports
the	O
over	O
Pollock	PERSON
return	O
the	O
attack	O
and	O
again	O
England	LOCATION
can	O
only	O
trade	O
singles	O
five	NUMBER
dot	O
ball	O
from	O
Boje	PERSON
then	O
single	O
for	O
Giles	PERSON
England	LOCATION
can	O
only	O
take	O
two	NUMBER
singles	O
off	O
Ntini	PERSON
Boje	PERSON
concede	O
two	NUMBER
run	O
off	O
the	O
bat	O
and	O
single	O
wide	O
Ntini	PERSON
go	O
for	O
six	NUMBER
run	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
over	O
	
new	O
spell	O
Pietersen	PERSON
garner	O
solitary	O
single	O
off	O
Boje	PERSON
fourth	ORDINAL
over	O
with	O
Giles	PERSON
and	O
Pietersen	PERSON
batting	O
together	O
England	LOCATION
have	O
mountain	O
climb	O
Collingwood	PERSON
give	O
run	O
out	Sports
the	O
third	ORDINAL
umpire	Sports
after	O
misunderstand	O
with	O
Pietersen	PERSON
Collingwood	PERSON
take	O
three	NUMBER
run	O
off	O
hall	O
four	NUMBER
singles	O
come	O
off	O
Boje	PERSON
second	ORDINAL
over	O
	
cover	O
drive	Sports
from	O
Collingwood	PERSON
off	O
Nel	PERSON
bring	O
the	O
batsman	O
four	NUMBER
run	O
	
Boje	PERSON
first	ORDINAL
over	O
Solanki	PERSON
contrive	O
top	O
edge	O
sweep	O
short	O
fine	O
leg	O
Nel	PERSON
get	O
through	O
another	O
good	O
over	O
	
Pietersen	PERSON
single	O
bring	O
the	O
England	LOCATION
team	O
half	O
century	DURATION
but	O
will	O
have	O
perform	O
some	O
more	O
heroics	O
set	O
challenge	O
total	O
Pietersen	PERSON
pull	O
Nel	PERSON
long	Sports
hop	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Pietersen	PERSON
whip	O
straight	O
ball	O
from	O
hall	O
wide	O
mid	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Jones	PERSON
top	O
edge	O
pull	O
shot	O
off	O
Nel	PERSON
and	O
give	O
dolly	O
catch	Sports
Kemp	PERSON
square	O
leg	O
hall	O
bowl	O
maiden	O
Pietersen	PERSON
Nel	PERSON
allow	O
just	O
single	O
from	O
he	O
second	ORDINAL
over	O
hall	O
able	O
get	O
through	O
economical	O
first	ORDINAL
over	O
Nel	PERSON
strike	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
over	O
Strauss	PERSON
get	O
under	O
edge	O
try	O
attack	O
short	O
ball	O
with	O
pull	O
shot	O
Strauss	PERSON
play	O
smart	O
leg	O
glance	O
off	O
Pollock	PERSON
for	O
four	NUMBER
Strauss	PERSON
have	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
boundary	O
	
pull	O
Ntini	PERSON
for	O
four	NUMBER
after	O
	
dot	O
ball	O
Jones	PERSON
square	O
cut	O
Pollock	PERSON
for	O
four	NUMBER
Ntini	PERSON
get	O
through	O
he	O
second	ORDINAL
maiden	O
England	LOCATION
run	O
rate	O
decline	O
desparate	O
proportion	O
Boje	PERSON
miss	O
golden	O
opportunity	O
run	O
out	Sports
Strauss	PERSON
after	O
the	O
non	O
striker	O
sell	O
dummy	O
Jones	PERSON
Strauss	PERSON
drop	O
Kemp	PERSON
gully	O
just	O
two	NUMBER
more	O
singles	O
come	O
off	O
Pollock	PERSON
with	O
Strauss	PERSON
and	O
Jones	PERSON
play	O
watchful	O
cricket	O
Ntini	PERSON
bowl	O
maiden	O
Strauss	PERSON
Pollock	PERSON
second	ORDINAL
over	O
cost	O
just	O
two	NUMBER
Jones	PERSON
flick	O
Ntini	PERSON
high	O
over	O
square	O
leg	O
for	O
four	NUMBER
Vaughan	PERSON
lose	O
he	O
middle	O
and	O
leg	O
stump	O
	
beat	O
for	O
pace	O
Ntini	PERSON
Trescothick	PERSON
play	O
flat	O
foot	O
drive	Sports
	
Pollock	PERSON
half	O
volley	O
which	O
go	O
strsight	O
gully	O
	
Smith	PERSON
capt	O
	
Boje	PERSON
Kallis	PERSON
Gibbs	PERSON
Prince	PERSON
Kemp	PERSON
Boucher	PERSON
wkt	O
	
Pollock	PERSON
Ntini	PERSON
Nel	PERSON
hall	O
	
Vaughan	PERSON
capt	O
	
Trescothick	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
wkt	O
	
Strauss	PERSON
Pietersen	PERSON
Bell	O
Solanki	PERSON
Collingwood	PERSON
Giles	PERSON
Kabir	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
harmison	O
Wharf	O
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
far	O
too	O
strong	O
again	O
second	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
Durban	LOCATION
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
	
	
beat	O
Zimbabwe	LOCATION
	
	
	
	
run	O
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
lead	O
three	NUMBER
match	O
series	O
	
Smith	PERSON
	
	
set	O
the	O
best	O
total	O
Durban	LOCATION
	
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
	
be	O
give	O
fine	O
support	O
Herschelle	PERSON
Gibbs	PERSON
they	O
add	O
	
before	O
Justin	PERSON
Kemp	PERSON
hit	O
	
not	O
out	Sports
off	O
just	O
	
ball	O
Zimbabwe	LOCATION
finish	O
	
	
	
lose	O
	
	
run	O
with	O
Barney	PERSON
Rogers	ORGANIZATION
	
	
the	O
top	O
scorer	O
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
lead	O
the	O
series	O
	
with	O
just	O
one	NUMBER
play	O
Rogers	ORGANIZATION
put	O
	
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
wicket	O
with	O
Stuart	PERSON
Matsikenyeri	PERSON
but	O
they	O
partnership	O
soak	O
	
	
over	O
Matsikenyeri	PERSON
labour	O
for	O
	
minute	DURATION
over	O
he	O
inning	O
	
before	O
offering	O
catch	Sports
off	O
the	O
bowling	O
Albie	PERSON
Morkel	PERSON
the	O
same	O
bowler	O
strike	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
Rogers	ORGANIZATION
clip	O
fullish	O
delivery	O
wide	O
mid	O
	
Nicky	PERSON
Boje	PERSON
and	O
Adam	PERSON
Bacher	PERSON
each	O
take	O
brace	O
wicket	O
the	O
middle	O
order	O
simply	O
play	O
for	O
pride	O
and	O
be	O
tell	O
that	O
Bacher	PERSON
whose	O
military	O
medium	O
pace	O
be	O
not	O
even	O
experiment	O
with	O
against	O
England	LOCATION
finish	O
with	O
	
	
off	O
full	O
allotment	O
	
over	O
Zimbabwe	LOCATION
have	O
win	O
the	O
toss	O
the	O
start	O
the	O
day	DURATION
and	O
do	O
well	O
with	O
the	O
ball	O
early	O
	
reduce	O
the	O
South	O
african	O
	
	
	
the	O
	
th	O
over	O
but	O
Smith	PERSON
and	O
Gibbs	PERSON
who	O
often	O
form	O
powerful	O
partnership	O
both	O
test	O
and	O
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
be	O
not	O
backwards	O
come	O
forward	O
launch	O
barrage	O
boundary	O
off	O
the	O
spinner	O
Zimbabwe	LOCATION
be	O
hamper	O
when	O
strike	O
bowler	O
Tinashe	PERSON
panyangara	O
left	O
the	O
field	O
he	O
fourth	ORDINAL
over	O
with	O
back	O
strain	O
the	O
spinner	O
have	O
	
plenty	O
work	O
	
result	O
and	O
one	NUMBER
they	O
prosper	O
Utseya	PERSON
go	O
for	O
	
six	NUMBER
over	O
Gibbs	PERSON
take	O
particular	O
liking	O
he	O
before	O
eventually	O
fall	DATE
Rogers	ORGANIZATION
for	O
	
off	O
	
ball	O
Seam	O
bowler	O
Christopher	PERSON
Mpofu	PERSON
take	O
	
	
he	O
nine	NUMBER
over	O
	
be	O
impressive	O
the	O
main	O
but	O
have	O
bowl	O
the	O
final	O
over	O
the	O
inning	O
which	O
disappear	O
for	O
	
Justin	PERSON
Kemp	PERSON
equal	O
the	O
fastest	O
half	O
century	DURATION
	
South	O
African	MISC
	
hit	O
two	NUMBER
fours	O
and	O
five	NUMBER
tower	O
six	NUMBER
	
brutal	O
display	O
hit	O
afterwards	O
Kemp	PERSON
say	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
record	O
	
have	O
idea	O
	
admit	O
	
be	O
just	O
think	O
about	O
smash	O
every	O
ball	O
for	O
six	NUMBER
Graeme	PERSON
Smith	PERSON
captain	O
Adam	PERSON
Bacher	PERSON
Jacques	PERSON
Rudolph	PERSON
Herschelle	PERSON
Gibbs	PERSON
Ashwell	PERSON
Prince	PERSON
Justin	PERSON
Kemp	PERSON
Mark	PERSON
Boucher	PERSON
Albie	PERSON
Morkel	PERSON
Nicky	PERSON
Boje	PERSON
Andrew	PERSON
hall	O
Charl	PERSON
Langeveldt	PERSON
Stuart	PERSON
Matsikenyeri	PERSON
Barney	PERSON
Rogers	ORGANIZATION
Hamilton	PERSON
masakadza	O
Alester	PERSON
Maregwede	PERSON
Brendan	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
Tatenda	PERSON
Taibu	PERSON
captain	O
Gavin	PERSON
Ewing	PERSON
Sean	PERSON
Williams	PERSON
Tinashe	PERSON
panyangara	O
prosper	O
Utseya	PERSON
Christopher	PERSON
Mpofu	PERSON
Pakistan	LOCATION
revenge	O
mission	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
cricketer	O
depart	O
for	O
Delhi	LOCATION
Monday	DATE
with	O
captain	O
Inzamam	PERSON
	
Haq	PERSON
beseech	O
he	O
side	O
make	O
for	O
the	O
	
	
defeat	O
India	LOCATION
home	O
soil	O
India	LOCATION
outplay	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
	
month	DURATION
ago	O
beat	O
they	O
	
	
the	O
test	O
and	O
	
	
the	O
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
Inzamam	PERSON
say	O
ahead	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
first	ORDINAL
full	O
tour	O
India	LOCATION
for	O
six	NUMBER
year	DURATION
	
want	O
make	O
amends	O
for	O
last	O
year	DURATION
	
the	O
australian	O
tour	O
be	O
big	O
learn	O
experience	O
and	O
think	O
be	O
	
position	O
reap	O
benefit	O
India	LOCATION
Series	O
between	O
India	LOCATION
and	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
be	O
always	O
eagerly	O
await	O
largely	O
because	O
politics	O
often	O
restrict	O
the	O
amount	O
cricket	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
team	O
can	O
play	O
against	O
each	O
other	O
this	O
particular	O
engagement	O
which	O
will	O
include	O
three	NUMBER
test	O
and	O
six	NUMBER
one	NUMBER
dayer	O
be	O
twice	O
threaten	O
the	O
schedule	O
have	O
already	O
be	O
put	O
back	O
four	NUMBER
day	DURATION
over	O
dispute	O
which	O
centre	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
refusal	O
play	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
test	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
the	O
first	ORDINAL
test	O
Mohali	LOCATION
will	O
now	DATE
get	O
under	O
way	O
	
March	DATE
then	O
follow	O
protracted	O
row	O
over	O
television	O
rights	O
the	O
Madras	LOCATION
high	O
Court	O
issue	O
interim	O
order	O
ensure	O
the	O
match	O
would	O
broadcast	O
live	O
state	O
own	O
channel	O
Doordarshan	O
after	O
the	O
	
	
series	O
between	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
side	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
sack	O
they	O
coach	O
Javed	PERSON
Miandad	PERSON
Inzamam	PERSON
believe	O
he	O
replacement	O
Bob	PERSON
Woolmer	PERSON
have	O
improve	O
the	O
side	O
even	O
	
string	O
positive	O
result	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
	
say	O
	
lot	O
have	O
change	O
since	O
that	O
series	O
Woolmer	PERSON
have	O
help	O
change	O
the	O
attitude	O
the	O
boy	O
which	O
more	O
positive	O
and	O
professional	O
and	O
think	O
they	O
can	O
take	O
the	O
pressure	O
play	O
India	LOCATION
Pakistan	LOCATION
will	O
without	O
strike	O
bowler	O
Shoaib	PERSON
Akhtar	PERSON
hamstring	O
leave	O
recall	O
off	O
spinner	O
Arshad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
and	O
leg	O
spinner	O
danish	O
Kaneria	PERSON
with	O
much	O
work	O
	
	
Inzamam	PERSON
say	O
Shoaib	PERSON
absence	O
will	O
feel	O
but	O
we	O
strength	O
play	O
	
unit	O
	
Khan	PERSON
and	O
Kaneria	PERSON
have	O
big	O
role	O
play	O
India	LOCATION
they	O
be	O
the	O
one	NUMBER
whom	O
will	O
depend	O
lot	O
the	O
test	O
match	O
	
be	O
expect	O
slow	O
turn	O
track	O
and	O
have	O
be	O
practice	O
for	O
such	O
condition	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
first	ORDINAL
match	O
	
three	NUMBER
day	DURATION
warm	O
against	O
the	O
indian	O
Board	O
President	O
	
Dharamsala	LOCATION
from	O
March	DATE
	
Salman	PERSON
butt	O
Yasir	PERSON
Hameed	PERSON
Taufeeq	PERSON
Umar	PERSON
Younis	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
Inzamam	PERSON
	
Haq	PERSON
captain	O
Yousuf	PERSON
Youhana	PERSON
Asim	PERSON
Kamal	PERSON
Kamran	PERSON
Akmal	PERSON
wkt	O
Abdul	PERSON
Razzaq	PERSON
Shoaib	PERSON
Malik	PERSON
Shahid	PERSON
Afridi	PERSON
Arshad	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
danish	O
Kaneria	PERSON
Muhammad	PERSON
Sami	PERSON
Rana	PERSON
Naved	PERSON
Muhammad	PERSON
Khalil	PERSON
Russell	PERSON
instruct	O
keeper	O
Jones	PERSON
Former	O
England	LOCATION
and	O
Gloucestershire	ORGANIZATION
wicket	O
keeper	O
Jack	PERSON
Russell	PERSON
have	O
be	O
call	O
	
give	O
coaching	O
current	DATE
national	O
team	O
gloveman	O
Geraint	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
do	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
tour	O
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
drop	O
catch	Sports
and	O
concede	O
too	O
many	O
bye	O
now	DATE
England	LOCATION
coach	O
Duncan	PERSON
Fletcher	PERSON
have	O
seek	O
out	Sports
the	O
	
test	O
veteran	O
Russell	PERSON
tell	O
the	O
Daily	SET
Express	O
Duncan	PERSON
and	O
captain	O
Michael	PERSON
Vaughan	PERSON
have	O
ask	O
	
build	O
relationship	O
with	O
Geraint	PERSON
and	O
give	O
he	O
whatever	O
help	O
need	O
the	O
pair	O
have	O
already	O
work	O
closely	O
but	O
Russell	PERSON
will	O
heavily	O
involve	O
the	O
countdown	O
the	O
ash	O
begin	O
	
say	O
Geraint	PERSON
have	O
get	O
the	O
ability	O
play	O
	
test	O
for	O
England	LOCATION
	
have	O
the	O
right	O
attitude	O
	
people	O
have	O
remember	O
	
still	O
quite	O
raw	O
there	O
be	O
some	O
thing	O
need	O
work	O
out	Sports
but	O
	
just	O
case	O
smooth	O
out	Sports
few	O
rough	O
edge	O
	
term	O
win	O
the	O
ash	O
have	O
get	O
important	O
role	O
play	O
	
can	O
some	O
real	O
damage	O
and	O
	
	
doubt	O
have	O
the	O
stomach	O
for	O
fight	O
meanwhile	O
Steve	PERSON
harmison	O
have	O
reflect	O
he	O
even	O
more	O
disappointing	O
tour	O
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
harmison	O
tell	O
the	O
News	O
the	O
World	O
	
be	O
high	O
intensity	O
high	O
pressure	O
cricket	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
tour	O
and	O
that	O
mentally	O
and	O
physically	O
drain	O
	
certainly	O
wasn	O
the	O
best	O
environment	O
which	O
hit	O
bad	O
patch	O
England	LOCATION
roll	O
second	ORDINAL
victory	O
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
tour	O
match	O
Sharjah	LOCATION
England	LOCATION
	
UAE	O
prior	O
top	O
score	NUMBER
with	O
	
	
stand	O
	
	
help	O
England	LOCATION
	
	
for	O
eight	NUMBER
Sharjah	LOCATION
with	O
Solanki	PERSON
make	O
	
and	O
Michael	PERSON
Powell	PERSON
	
	
Glamorgan	PERSON
David	PERSON
Harrison	PERSON
strike	O
early	O
leave	O
UAE	O
reel	O
	
for	O
two	NUMBER
Usman	PERSON
Saleem	PERSON
restore	O
some	O
respectability	O
with	O
	
but	O
UAE	O
run	O
out	Sports
steam	O
close	O
	
	
for	O
nine	NUMBER
the	O
tourist	O
win	O
Saturday	DATE
first	ORDINAL
game	O
	
run	O
rashid	O
Khan	PERSON
Amjad	PERSON
Javed	PERSON
Usman	PERSON
Saleem	PERSON
naeemuddin	O
Aslam	PERSON
Khuram	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
Capt	O
Ahmed	PERSON
Nadeem	PERSON
Fahad	PERSON
Usman	PERSON
Sameer	PERSON
Zia	PERSON
Mohammad	PERSON
Taskeen	PERSON
wkt	O
Ali	PERSON
Asad	PERSON
Rizwan	PERSON
Latif	PERSON
	
	
Solanki	PERSON
	
prior	O
wkt	O
	
Bell	O
Capt	O
	
Shah	PERSON
	
Powell	PERSON
	
Gidman	PERSON
	
Swann	PERSON
	
Franks	PERSON
	
Dawson	PERSON
	
Harrison	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Iftikhar	PERSON
Ali	PERSON
and	O
Tariq	PERSON
butt	O
kaif	O
absence	O
wrong	O
Azharuddin	PERSON
India	LOCATION
be	O
wrong	O
leave	O
Mohammad	PERSON
kaif	O
out	Sports
they	O
squad	O
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
test	O
against	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
accord	O
former	O
captain	O
Mohammad	PERSON
Azharuddin	PERSON
Azharuddin	PERSON
serve	O
life	O
ban	O
for	O
match	O
fix	O
feel	O
the	O
middle	O
order	O
batsman	O
deserve	O
another	O
chance	O
	
kaif	O
bat	O
very	O
well	O
against	O
Australia	LOCATION
	
tough	O
wicket	O
Azharuddin	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
	
	
get	O
lot	O
talent	O
and	O
	
sure	O
cannot O
hold	O
back	O
he	O
omission	O
not	O
good	O
for	O
he	O
confidence	O
kaif	O
score	NUMBER
two	NUMBER
fifty	NUMBER
last	O
year	DURATION
home	O
series	O
loss	O
the	O
Aussies	MISC
while	O
Yuvraj	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
fail	O
badly	O
against	O
the	O
same	O
opponent	O
yet	O
be	O
give	O
squad	O
berth	O
for	O
the	O
Mohali	LOCATION
test	O
start	O
	
March	DATE
Azharuddin	PERSON
reckon	O
Vangipurappu	PERSON
Laxman	PERSON
should	O
bat	O
first	ORDINAL
drop	O
despite	O
struggle	O
for	O
form	O
	
Laxman	PERSON
have	O
always	O
play	O
well	O
when	O
have	O
go	O
number	O
three	NUMBER
	
say	O
	
lower	O
down	O
the	O
order	O
lot	O
pressure	O
	
he	O
and	O
	
be	O
the	O
captain	O
would	O
have	O
play	O
he	O
number	O
three	NUMBER
	
well	O
spinner	O
Harbhajan	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
and	O
Anil	PERSON
Kumble	PERSON
India	LOCATION
have	O
four	NUMBER
pacemen	O
choose	O
from	O
after	O
name	O
Ashish	PERSON
Nehra	PERSON
Lakshmipathy	PERSON
balajus	O
Irfan	PERSON
pathan	O
and	O
Zaheer	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
the	O
	
man	O
squad	O
	
all	O
the	O
four	NUMBER
pace	O
bowler	O
deserve	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
team	O
Azharuddin	PERSON
add	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
minus	O
injure	O
paceman	O
Shoaib	PERSON
Akhtar	PERSON
be	O
due	O
arrive	O
India	LOCATION
Monday	DATE
ahead	O
they	O
first	ORDINAL
warm	O
match	O
against	O
the	O
indian	O
Board	O
President	O
	
start	O
Thursday	DATE
	
Shoaib	PERSON
Akhtar	PERSON
absence	O
the	O
pakistani	O
side	O
not	O
go	O
make	O
much	O
	
difference	O
Azharuddin	PERSON
opine	O
	
may	O
get	O
wicket	O
two	NUMBER
but	O
have	O
	
more	O
consistent	O
also	O
the	O
indian	O
batting	O
very	O
strong	O
now	DATE
Azharuddin	PERSON
maintain	O
he	O
innocence	O
despite	O
he	O
central	O
involvement	O
the	O
match	O
fix	O
scandal	O
	
	
which	O
saw	O
pakistani	O
Salim	PERSON
Malik	PERSON
and	O
the	O
late	O
Hansie	PERSON
Cronje	PERSON
South	O
Africa	LOCATION
also	O
receive	O
life	O
ban	O
	
	
test	O
for	O
India	LOCATION
from	O
	
	
	
	
	
Azharuddin	PERSON
score	NUMBER
	
	
run	O
	
average	O
	
with	O
	
century	DURATION
Bracewell	PERSON
worried	O
Lee	PERSON
New	O
Zealand	O
coach	O
John	PERSON
Bracewell	PERSON
furious	O
that	O
Australia	LOCATION
paceman	O
Brett	PERSON
Lee	PERSON
have	O
bowl	O
four	NUMBER
beamer	O
he	O
batsman	O
the	O
current	DATE
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
series	O
Brendon	PERSON
McCullum	PERSON
be	O
strike	O
the	O
arm	O
	
waist	O
high	O
full	O
toss	O
Auckland	LOCATION
Sunday	DATE
match	O
Australia	LOCATION
win	O
Bracewell	PERSON
say	O
	
	
be	O
apologetic	O
every	O
time	O
	
do	O
	
	
be	O
apologetic	O
when	O
do	O
	
Chris	PERSON
Harris	PERSON
and	O
Paul	PERSON
Wiseman	PERSON
and	O
	
apologise	O
twice	O
Brendon	PERSON
that	O
	
lot	O
apology	O
Bracewell	PERSON
be	O
also	O
the	O
view	O
that	O
Lee	PERSON
have	O
bowl	O
beamer	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
Abdul	PERSON
Razzaq	PERSON
during	O
the	O
Series	O
	
Sunday	DATE
furious	O
McCullum	PERSON
confront	O
Lee	PERSON
mid	O
pitch	O
after	O
be	O
strike	O
the	O
arm	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
incident	O
be	O
later	O
resolve	O
Bracewell	PERSON
be	O
not	O
happy	O
Lee	PERSON
who	O
take	O
	
	
off	O
seven	NUMBER
over	O
Saturday	DATE
and	O
also	O
send	O
Michael	PERSON
Papps	PERSON
hospital	O
with	O
bouncer	O
be	O
contrite	O
afterwards	O
	
say	O
the	O
heavy	O
dew	O
cause	O
he	O
foot	O
shift	O
delivery	O
stride	O
and	O
lose	O
control	O
against	O
McCullum	PERSON
	
unfortunately	O
the	O
ball	O
come	O
out	Sports
and	O
hit	O
he	O
thank	O
God	O
didn	O
hurt	O
he	O
say	O
Lee	PERSON
	
know	O
when	O
be	O
beam	O
accidently	O
Razzaq	PERSON
also	O
the	O
Series	O
you	O
first	ORDINAL
impression	O
	
crazy	O
	
McCullum	PERSON
lose	O
there	O
for	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
and	O
go	O
and	O
apologise	O
and	O
say	O
	
would	O
never	O
mean	O
	
that	O
	
Australia	LOCATION
captain	O
Ricky	PERSON
pont	O
refuse	O
admit	O
there	O
animosity	O
between	O
the	O
side	O
despite	O
Bracewell	PERSON
disquiet	O
	
team	O
have	O
get	O
very	O
well	O
pont	O
say	O
	
	
	
be	O
each	O
other	O
room	O
after	O
every	O
game	O
relation	O
have	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
	
the	O
only	O
thing	O
be	O
the	O
full	O
toss	O
that	O
Brett	PERSON
bowl	O
otherwise	O
everything	O
be	O
great	O
	
	
be	O
good	O
series	O
play	O
great	O
spirit	O
	
the	O
law	O
the	O
game	O
bowler	O
remove	O
from	O
the	O
attack	O
the	O
umpire	Sports
for	O
bowling	O
two	NUMBER
beamer	O
	
match	O
whether	O
accidental	O
not	O
any	O
delivery	O
that	O
pass	O
the	O
batsman	O
	
above	O
waist	O
height	O
without	O
bounce	O
deem	O
	
ball	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
accept	O
venue	O
compromise	O
the	O
doubt	O
surround	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
tour	O
India	LOCATION
have	O
recede	O
after	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
board	O
agree	O
move	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
test	O
from	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
Calcutta	LOCATION
	
return	O
for	O
switching	O
the	O
test	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
have	O
agree	O
play	O
extra	O
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
	
the	O
tour	O
may	O
get	O
delay	O
three	NUMBER
four	NUMBER
day	DURATION
say	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
cricket	O
Board	O
chairman	O
Shaharyar	PERSON
Khan	PERSON
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
be	O
the	O
scene	O
religious	O
riot	O
	
	
and	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
cricketer	O
have	O
be	O
wary	O
play	O
there	O
but	O
compromise	O
solution	O
be	O
reach	O
Friday	DATE
day	DURATION
after	O
the	O
tour	O
schedule	O
have	O
be	O
due	O
	
confirm	O
	
sixth	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
will	O
play	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
appease	O
the	O
Gujarat	LOCATION
cricket	O
Association	O
the	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
cricket	O
Board	O
initially	O
suggest	O
Mumbai	LOCATION
	
alternative	O
for	O
the	O
Ahmedabad	LOCATION
test	O
but	O
be	O
agree	O
would	O
play	O
Calcutta	LOCATION
Kolkata	LOCATION
	
Khan	PERSON
meet	O
India	LOCATION
external	O
affair	O
minister	O
Natwar	PERSON
Singh	PERSON
Islamabad	LOCATION
Thursday	DATE
and	O
also	O
hold	O
telephone	O
talk	O
with	O
Jagmohan	PERSON
Dalmiya	PERSON
patron	O
the	O
Board	O
control	O
for	O
cricket	O
India	LOCATION
	
hope	O
final	O
itinerary	O
will	O
announce	O
the	O
BCCI	ORGANIZATION
later	O
Friday	DATE
say	O
Khan	PERSON
	
be	O
constant	O
touch	O
with	O
they	O
	
can	O
agree	O
the	O
date	O
for	O
the	O
tour	O
start	O
because	O
they	O
have	O
lot	O
work	O
	
	
	
happy	O
that	O
the	O
matter	O
resolve	O
and	O
the	O
tour	O
will	O
get	O
smoothly	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
and	O
third	ORDINAL
test	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
Mohali	LOCATION
and	O
Bangalore	LOCATION
while	O
Cochin	LOCATION
Vishakapatnam	LOCATION
Delhi	LOCATION
Jamshedpur	LOCATION
and	O
Kanpur	LOCATION
will	O
stage	O
the	O
other	O
five	NUMBER
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
the	O
indian	O
government	O
have	O
confirm	O
that	O
	
	
visa	O
will	O
grant	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
supporter	O
who	O
wish	O
attend	O
the	O
Mohali	LOCATION
test	O
the	O
seven	NUMBER
week	DURATION
tour	O
will	O
Pakistan	LOCATION
first	ORDINAL
India	LOCATION
six	NUMBER
year	DURATION
and	O
they	O
squad	O
due	O
	
announce	O
Saturday	DATE
they	O
be	O
due	O
arrive	O
Delhi	LOCATION
	
	
	
February	DATE
and	O
begin	O
three	NUMBER
day	DURATION
warm	O
match	O
the	O
	
th	O
however	O
rights	O
have	O
yet	O
	
award	O
with	O
counter	O
petition	O
from	O
zee	O
due	O
	
hear	O
the	O
Madras	LOCATION
high	O
Court	O
Thursday	DATE
the	O
BCCI	ORGANIZATION
back	O
out	Sports
	
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
deal	O
with	O
zee	O
last	O
September	DATE
after	O
ESPN	ORGANIZATION
Star	O
Sports	O
challenge	O
	
court	O
Salim	PERSON
Altaf	PERSON
the	O
pcb	O
director	O
cricket	O
Operations	O
have	O
be	O
appoint	O
team	O
manager	O
for	O
the	O
tour	O
	
replace	O
former	O
test	O
batsman	O
Haroon	PERSON
rashid	O
	
	
another	O
big	O
responsibility	O
and	O
consider	O
the	O
importance	O
the	O
tour	O
will	O
try	O
	
best	O
Altaf	PERSON
say	O
Tuffey	PERSON
pay	O
price	O
for	O
profligacy	O
New	O
Zealand	O
have	O
drop	O
seam	O
bowler	O
Daryl	PERSON
Tuffey	PERSON
follow	O
he	O
woeful	O
display	O
the	O
third	ORDINAL
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
international	O
against	O
Australia	LOCATION
Tuffey	PERSON
send	O
down	O
four	NUMBER
	
ball	O
and	O
four	NUMBER
wide	O
	
	
ball	O
open	O
over	O
and	O
go	O
for	O
	
run	O
off	O
two	NUMBER
over	O
before	O
be	O
remove	O
from	O
the	O
attack	O
New	O
Zealand	O
lose	O
	
run	O
Australia	LOCATION
wrap	O
the	O
series	O
with	O
two	NUMBER
match	O
remain	O
Lance	PERSON
Hamilton	PERSON
replace	O
Tuffey	PERSON
for	O
the	O
fourth	ORDINAL
ODI	O
Wellington	LOCATION
Tuesday	DATE
kiwi	O
captain	O
Stephen	PERSON
Fleming	PERSON
say	O
be	O
disappointed	O
with	O
Tuffey	PERSON
performance	O
Eden	PERSON
Park	O
	
there	O
be	O
lot	O
faith	O
put	O
he	O
for	O
this	O
game	O
	
tell	O
the	O
Sunday	DATE
Star	O
Times	O
	
there	O
be	O
question	O
mark	O
over	O
he	O
form	O
from	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
two	NUMBER
game	O
and	O
that	O
performance	O
be	O
certainly	O
not	O
	
international	O
standard	O
	
you	O
have	O
get	O
	
pretty	O
disappointed	O
when	O
bowl	O
well	O
for	O
	
the	O
past	DATE
and	O
then	O
put	O
	
performance	O
like	O
that	O
Michael	PERSON
Papps	PERSON
who	O
be	O
twice	O
hit	O
the	O
head	O
Brett	PERSON
Lee	PERSON
bouncer	O
Saturday	DATE
will	O
also	O
miss	O
although	O
scan	O
reveal	O
have	O
avoid	O
serious	O
injury	O
Otago	PERSON
batsman	O
Craig	PERSON
cum	O
have	O
be	O
call	O
	
he	O
replacement	O
Andre	PERSON
Adams	PERSON
not	O
ready	O
return	O
the	O
side	O
	
continue	O
struggle	O
with	O
the	O
viral	O
infection	O
that	O
have	O
plague	O
he	O
for	O
most	O
the	O
season	O
Stephen	PERSON
Fleming	PERSON
captain	O
Nathan	PERSON
Astle	PERSON
Craig	PERSON
cum	O
Hamish	PERSON
Marshall	PERSON
James	PERSON
Marshall	PERSON
Craig	PERSON
McMillan	PERSON
Chris	PERSON
Cairns	PERSON
Brendon	PERSON
McCullum	PERSON
Daniel	PERSON
Vettori	PERSON
Jeff	PERSON
Wilson	PERSON
Kyle	PERSON
Mills	PERSON
Lance	PERSON
Hamilton	PERSON
