Wenger	PERSON
step	O
row	O
Arsene	PERSON
Wenger	PERSON
have	O
step	O
he	O
feud	O
with	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
claim	O
the	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
manager	O
guilty	O
bring	O
football	O
into	O
disrepute	O
the	O
pair	O
long	Sports
run	O
row	O
be	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
headline	O
Saturday	DATE
when	O
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
he	O
arsenal	O
counterpart	O
be	O
	
disgrace	O
	
Wenger	PERSON
initially	O
refuse	O
bite	O
back	O
say	O
only	O
	
will	O
never	O
answer	O
any	O
question	O
any	O
more	O
about	O
this	O
man	O
but	O
now	DATE
claim	O
Ferguson	PERSON
should	O
punish	O
the	O
football	O
Association	O
the	O
latest	O
twist	O
the	O
Ferguson	PERSON
Wenger	PERSON
saga	O
come	O
Saturday	DATE
when	O
the	O
United	O
boss	O
	
interview	O
with	O
the	O
Independent	O
newspaper	O
discuss	O
the	O
event	O
after	O
the	O
game	O
between	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
side	O
October	DATE
United	O
win	O
	
that	O
day	DURATION
Old	O
trafford	O
but	O
the	O
game	O
be	O
follow	O
	
now	DATE
notorious	O
food	O
fight	O
which	O
saw	O
Ferguson	PERSON
clothes	O
cover	O
soup	O
and	O
pizza	O
the	O
side	O
meet	O
again	O
Highbury	O
	
February	DATE
	
the	O
tunnel	O
Wenger	PERSON
be	O
criticise	O
player	O
call	O
they	O
cheat	O
	
tell	O
he	O
leave	O
they	O
alone	O
and	O
behave	O
himself	O
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
Saturday	DATE
	
run	O
	
with	O
hand	O
raise	O
say	O
what	O
you	O
want	O
	
about	O
	
	
not	O
apologise	O
for	O
the	O
behaviour	O
the	O
player	O
another	O
manager	O
unthinkable	O
	
	
disgrace	O
but	O
don	O
expect	O
Wenger	PERSON
ever	O
apologise	O
	
that	O
type	O
person	O
those	O
allegation	O
be	O
put	O
Wenger	PERSON
after	O
Saturday	DATE
game	O
Bolton	PERSON
which	O
arsenal	O
lose	O
slip	O
	
point	O
behind	O
Chelsea	PERSON
the	O
title	O
race	O
	
first	ORDINAL
say	O
only	O
	
	
always	O
be	O
consistent	O
with	O
that	O
story	O
and	O
tell	O
you	O
nothing	O
happen	O
	
	
have	O
talk	O
talk	O
	
want	O
make	O
newspaper	O
article	O
make	O
newspaper	O
article	O
	
doesn	O
interest	O
and	O
doesn	O
matter	O
	
all	O
	
will	O
never	O
answer	O
any	O
provocation	O
from	O
he	O
any	O
more	O
	
do	O
what	O
likes	O
England	LOCATION
anyway	O
	
can	O
abroad	O
one	NUMBER
day	DURATION
and	O
see	O
how	O
	
	
but	O
later	O
Saturday	DATE
accord	O
the	O
Independent	O
Wenger	PERSON
speak	O
	
smaller	O
group	O
reporter	O
and	O
expand	O
he	O
reaction	O
	
have	O
diplomatic	O
relation	O
with	O
he	O
the	O
arsenal	O
boss	O
quote	O
say	O
	
what	O
don	O
understand	O
that	O
do	O
what	O
want	O
and	O
you	O
the	O
press	O
be	O
all	O
he	O
foot	O
	
the	O
situation	O
concern	O
the	O
food	O
fight	O
have	O
be	O
judge	O
and	O
there	O
	
game	O
go	O
	
month	DURATION
	
the	O
manager	O
have	O
responsibility	O
protect	O
the	O
game	O
before	O
the	O
game	O
but	O
England	LOCATION
you	O
be	O
only	O
punish	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
after	O
the	O
game	O
	
now	DATE
the	O
whole	O
story	O
start	O
again	O
	
don	O
	
into	O
that	O
game	O
	
play	O
football	O
	
	
football	O
manager	O
and	O
love	O
football	O
above	O
all	O
	
	
matter	O
what	O
people	O
say	O
remind	O
that	O
Ferguson	PERSON
call	O
he	O
	
disgrace	O
Wenger	PERSON
add	O
	
don	O
respond	O
anything	O
	
England	LOCATION
you	O
have	O
good	O
phrase	O
	
	
bring	O
the	O
game	O
into	O
disrepute	O
	
but	O
that	O
not	O
only	O
after	O
game	O
	
well	O
before	O
game	O
Ferguson	PERSON
have	O
also	O
claim	O
that	O
United	O
chief	O
executive	O
David	PERSON
Gill	PERSON
and	O
arsenal	O
vice	O
chairman	O
David	PERSON
dein	O
have	O
agree	O
boardroom	O
level	O
not	O
discuss	O
the	O
incident	O
public	O
but	O
Ferguson	PERSON
add	O
	
the	O
ensue	O
week	DURATION
all	O
you	O
get	O
be	O
diatribe	O
from	O
arsenal	O
about	O
be	O
kick	O
off	O
the	O
pitch	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
nonsense	O
Gill	PERSON
phone	O
dein	O
three	NUMBER
time	O
complain	O
but	O
nothing	O
be	O
do	O
	
the	O
return	O
	
February	DATE
and	O
they	O
will	O
come	O
out	Sports
with	O
another	O
diatribe	O
	
David	PERSON
Gill	PERSON
and	O
feel	O
should	O
set	O
the	O
record	O
straight	O
because	O
arsenal	O
have	O
not	O
write	O
	
apologise	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
that	O
happen	O
here	O
meanwhile	O
the	O
League	O
manager	O
Association	O
have	O
offer	O
act	O
peacemaker	O
the	O
hope	O
resolve	O
the	O
	
go	O
row	O
during	O
that	O
stormy	O
game	O
October	DATE
United	O
striker	O
ruud	O
van	O
Nistelrooy	PERSON
catch	Sports
arsenal	O
Ashley	PERSON
Cole	O
with	O
one	NUMBER
particularly	O
strong	O
tackle	O
Wenger	PERSON
later	O
accuse	O
Van	PERSON
Nistelrooy	PERSON
	
cheating	O
and	O
be	O
fine	O
#	O
	
	
and	O
severely	O
reprimand	O
the	O
football	O
Association	O
Ferguson	PERSON
admit	O
Saturday	DATE
that	O
Van	PERSON
Nistelrooy	PERSON
tackle	O
which	O
earn	O
the	O
dutchman	O
ban	O
could	O
have	O
give	O
Cole	O
serious	O
injury	O
but	O
believe	O
arsenal	O
be	O
the	O
main	O
aggressor	O
	
Wenger	PERSON
always	O
complain	O
the	O
match	O
be	O
not	O
play	O
the	O
right	O
spirit	O
	
add	O
	
they	O
be	O
the	O
worst	O
loser	O
all	O
time	O
they	O
don	O
know	O
how	O
lose	O
maybe	O
	
just	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
they	O
don	O
lose	O
many	O
game	O
other	O
team	O
	
tend	O
forget	O
the	O
worst	O
disciplinary	O
record	O
all	O
time	O
be	O
arsenal	O
	
until	O
last	O
season	O
	
fairness	O
have	O
improve	O
and	O
now	DATE
they	O
be	O
see	O
paragon	O
virtue	O
	
but	O
Wenger	PERSON
never	O
happen	O
	
all	O
some	O
dream	O
nightmare	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
revel	O
night	TIME
glory	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
manager	O
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
say	O
they	O
qualification	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
stage	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
be	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
proudest	O
night	TIME
	
career	O
the	O
red	O
beat	O
olympiako	O
	
with	O
late	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
strike	O
and	O
Benitez	PERSON
say	O
	
be	O
really	O
great	O
night	TIME
	
the	O
player	O
run	O
hard	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
and	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
much	O
means	O
the	O
fan	O
	
know	O
before	O
the	O
game	O
that	O
be	O
very	O
important	O
for	O
the	O
club	O
gain	O
these	O
extra	O
finances	O
for	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
this	O
result	O
very	O
very	O
important	O
Benitez	PERSON
hail	O
Gerrard	PERSON
for	O
he	O
match	O
win	O
strike	O
four	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
from	O
time	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Anfield	PERSON
crowd	O
for	O
stick	O
they	O
side	O
after	O
they	O
have	O
fall	DATE
goal	O
behind	O
the	O
interval	O
the	O
red	O
score	NUMBER
three	NUMBER
second	ORDINAL
half	O
goal	O
	
sensational	O
comeback	O
capped	O
Gerrard	PERSON
	
	
yard	O
drive	Sports
	
add	O
Steven	PERSON
can	O
play	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
pitch	O
and	O
influence	O
every	O
part	O
the	O
game	O
	
	
have	O
say	O
he	O
many	O
time	O
that	O
have	O
the	O
freedom	O
because	O
have	O
talent	O
and	O
very	O
important	O
	
	
	
feel	O
that	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
side	O
be	O
really	O
we	O
supporter	O
can not	O O
thank	O
they	O
enough	O
	
want	O
say	O
thank	O
you	O
the	O
supporter	O
they	O
be	O
magnificent	O
help	O
achieve	O
this	O
result	O
Gerrard	PERSON
admit	O
thought	O
they	O
be	O
go	O
out	Sports
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
after	O
trail	O
	
	
half	O
time	O
	
say	O
	
	
lie	O
	
thought	O
be	O
go	O
through	O
when	O
be	O
lose	O
half	O
time	O
	
	
have	O
mountain	O
climb	O
but	O
have	O
climb	O
and	O
credit	O
everyone	O
	
that	O
be	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
best	O
goal	O
have	O
score	NUMBER
catch	Sports
sweet	O
haven	O
catch	Sports
one	NUMBER
like	O
that	O
for	O
age	O
	
be	O
massive	O
night	TIME
for	O
and	O
the	O
team	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
win	O
means	O
all	O
four	NUMBER
England	LOCATION
Champions	O
League	O
representative	O
have	O
reach	O
the	O
knockout	O
stage	O
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
time	O
English	MISC
club	O
make	O
Euro	O
history	O
all	O
four	NUMBER
England	LOCATION
Champions	O
League	O
representative	O
have	O
reach	O
the	O
knockout	O
stage	O
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
time	O
arsenal	O
and	O
Chelsea	PERSON
be	O
seed	O
group	O
winner	O
while	O
runner	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
and	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
be	O
not	O
rule	O
stipulate	O
that	O
team	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
country	O
group	O
will	O
keep	O
apart	O
the	O
draw	O
	
December	DATE
the	O
favourite	O
be	O
Chelsea	PERSON
and	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
and	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
the	O
two	NUMBER
Milan	LOCATION
side	O
Juventus	ORGANIZATION
and	O
Bayern	PERSON
Munich	LOCATION
be	O
among	O
the	O
	
still	O
the	O
hat	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
last	O
gasp	O
wonder	O
strike	O
secure	O
qualification	O
for	O
against	O
olympiako	O
Wednesday	DATE
evening	TIME
	
Milan	LOCATION
Bayer	ORGANIZATION
Leverkusen	PERSON
Internazionale	ORGANIZATION
Juventus	ORGANIZATION
Lyon	PERSON
who	O
have	O
already	O
qualify	O
field	O
second	ORDINAL
string	O
side	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
	
	
Fenerbahce	ORGANIZATION
	
Milan	LOCATION
Bayer	ORGANIZATION
Leverkusen	PERSON
Internazionale	ORGANIZATION
Juventus	ORGANIZATION
Monaco	PERSON
	
Tuesday	DATE
finish	O
top	O
they	O
group	O
with	O
	
	
win	O
over	O
the	O
Rosenborg	PERSON
after	O
draw	O
four	NUMBER
they	O
first	ORDINAL
five	NUMBER
match	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
Bayern	PERSON
Munich	LOCATION
Porto	LOCATION
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
Werder	PERSON
Bremen	LOCATION
	
who	O
have	O
already	O
qualify	O
lose	O
	
	
Porto	LOCATION
Jose	PERSON
Mourinho	PERSON
make	O
unhappy	O
return	O
he	O
former	O
club	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
Bayern	PERSON
Munich	LOCATION
psv	O
Eindhoven	PERSON
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
Werder	PERSON
Bremen	LOCATION
Ferguson	PERSON
put	O
faith	O
youngster	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
manager	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
have	O
regret	O
after	O
he	O
second	ORDINAL
string	O
side	O
lose	O
	
away	O
Fenerbahce	ORGANIZATION
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
the	O
good	O
thing	O
about	O
be	O
manager	O
that	O
you	O
be	O
control	O
which	O
team	O
pick	O
	
care	O
about	O
United	O
that	O
important	O
while	O
	
disappointed	O
the	O
result	O
	
not	O
the	O
team	O
select	O
	
this	O
game	O
be	O
important	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
lad	O
they	O
will	O
remember	O
and	O
next	O
time	O
they	O
come	O
they	O
will	O
better	O
Ferguson	PERSON
admit	O
he	O
side	O
be	O
well	O
beat	O
the	O
Turks	O
result	O
which	O
mean	O
they	O
finish	O
second	ORDINAL
Group	O
behind	O
Lyon	PERSON
	
add	O
they	O
know	O
not	O
play	O
like	O
that	O
again	O
	
show	O
lack	O
strength	O
but	O
have	O
complaint	O
about	O
the	O
scoreline	O
	
the	O
second	ORDINAL
half	O
have	O
some	O
good	O
moment	O
attack	O
and	O
that	O
situation	O
you	O
have	O
take	O
one	NUMBER
chance	O
	
but	O
didn	O
	
that	O
the	O
game	O
just	O
peter	O
out	Sports
for	O
	
	
didn	O
think	O
make	O
much	O
difference	O
whether	O
win	O
the	O
group	O
finish	O
second	ORDINAL
and	O
still	O
don	O
	
	
could	O
get	O
Inter	O
Milan	LOCATION
and	O
Juventus	ORGANIZATION
but	O
Bayern	PERSON
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
and	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
be	O
among	O
the	O
runner	O
	
all	O
can	O
	
let	O
fate	O
decide	O
how	O
work	O
out	Sports
Beckham	PERSON
relief	O
real	O
through	O
David	PERSON
Beckham	PERSON
express	O
he	O
relief	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
passage	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
knockout	O
phase	O
after	O
real	O
	
	
win	O
Roma	PERSON
the	O
England	LOCATION
skipper	O
admit	O
another	O
season	O
under	O
achievement	O
would	O
not	O
tolerate	O
the	O
Bernabeu	PERSON
stadium	O
Beckham	PERSON
say	O
	
	
expect	O
Madrid	LOCATION
get	O
through	O
but	O
	
	
relief	O
for	O
the	O
club	O
and	O
player	O
have	O
win	O
	
lose	O
momentum	O
last	O
season	O
but	O
can not	O O
afford	O
	
another	O
season	O
without	O
win	O
anything	O
real	O
finish	O
runner	O
	
they	O
Champions	O
League	O
group	O
means	O
they	O
can not	O O
face	O
he	O
old	O
club	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
the	O
next	O
round	O
but	O
real	O
could	O
draw	O
against	O
other	O
premiership	O
hopeful	O
arsenal	O
Chelsea	PERSON
who	O
win	O
they	O
respective	O
group	O
	
	
go	O
	
great	O
whoever	O
play	O
even	O
	
don	O
get	O
either	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
English	MISC
team	O
man	O
utd	O
through	O
after	O
Exeter	LOCATION
test	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
avoid	O
	
Cup	O
upset	O
edge	O
past	DATE
Exeter	LOCATION
City	O
they	O
third	ORDINAL
round	O
replay	O
Cristiano	PERSON
Ronaldo	PERSON
score	NUMBER
the	O
opener	O
slip	O
the	O
ball	O
between	O
Paul	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
leg	O
after	O
just	O
nine	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
United	O
waste	O
host	O
chance	O
make	O
safe	O
Jones	PERSON
make	O
some	O
great	O
save	O
but	O
Wayne	PERSON
Rooney	PERSON
put	O
the	O
tie	O
beyond	O
doubt	O
late	O
with	O
cool	O
finish	O
Exeter	LOCATION
have	O
chance	O
they	O
own	O
Sean	PERSON
devine	PERSON
twice	O
volley	O
wide	O
and	O
Andrew	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
force	O
Tim	PERSON
Howard	PERSON
save	O
United	O
boss	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
be	O
take	O
few	O
chance	O
after	O
they	O
	
draw	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
game	O
and	O
handed	O
start	O
Paul	PERSON
Scholes	PERSON
and	O
Ryan	PERSON
well	O
Ronaldo	PERSON
and	O
Rooney	PERSON
Exeter	LOCATION
begin	O
brightly	O
with	O
devine	PERSON
and	O
Steve	PERSON
Flack	PERSON
see	O
plenty	O
the	O
ball	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
United	O
long	Sports
assert	O
they	O
authority	O
and	O
the	O
host	O
soon	O
find	O
themselves	O
goal	O
down	O
Scholes	PERSON
play	O
lovely	O
pass	O
	
Ronaldo	PERSON
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
the	O
six	NUMBER
yard	O
box	O
and	O
the	O
portuguese	O
winger	O
slide	O
the	O
ball	O
between	O
the	O
leg	O
Jones	PERSON
open	O
the	O
score	NUMBER
United	O
sense	O
chance	O
finish	O
the	O
tie	O
	
contest	O
early	O
and	O
Ronaldo	PERSON
blaze	O
over	O
before	O
Jones	PERSON
save	O
well	O
from	O
Scholes	PERSON
and	O
then	O
Rooney	PERSON
the	O
visitor	O
pressure	O
now	DATE
be	O
incessant	O
and	O
Rooney	PERSON
have	O
another	O
shot	O
block	O
while	O
Ronaldo	PERSON
slam	O
well	O
over	O
the	O
bar	O
again	O
from	O
good	O
position	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
break	O
Giggs	PERSON
have	O
golden	O
chance	O
double	O
the	O
advantage	O
but	O
the	O
welshman	O
drag	O
left	O
foot	O
effort	O
badly	O
wide	O
from	O
	
yard	O
	
stoppage	O
time	O
Exeter	LOCATION
create	O
they	O
best	O
chance	O
Alex	PERSON
Jeannin	PERSON
swing	O
	
cross	O
from	O
the	O
left	O
that	O
devine	PERSON
manage	O
flick	O
goalwards	O
but	O
the	O
ball	O
fly	O
wide	O
Howard	PERSON
goal	O
the	O
Grecians	MISC
come	O
out	Sports
after	O
the	O
break	O
determine	O
fashion	O
and	O
Howard	PERSON
have	O
show	O
safe	O
hand	O
collect	O
two	NUMBER
search	O
cross	O
into	O
the	O
United	O
box	O
Rooney	PERSON
look	O
like	O
might	O
have	O
seal	O
the	O
result	O
with	O
turn	O
and	O
shot	O
but	O
the	O
ball	O
stick	O
the	O
James	PERSON
Park	O
mud	O
and	O
Jones	PERSON
race	O
back	O
gather	O
the	O
goalline	O
moment	O
later	O
devine	PERSON
have	O
the	O
chance	O
make	O
himself	O
hero	O
but	O
could	O
only	O
volley	O
Jeannin	PERSON
brilliant	O
cross	O
wide	O
Howard	PERSON
goal	O
after	O
be	O
left	O
unmarked	O
six	NUMBER
yard	O
out	Sports
after	O
Rooney	PERSON
have	O
completely	O
mess	O
	
free	O
kick	O
	
yard	O
out	Sports
Taylor	PERSON
show	O
he	O
how	O
should	O
do	O
he	O
stunning	O
drive	Sports
from	O
distance	O
force	O
fly	O
stop	O
from	O
Howard	PERSON
the	O
home	O
crowd	O
be	O
bay	O
for	O
goal	O
and	O
they	O
do	O
get	O
the	O
ball	O
into	O
the	O
net	O
only	O
for	O
devine	PERSON
low	O
effort	O
	
rule	O
out	Sports
for	O
obvious	O
offside	O
the	O
persistent	O
Rooney	PERSON
eventually	O
round	O
Jones	PERSON
with	O
three	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
	
and	O
slot	O
into	O
empty	O
net	O
book	O
home	O
tie	O
with	O
Middlesbrough	ORGANIZATION
the	O
fourth	ORDINAL
round	O
Jones	PERSON
Hiley	PERSON
Sawyer	PERSON
Gaia	PERSON
Jeannin	PERSON
Moxey	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
Martin	PERSON
	
	
Ampadu	PERSON
Afful	PERSON
	
	
Clay	PERSON
Flack	PERSON
Edwards	PERSON
	
	
devine	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Rice	PERSON
Todd	PERSON
Ampadu	PERSON
Clay	PERSON
Howard	PERSON
Phil	PERSON
Neville	PERSON
Gary	PERSON
Neville	PERSON
	
Shea	PERSON
fortune	O
Giggs	PERSON
saha	O
	
	
Miller	PERSON
Fletcher	PERSON
	
	
Scholes	PERSON
djemba	O
djemba	O
Silvestre	PERSON
	
	
Ronaldo	PERSON
Rooney	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Ricardo	PERSON
Bellion	PERSON
Ronaldo	PERSON
	
Rooney	PERSON
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
Dowd	PERSON
Staffordshire	LOCATION
	
Hamm	PERSON
bow	O
out	Sports
for	O
woman	O
football	O
legend	O
Mia	PERSON
Hamm	PERSON
have	O
play	O
she	O
final	O
game	O
Hamm	PERSON
	
who	O
officially	O
retire	O
after	O
this	O
year	DURATION
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
take	O
the	O
field	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
help	O
the	O
claim	O
	
	
win	O
over	O
Mexico	LOCATION
Hamm	PERSON
end	O
she	O
career	O
the	O
most	O
prolific	O
scorer	O
male	O
female	O
	
international	O
football	O
with	O
	
goal	O
	
	
game	O
for	O
the	O
	
she	O
be	O
twice	O
Fifa	O
woman	O
player	O
the	O
year	DURATION
and	O
win	O
the	O
World	O
Cup	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
and	O
two	NUMBER
Olympic	MISC
gold	O
	
she	O
retirement	O
Hamm	PERSON
say	O
there	O
be	O
mixed	O
emotion	O
there	O
be	O
thing	O
you	O
life	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
have	O
put	O
the	O
back	O
burner	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
focus	O
more	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
that	O
now	DATE
	
have	O
see	O
what	O
out	Sports
there	O
and	O
not	O
commit	O
everything	O
the	O
begin	O
the	O
friendly	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
end	O
Julie	PERSON
foudy	O
and	O
Joy	O
Fawcett	PERSON
	
career	O
Hamm	PERSON
will	O
now	DATE
embark	O
	
new	O
life	O
with	O
husband	O
Chicago	LOCATION
Cubs	O
shortstop	O
Nomar	PERSON
Garciaparra	PERSON
who	O
be	O
the	O
stand	O
watch	O
she	O
final	O
game	O
	
have	O
just	O
agree	O
new	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
Cubs	O
after	O
join	O
they	O
July	DATE
Wenger	PERSON
rule	O
out	Sports
new	O
keeper	O
arsenal	O
boss	O
Arsene	PERSON
Wenger	PERSON
say	O
have	O
plan	O
sign	O
new	O
goalkeeper	O
during	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
Wenger	PERSON
have	O
bring	O
Manuel	PERSON
Almunia	PERSON
for	O
the	O
last	O
three	NUMBER
game	O
for	O
the	O
out	Sports
	
form	O
Jens	PERSON
Lehmann	PERSON
but	O
the	O
spaniard	O
himself	O
have	O
be	O
prone	O
mistake	O
there	O
have	O
be	O
suggestion	O
that	O
Wenger	PERSON
will	O
swoop	O
for	O
high	O
quality	O
shot	O
stopper	O
the	O
New	O
year	DURATION
but	O
tell	O
the	O
even	O
Standard	O
	
don	O
feel	O
will	O
necessary	O
bring	O
	
new	O
goalkeeper	O
January	DATE
the	O
gunner	O
manager	O
refuse	O
comment	O
the	O
difficult	O
start	O
that	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Almunia	PERSON
have	O
make	O
he	O
career	O
Highbury	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
draw	O
whether	O
Lehmann	PERSON
would	O
return	O
for	O
the	O
top	O
	
the	O
table	O
clash	O
with	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Sunday	DATE
Almunia	PERSON
be	O
fault	O
for	O
Rosenborg	PERSON
goal	O
arsenal	O
	
	
Champions	O
League	O
win	O
Tuesday	DATE
and	O
have	O
some	O
hairy	O
moment	O
last	O
week	DURATION
win	O
over	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
but	O
Wenger	PERSON
say	O
earlier	O
this	O
week	DURATION
that	O
he	O
indifferent	O
form	O
be	O
down	O
pressure	O
cause	O
be	O
under	O
scrutiny	O
from	O
the	O
media	O
	
the	O
debate	O
have	O
go	O
too	O
long	Sports
everyone	O
have	O
opinion	O
and	O
	
not	O
have	O
add	O
	
	
Wenger	PERSON
add	O
arsenal	O
have	O
be	O
link	O
with	O
Middlesbrough	ORGANIZATION
keeper	O
Mark	PERSON
Schwarzer	PERSON
Fulham	PERSON
Edwin	PERSON
van	O
der	O
Sar	PERSON
and	O
parma	O
Sebastien	PERSON
Frey	PERSON
and	O
Wenger	PERSON
have	O
immediate	O
plan	O
recall	O
former	O
England	LOCATION
under	O
	
international	O
Stuart	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
from	O
he	O
loan	O
spell	O
Leicester	LOCATION
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
pledge	O
keep	O
Gerrard	PERSON
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
chief	O
executive	O
Rick	PERSON
parry	O
insist	O
the	O
club	O
will	O
never	O
sell	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
amid	O
report	O
Chelsea	PERSON
will	O
renew	O
they	O
bid	O
lure	O
he	O
from	O
Anfield	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
reiterate	O
he	O
desire	O
win	O
trophy	O
with	O
the	O
red	O
after	O
he	O
superb	O
Champions	O
League	O
winner	O
Wednesday	DATE
and	O
parry	O
have	O
move	O
scotch	O
claim	O
that	O
Chelsea	PERSON
could	O
launch	O
#	O
m	O
bid	O
	
there	O
	
chance	O
Stevie	PERSON
go	O
January	DATE
say	O
parry	O
	
that	O
just	O
win	O
happen	O
we	O
intention	O
that	O
will	O
never	O
let	O
he	O
	
Gerrard	PERSON
score	NUMBER
spectacular	O
late	O
goal	O
give	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
	
	
win	O
over	O
olympiako	O
and	O
book	O
they	O
place	O
the	O
knockout	O
stage	O
	
course	O
	
ambitious	O
but	O
be	O
	
parry	O
add	O
	
firmly	O
believe	O
that	O
	
can	O
satisfy	O
he	O
ambition	O
will	O
remain	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
player	O
	
have	O
open	O
and	O
straightforward	O
relationship	O
	
both	O
know	O
where	O
stand	O
and	O
that	O
play	O
big	O
part	O
he	O
decision	O
stay	O
last	O
summer	DATE
	
be	O
not	O
commit	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
would	O
have	O
go	O
now	DATE
Gerrard	PERSON
have	O
say	O
before	O
Wednesday	DATE
game	O
would	O
consider	O
leave	O
the	O
club	O
be	O
knock	O
out	Sports
Europe	LOCATION
with	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
also	O
believe	O
	
monitor	O
he	O
situation	O
	
the	O
main	O
point	O
have	O
make	O
	
want	O
	
	
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
side	O
which	O
challenge	O
for	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
and	O
the	O
title	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
	
say	O
afterwards	O
	
want	O
	
win	O
thing	O
with	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
not	O
somewhere	O
else	O
	
	
fan	O
well	O
and	O
think	O
what	O
have	O
say	O
the	O
supporter	O
will	O
agree	O
with	O
	
have	O
build	O
win	O
like	O
that	O
not	O
just	O
settle	O
for	O
great	O
win	O
and	O
then	O
not	O
progress	O
any	O
further	O
	
goal	O
be	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
most	O
important	O
have	O
ever	O
score	NUMBER
and	O
hope	O
turn	O
out	Sports
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
most	O
important	O
for	O
the	O
club	O
for	O
long	Sports
time	O
	
know	O
put	O
lot	O
pressure	O
myself	O
because	O
what	O
say	O
and	O
feel	O
need	O
big	O
performance	O
but	O
	
not	O
go	O
	
around	O
tell	O
lie	O
about	O
how	O
feel	O
red	O
manager	O
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
believe	O
Gerrard	PERSON
can	O
win	O
everything	O
want	O
without	O
move	O
club	O
	
Steven	PERSON
can	O
win	O
all	O
want	O
with	O
and	O
need	O
he	O
	
have	O
see	O
that	O
have	O
good	O
team	O
and	O
can	O
more	O
thing	O
the	O
future	DATE
say	O
Benitez	PERSON
	
but	O
	
want	O
win	O
more	O
game	O
important	O
game	O
need	O
Steven	PERSON
the	O
team	O
	
need	O
he	O
strength	O
the	O
strong	O
mentality	O
have	O
and	O
he	O
quality	O
	
think	O
likes	O
and	O
want	O
the	O
responsibility	O
lead	O
this	O
team	O
Pearce	PERSON
keen	O
succeed	O
Keegan	PERSON
Joint	O
assistant	O
boss	O
Stuart	PERSON
Pearce	PERSON
have	O
admit	O
would	O
like	O
succeed	O
Kevin	PERSON
Keegan	PERSON
manager	O
Manchester	LOCATION
City	O
Keegan	PERSON
have	O
decide	O
step	O
down	O
City	O
manager	O
when	O
he	O
contract	O
come	O
	
end	O
	
month	DURATION
	
you	O
don	O
have	O
	
Einstein	PERSON
realise	O
there	O
will	O
	
manager	O
job	O
available	O
	
really	O
good	O
club	O
Pearce	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
GMR	O
	
will	O
certainly	O
apply	O
for	O
	
although	O
whether	O
the	O
board	O
deem	O
good	O
enough	O
take	O
	
	
not	O
know	O
Pearce	PERSON
initially	O
join	O
City	O
	
player	O
under	O
Keegan	PERSON
	
	
before	O
become	O
part	O
the	O
coaching	O
staff	O
	
be	O
promote	O
joint	O
assistant	O
manager	O
follow	O
the	O
departure	O
Arthur	PERSON
cox	O
last	O
summer	DATE
the	O
former	O
England	LOCATION
defender	O
have	O
year	DURATION
player	O
boss	O
with	O
Nottingham	PERSON
forest	O
eight	NUMBER
season	O
ago	O
but	O
have	O
make	O
secret	O
he	O
desire	O
have	O
another	O
crack	O
the	O
job	O
	
be	O
link	O
with	O
the	O
manager	O
job	O
Oldham	PERSON
and	O
Keegan	PERSON
have	O
state	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
way	O
Pearce	PERSON
want	O
leave	O
but	O
now	DATE
appear	O
Pearce	PERSON
keen	O
wait	O
for	O
he	O
chance	O
City	O
	
add	O
	
that	O
time	O
will	O
have	O
be	O
here	O
for	O
five	NUMBER
year	DURATION
	
least	O
they	O
will	O
have	O
have	O
good	O
look	O
	
and	O
they	O
be	O
aware	O
	
feeling	O
with	O
regard	O
be	O
Kevin	PERSON
successor	O
	
obviously	O
the	O
issue	O
out	Sports
	
hand	O
but	O
	
fantastic	O
job	O
for	O
anybody	O
	
just	O
hope	O
will	O
bomb	O
threat	O
Bernabeu	PERSON
stadium	O
spectator	O
be	O
evacuate	O
from	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
Bernabeu	PERSON
stadium	O
Sunday	DATE
follow	O
bomb	O
scare	O
during	O
the	O
game	O
between	O
the	O
host	O
and	O
real	O
Sociedad	PERSON
more	O
than	O
	
	
	
people	O
abandon	O
the	O
ground	O
with	O
the	O
score	NUMBER
	
	
and	O
only	O
three	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
left	O
play	O
the	O
basque	O
newspaper	O
Gara	PERSON
apparently	O
receive	O
telephone	O
call	O
say	O
bomb	O
be	O
due	O
explode	O
	
	
local	O
time	O
but	O
after	O
search	O
the	O
stadium	O
with	O
sniffer	O
dog	O
the	O
police	O
say	O
that	O
explosive	O
device	O
have	O
be	O
find	O
	
the	O
police	O
have	O
say	O
they	O
have	O
complete	O
they	O
search	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
find	O
anything	O
say	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
president	O
florentino	O
Perez	PERSON
	
the	O
best	O
thing	O
can	O
all	O
now	DATE
	
put	O
this	O
nightmare	O
behind	O
	
Madrid	LOCATION
midfielder	O
Guti	PERSON
tell	O
private	O
spanish	O
radio	O
station	O
Cadena	PERSON
ser	O
	
have	O
never	O
see	O
this	O
before	O
and	O
sport	O
should	O
above	O
all	O
real	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
break	O
when	O
brazilian	O
striker	O
Ronaldo	PERSON
crack	O
home	O
with	O
he	O
left	O
foot	O
Sociedad	PERSON
level	O
the	O
match	O
midway	O
through	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
half	O
when	O
turkish	O
striker	O
Nihat	PERSON
Kahveci	PERSON
smash	O
home	O
with	O
acrobatic	O
finish	O
	
not	O
yet	O
clear	O
the	O
remain	O
three	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
the	O
game	O
will	O
play	O
	
later	O
date	O
	
the	O
result	O
will	O
allow	O
stand	O
	
the	O
result	O
remains	O
	
	
real	O
will	O
drop	O
third	ORDINAL
place	O
the	O
standing	O
	
point	O
behind	O
leader	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
who	O
snatch	O
late	O
	
win	O
Albacete	PERSON
Saturday	DATE
initial	O
report	O
suggest	O
the	O
basque	O
separatist	O
group	O
ETA	ORGANIZATION
may	O
responsible	O
for	O
the	O
bomb	O
threat	O
after	O
issue	O
similar	O
warning	O
before	O
series	O
small	O
explosion	O
recent	O
day	DURATION
the	O
Bernabeu	PERSON
be	O
target	O
ETA	ORGANIZATION
	
May	DATE
	
	
when	O
Madrid	LOCATION
be	O
about	O
play	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
	
Champions	O
League	O
semi	O
final	O
	
car	O
bomb	O
explode	O
	
street	O
outside	O
the	O
stadium	O
and	O
	
people	O
be	O
slightly	O
injure	O
Chelsea	PERSON
hold	O
arsenal	O
	
grip	O
game	O
between	O
arsenal	O
and	O
Chelsea	PERSON
end	O
with	O
the	O
honour	O
finish	O
even	O
Highbury	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
produce	O
sublime	O
strike	O
put	O
arsenal	O
ahead	O
but	O
John	PERSON
Terry	PERSON
level	O
with	O
powerful	O
header	O
Henry	PERSON
quickly	O
take	O
free	O
kick	O
put	O
arsenal	O
back	O
front	O
but	O
Eidur	PERSON
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
equalise	O
with	O
header	O
from	O
William	PERSON
Gallas	PERSON
knockback	O
Henry	PERSON
miss	O
golden	O
chance	O
when	O
blaze	O
shot	O
high	O
late	O
and	O
arsenal	O
also	O
have	O
penalty	O
appeal	O
reject	O
Henry	PERSON
opener	O
have	O
give	O
arsenal	O
the	O
perfect	O
start	O
and	O
set	O
	
enthral	O
affair	O
the	O
french	O
striker	O
head	O
long	Sports
Cesc	PERSON
Faregas	PERSON
ball	O
back	O
Jose	PERSON
Antonio	PERSON
Reyes	PERSON
from	O
the	O
edge	O
the	O
Chelsea	PERSON
area	O
and	O
immediately	O
saw	O
head	O
back	O
into	O
he	O
path	O
from	O
the	O
spaniard	O
and	O
with	O
he	O
back	O
goal	O
Henry	PERSON
finish	O
with	O
aplomb	O
when	O
take	O
one	NUMBER
touch	O
turn	O
and	O
strike	O
angled	O
strike	O
past	DATE
the	O
despair	O
dive	O
keeper	O
Petr	PERSON
Cech	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
epitomise	O
determination	O
about	O
the	O
arsenal	O
side	O
but	O
Chelsea	PERSON
appear	O
unruffled	O
and	O
equalise	O
after	O
	
minute	DURATION
gunner	O
keeper	O
Manuel	PERSON
Almunia	PERSON
who	O
get	O
the	O
nod	O
ahead	O
Jens	PERSON
Lehmann	PERSON
do	O
well	O
save	O
well	O
strike	O
Frank	PERSON
Lampard	PERSON
shot	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
out	Sports
Terry	PERSON
power	O
header	O
from	O
the	O
resultant	O
corner	O
arsenal	O
weakness	O
set	O
piece	O
be	O
again	O
expose	O
almost	O
immediately	O
Henry	PERSON
go	O
close	O
and	O
Chelsea	PERSON
gather	O
the	O
loose	O
ball	O
before	O
go	O
straight	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
where	O
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
fluff	O
effort	O
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
do	O
not	O
make	O
the	O
same	O
error	O
minute	DURATION
later	O
when	O
strike	O
sweet	O
shot	O
only	O
for	O
Almunia	PERSON
	
equal	O
the	O
task	O
and	O
save	O
the	O
home	O
side	O
regain	O
the	O
lead	O
controversial	O
fashion	O
when	O
Robert	PERSON
Pires	PERSON
win	O
dubious	O
free	O
kick	O
and	O
give	O
the	O
option	O
take	O
the	O
	
yard	O
set	O
piece	O
quickly	O
Henry	PERSON
curl	O
	
shot	O
with	O
Cech	PERSON
still	O
organise	O
he	O
wall	O
this	O
time	O
arsenal	O
do	O
not	O
allow	O
Chelsea	PERSON
level	O
soon	O
they	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
break	O
ahead	O
Chelsea	PERSON
bring	O
striker	O
Didier	PERSON
Drogba	PERSON
	
partner	O
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
front	O
after	O
the	O
interval	O
and	O
the	O
move	O
reap	O
immediate	O
reward	O
Lampard	PERSON
swing	O
	
cross	O
which	O
Gallas	PERSON
knock	O
back	O
across	O
goal	O
and	O
deft	O
header	O
from	O
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
level	O
matter	O
again	O
Chelsea	PERSON
main	O
threat	O
be	O
come	O
from	O
cross	O
and	O
Lampard	PERSON
miss	O
great	O
opportunity	O
	
head	O
wide	O
when	O
left	O
unmarked	O
the	O
far	O
post	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
half	O
fail	O
live	O
	
the	O
thrilling	O
pace	O
the	O
open	O
period	O
but	O
there	O
be	O
flash	O
brilliance	O
one	NUMBER
they	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
enigmatic	O
Robben	PERSON
when	O
jink	O
he	O
way	O
through	O
two	NUMBER
arsenal	O
defender	O
only	O
see	O
he	O
poke	O
shot	O
save	O
Almunia	PERSON
arsenal	O
end	O
the	O
match	O
the	O
stronger	O
and	O
work	O
excellent	O
chance	O
for	O
Henry	PERSON
who	O
put	O
left	O
foot	O
shot	O
high	O
from	O
eight	NUMBER
yard	O
subtitute	O
Robin	PERSON
van	O
Persie	PERSON
could	O
also	O
have	O
nick	O
win	O
for	O
the	O
Highbury	O
outfit	O
but	O
frustratingly	O
sidefoot	O
just	O
wide	O
Matthieu	PERSON
Flamini	PERSON
have	O
late	O
penal	O
appeal	O
wave	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
final	O
whistle	O
which	O
maintain	O
Chelsea	PERSON
five	NUMBER
point	O
premiership	O
lead	O
over	O
arsenal	O
Almunia	PERSON
Lauren	PERSON
Toure	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
Cole	O
Pires	PERSON
Flamini	PERSON
Fabregas	PERSON
Reyes	PERSON
Clichy	PERSON
	
	
Bergkamp	PERSON
Van	PERSON
Persie	PERSON
	
	
Henry	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Senderos	PERSON
Hoyte	PERSON
Lehmann	PERSON
Cole	O
Henry	PERSON
	
	
	
Cech	PERSON
Paulo	PERSON
Ferreira	PERSON
Ricardo	PERSON
Carvalho	PERSON
Drogba	PERSON
	
	
Terry	PERSON
Gallas	PERSON
Duff	PERSON
Tiago	PERSON
Bridge	O
	
	
Makelele	PERSON
Lampard	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
Parker	PERSON
	
	
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Kezman	PERSON
Cudicini	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
Drogba	PERSON
Lampard	PERSON
Terry	PERSON
	
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
	
	
	
	
	
	
Poll	O
Hertfordshire	LOCATION
	
real	O
will	O
finish	O
abandon	O
match	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
and	O
real	O
socieded	O
will	O
play	O
the	O
final	O
six	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
they	O
match	O
which	O
be	O
abandon	O
Sunday	DATE
because	O
	
bomb	O
scare	O
the	O
Bernabeu	PERSON
be	O
evacuate	O
with	O
the	O
score	NUMBER
	
	
and	O
two	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
normal	O
time	O
remain	O
the	O
game	O
the	O
team	O
will	O
now	DATE
play	O
the	O
final	O
two	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
plus	O
four	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
injury	O
time	O
	
January	DATE
brazilian	O
Ronaldo	PERSON
and	O
England	LOCATION
captain	O
David	PERSON
Beckham	PERSON
have	O
wait	O
the	O
street	O
they	O
kit	O
after	O
the	O
abandonment	O
real	O
Sociedad	PERSON
president	O
Jose	PERSON
Luis	PERSON
astiazaran	O
say	O
	
thought	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
be	O
play	O
the	O
time	O
remain	O
hundred	NUMBER
fan	O
stream	O
across	O
the	O
pitch	O
they	O
way	O
the	O
exit	O
after	O
the	O
game	O
be	O
call	O
off	O
tourist	O
and	O
fan	O
take	O
advantage	O
the	O
opportunity	O
for	O
photograph	O
between	O
the	O
famous	O
stadium	O
goalpost	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
club	O
meet	O
the	O
spanish	O
	
Monday	DATE
and	O
astiazaran	O
add	O
	
thought	O
about	O
give	O
the	O
game	O
conclude	O
but	O
after	O
talk	O
with	O
the	O
	
decide	O
there	O
be	O
precedent	O
for	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
best	O
thing	O
be	O
play	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
be	O
remain	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
director	O
sport	O
Emilio	PERSON
Butragueno	PERSON
praise	O
the	O
spectator	O
inside	O
the	O
ground	O
for	O
they	O
conduct	O
	
	
like	O
highlight	O
the	O
behaviour	O
the	O
fan	O
who	O
show	O
great	O
maturity	O
and	O
be	O
example	O
good	O
citizenship	O
	
say	O
Butragueno	PERSON
confirn	O
before	O
confirm	O
that	O
Tuesday	DATE
charity	O
match	O
which	O
have	O
be	O
bill	O
	
Ronaldo	PERSON
friend	O
against	O
Zidane	PERSON
friend	O
will	O
ahead	O
plan	O
	
	
also	O
like	O
take	O
the	O
chance	O
say	O
that	O
tomorrow	DATE
game	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
Butragueno	PERSON
declare	O
the	O
Partido	PERSON
contra	O
Pobreza	PERSON
game	O
against	O
poverty	O
	
add	O
football	O
important	O
for	O
society	O
and	O
want	O
show	O
that	O
	
also	O
think	O
that	O
football	O
should	O
	
fiesta	O
have	O
program	O
and	O
people	O
deserve	O
enjoy	O
the	O
game	O
Poll	O
explain	O
free	O
kick	O
decision	O
referee	O
Graham	PERSON
Poll	O
say	O
apply	O
the	O
law	O
the	O
game	O
allow	O
arsenal	O
striker	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
free	O
kick	O
Sunday	DATE
	
	
draw	O
with	O
Chelsea	PERSON
keeper	O
Petr	PERSON
Cech	PERSON
be	O
organise	O
he	O
defensive	O
wall	O
when	O
Henry	PERSON
quick	O
free	O
kick	O
fly	O
	
which	O
angered	O
Chelsea	PERSON
	
the	O
whistle	O
doesn	O
need	O
	
blow	O
	
ask	O
Henry	PERSON
	
you	O
want	O
wall	O
	
	
say	O
can	O
take	O
please	O
	
be	O
very	O
polite	O
	
say	O
yes	O
	
say	O
Poll	O
	
deal	O
with	O
the	O
law	O
the	O
game	O
	
deal	O
with	O
fact	O
Poll	O
add	O
	
give	O
the	O
signal	O
for	O
he	O
take	O
	
that	O
what	O
do	O
	
the	O
same	O
thing	O
happen	O
when	O
referee	O
Chelsea	PERSON
against	O
West	O
ham	O
	
Cup	O
replay	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ago	O
when	O
Jimmy	PERSON
Floyd	PERSON
Hasselbaink	PERSON
score	NUMBER
and	O
don	O
remember	O
they	O
complain	O
about	O
that	O
Henry	PERSON
explain	O
why	O
pause	O
before	O
striking	O
the	O
ball	O
for	O
the	O
goal	O
which	O
put	O
arsenal	O
	
ahead	O
Henry	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
radio	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
the	O
ref	O
ask	O
	
want	O
	
yard	O
	
want	O
take	O
straight	O
away	O
and	O
say	O
that	O
want	O
take	O
straight	O
away	O
	
say	O
	
	
	
	
	
look	O
bit	O
strange	O
because	O
take	O
time	O
	
be	O
wait	O
for	O
Eidur	PERSON
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
move	O
and	O
give	O
some	O
space	O
	
one	NUMBER
point	O
turn	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
try	O
	
Former	O
referee	O
chief	O
Philip	PERSON
Don	PERSON
back	O
Poll	O
decision	O
allow	O
the	O
strike	O
	
the	O
advantage	O
should	O
	
the	O
non	O
offend	O
team	O
	
this	O
occasion	O
be	O
arsenal	O
Don	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
radio	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
	
referee	O
have	O
be	O
tell	O
ask	O
the	O
player	O
	
you	O
want	O
take	O
the	O
quick	O
free	O
kick	O
	
	
you	O
want	O
	
get	O
the	O
wall	O
back	O
	
	
metre	O
	
they	O
say	O
quick	O
the	O
referee	O
tend	O
move	O
away	O
and	O
allow	O
the	O
kick	O
Don	PERSON
be	O
head	O
the	O
referee	O
for	O
the	O
Premier	O
League	O
and	O
reveal	O
all	O
club	O
be	O
inform	O
free	O
kick	O
option	O
	
speak	O
all	O
the	O
Premier	O
League	O
club	O
well	O
all	O
the	O
football	O
League	O
club	O
the	O
summer	DATE
	
	
explain	O
what	O
the	O
situation	O
be	O
	
add	O
	
give	O
they	O
the	O
option	O
either	O
the	O
quick	O
free	O
kick	O
the	O
ceremonial	O
free	O
kick	O
player	O
and	O
club	O
be	O
aware	O
what	O
referee	O
be	O
do	O
Solskjaer	PERSON
raise	O
hope	O
return	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
striker	O
ole	O
Gunnar	PERSON
Solskjaer	PERSON
say	O
hope	O
return	O
next	O
season	O
follow	O
career	O
threaten	O
injury	O
he	O
right	O
knee	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Norway	LOCATION
international	O
have	O
surgery	O
Sweden	LOCATION
August	DATE
transplant	O
cartilage	O
into	O
the	O
joint	O
	
	
	
doubt	O
that	O
	
play	O
again	O
Solskjaer	PERSON
tell	O
Aftenposten	O
Daily	SET
	
the	O
problem	O
will	O
the	O
speed	O
but	O
	
talk	O
about	O
eight	NUMBER
month	DURATION
time	O
	
	
go	O
	
should	O
with	O
the	O
knee	O
	
	
slavishly	O
follow	O
programme	O
Solskjaer	PERSON
last	O
play	O
for	O
United	O
	
late	O
substitute	O
May	DATE
	
Cup	O
final	O
win	O
over	O
Millwall	PERSON
he	O
contract	O
with	O
United	O
run	O
out	Sports
	
	
	
which	O
time	O
will	O
have	O
be	O
the	O
Premier	O
League	O
club	O
for	O
	
year	DURATION
Dunne	PERSON
keen	O
commit	O
man	O
City	O
Richard	PERSON
Dunne	PERSON
ready	O
commit	O
he	O
long	Sports
term	O
future	DATE
Manchester	LOCATION
City	O
after	O
turn	O
he	O
career	O
around	O
	
be	O
once	DATE
threaten	O
with	O
the	O
sack	O
City	O
boss	O
Kevin	PERSON
Keegan	PERSON
but	O
have	O
since	O
respond	O
with	O
impressive	O
performance	O
prompt	O
interest	O
from	O
other	O
club	O
early	O
talk	O
have	O
take	O
place	O
and	O
the	O
defender	O
say	O
hopefully	O
something	O
will	O
sort	O
out	Sports
soon	O
possible	O
	
definitely	O
want	O
stay	O
City	O
because	O
have	O
really	O
improve	O
	
player	O
here	O
Newcastle	PERSON
boss	O
Graeme	PERSON
Souness	PERSON
say	O
have	O
be	O
impressed	O
enough	O
Dunne	PERSON
turnaround	O
form	O
	
ready	O
make	O
bid	O
for	O
the	O
big	O
stopper	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
but	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
dubliner	O
underline	O
he	O
intention	O
stay	O
eastland	O
	
add	O
	
	
nice	O
	
link	O
with	O
top	O
club	O
but	O
the	O
important	O
thing	O
this	O
one	NUMBER
and	O
what	O
	
	
	
really	O
enjoy	O
	
City	O
and	O
want	O
keep	O
that	O
go	O
Keegan	PERSON
expect	O
	
tell	O
there	O
will	O
	
fund	O
bring	O
fresh	O
face	O
January	DATE
Dunne	PERSON
professionalism	O
be	O
famously	O
question	O
Keegan	PERSON
who	O
order	O
the	O
defender	O
home	O
after	O
allegedly	O
turn	O
for	O
training	O
	
dishevelled	O
state	O
but	O
Dunne	PERSON
keen	O
put	O
that	O
period	O
he	O
life	O
behind	O
he	O
and	O
say	O
	
	
grow	O
	
lot	O
and	O
the	O
manager	O
see	O
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
most	O
experienced	O
player	O
the	O
squad	O
	
	
play	O
more	O
game	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
outfield	O
player	O
this	O
season	O
	
can	O
	
regard	O
be	O
kid	O
any	O
more	O
	
have	O
use	O
that	O
add	O
pressure	O
perform	O
and	O
apart	O
from	O
the	O
game	O
Newcastle	PERSON
and	O
Middlesbrough	ORGANIZATION
defensively	O
	
do	O
quite	O
well	O
Keegan	PERSON
set	O
for	O
another	O
boost	O
when	O
goalkeeper	O
Nicky	PERSON
Weaver	PERSON
make	O
he	O
long	Sports
await	O
return	O
	
reserve	O
game	O
Blackburn	PERSON
Tuesday	DATE
Former	O
England	LOCATION
under	O
	
keeper	O
Weaver	PERSON
have	O
miss	O
nearly	O
three	NUMBER
full	O
season	O
with	O
succession	O
knee	O
injury	O
which	O
eventually	O
need	O
pioneering	O
transplant	O
surgery	O
earlier	O
this	O
year	DURATION
Bates	PERSON
seal	O
takeover	O
Ken	PERSON
Bates	PERSON
have	O
complete	O
he	O
takeover	O
leed	O
United	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
former	O
Chelsea	PERSON
chairman	O
seal	O
the	O
deal	O
	
	
GMT	MISC
Friday	DATE
and	O
have	O
buy	O
	
	
stake	O
the	O
club	O
	
say	O
	
	
delighted	O
	
step	O
	
the	O
mantel	O
such	O
fantastic	O
club	O
	
recognise	O
leed	O
	
great	O
club	O
that	O
have	O
fall	DATE
hard	O
time	O
	
have	O
lot	O
hard	O
work	O
ahead	O
get	O
the	O
club	O
back	O
where	O
belong	O
the	O
premiership	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
we	O
fan	O
will	O
everything	O
can	O
Bates	PERSON
buy	O
he	O
stake	O
under	O
the	O
guise	O
	
Geneva	LOCATION
base	O
company	O
know	O
the	O
forward	O
Sports	O
Fund	O
	
reveal	O
that	O
part	O
he	O
plan	O
	
buy	O
back	O
leed	O
Elland	PERSON
Road	O
stadium	O
and	O
Thorp	PERSON
Arch	O
training	O
ground	O
due	O
course	O
	
	
	
go	O
	
tough	O
jon	O
and	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
task	O
	
stabilise	O
the	O
cash	O
flow	O
and	O
sort	O
out	Sports
the	O
remain	O
creditor	O
Bates	PERSON
add	O
	
but	O
there	O
light	O
the	O
end	O
	
very	O
long	Sports
tunnel	O
for	O
the	O
past	DATE
year	DURATION
have	O
be	O
matter	O
firefighting	O
now	DATE
can	O
start	O
run	O
the	O
club	O
again	O
outgoing	O
leed	O
chairman	O
Gerald	PERSON
Krasner	PERSON
say	O
this	O
deal	O
ensure	O
the	O
medium	O
long	Sports
term	O
survival	O
the	O
club	O
and	O
believe	O
Bates	PERSON
proposal	O
be	O
totally	O
for	O
the	O
benefit	O
the	O
club	O
	
be	O
content	O
that	O
under	O
Bates	PERSON
leed	O
United	O
will	O
continue	O
consolidate	O
and	O
move	O
forward	O
	
when	O
take	O
over	O
leed	O
United	O
March	DATE
	
	
the	O
club	O
have	O
debt	O
#	O
	
m	O
since	O
that	O
date	O
board	O
have	O
succeed	O
reduce	O
the	O
debt	O
under	O
#	O
m	O
	
work	O
tirelessly	O
solve	O
all	O
the	O
problem	O
leed	O
United	O
	
eighty	NUMBER
percent	O
the	O
problem	O
have	O
already	O
be	O
overcome	O
and	O
come	O
this	O
agreement	O
with	O
Bates	PERSON
secure	O
its	O
ongoing	O
success	O
Krasner	PERSON
reveal	O
that	O
he	O
consortium	O
have	O
be	O
ask	O
remain	O
the	O
background	O
the	O
club	O
for	O
undisclosed	O
period	O
help	O
ensure	O
smooth	O
hand	O
over	O
	
will	O
stay	O
	
unpaid	O
capacity	O
while	O
Peter	PERSON
Lorimer	PERSON
will	O
continue	O
he	O
role	O
director	O
and	O
point	O
contact	O
for	O
the	O
fan	O
and	O
Peter	PERSON
McCormick	PERSON
will	O
serve	O
	
consultant	O
the	O
incoming	O
board	O
the	O
other	O
outgoing	O
director	O
have	O
agree	O
leave	O
they	O
loan	O
#	O
	
m	O
the	O
company	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
	
leed	O
new	O
look	O
board	O
	
understand	O
that	O
Lorimer	PERSON
will	O
join	O
former	O
Chelsea	PERSON
finance	O
director	O
Yvonne	PERSON
Todd	PERSON
and	O
Bates	PERSON
lawyer	O
Mark	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
Krasner	PERSON
refuse	O
give	O
any	O
detail	O
the	O
finances	O
involve	O
the	O
takeover	O
	
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
five	NUMBER
Live	O
	
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
figure	O
	
Ken	PERSON
want	O
give	O
they	O
that	O
	
he	O
	
can	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
the	O
money	O
will	O
use	O
for	O
	
this	O
dea	O
	
not	O
about	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
current	DATE
board	O
	
the	O
last	O
four	NUMBER
month	DURATION
never	O
saw	O
any	O
cheque	O
until	O
this	O
week	DURATION
from	O
one	NUMBER
person	O
	
not	O
stretch	O
figure	O
don	O
discuss	O
internal	O
arrangement	O
Bates	PERSON
step	O
down	O
Chelsea	PERSON
chairman	O
March	DATE
last	O
year	DURATION
follow	O
Roman	MISC
Abramovich	PERSON
#	O
	
m	O
takeover	O
Stamford	LOCATION
Bridge	O
	
May	DATE
make	O
proposal	O
invest	O
#	O
m	O
Sheffield	PERSON
Wednesday	DATE
but	O
this	O
be	O
reject	O
the	O
club	O
Sebastien	PERSON
Sainsbury	PERSON
have	O
be	O
close	O
	
takeover	O
leed	O
but	O
withdraw	O
he	O
#	O
m	O
offer	O
last	O
week	DURATION
he	O
effort	O
fail	O
after	O
reveal	O
would	O
take	O
#	O
m	O
stage	O
takeover	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
club	O
will	O
also	O
lose	O
#	O
m	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
six	NUMBER
month	DURATION
the	O
club	O
be	O
the	O
brink	O
administration	O
and	O
the	O
deduction	O
	
point	O
the	O
football	O
League	O
before	O
Bates	PERSON
arrival	O
but	O
he	O
investment	O
have	O
spare	O
they	O
that	O
prospect	O
Ferguson	PERSON
rue	O
failure	O
cut	O
gap	O
Boss	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
be	O
left	O
rue	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
failure	O
close	O
the	O
gap	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Everton	ORGANIZATION
and	O
arsenal	O
after	O
he	O
side	O
	
	
draw	O
with	O
Fulham	PERSON
premiership	O
leader	O
Chelsea	PERSON
and	O
the	O
gunner	O
endure	O
	
	
stalemate	O
Sunday	DATE
give	O
United	O
the	O
chance	O
make	O
some	O
ground	O
the	O
league	O
but	O
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
	
think	O
what	O
make	O
	
bad	O
that	O
both	O
we	O
rival	O
drop	O
point	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
	
be	O
great	O
opportunity	O
and	O
haven	O
deliver	O
United	O
go	O
ahead	O
through	O
Alan	PERSON
Smith	PERSON
the	O
	
rd	O
minute	DURATION
before	O
Bouba	PERSON
Diop	PERSON
superb	O
	
yard	O
strike	O
cancel	O
out	Sports
the	O
visitor	O
lead	O
the	O
	
th	O
minute	DURATION
Ferguson	PERSON
describe	O
the	O
result	O
	
absolute	O
giveaway	O
after	O
United	O
have	O
earlier	O
miss	O
host	O
opportunity	O
finish	O
off	O
the	O
encounter	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
good	O
performance	O
some	O
the	O
football	O
be	O
fantastic	O
but	O
just	O
didn	O
finish	O
they	O
off	O
	
fairness	O
	
	
fantastic	O
strike	O
from	O
the	O
Fulham	PERSON
player	O
the	O
result	O
leaf	O
Ferguson	PERSON
side	O
fourth	ORDINAL
the	O
league	O
	
point	O
four	NUMBER
point	O
behind	O
arsenal	O
and	O
further	O
five	NUMBER
back	O
from	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Old	O
firm	O
pair	O
handed	O
suspension	O
celtic	O
Henri	PERSON
Camara	PERSON
and	O
Nacho	PERSON
Novo	O
Rangers	O
have	O
both	O
be	O
suspend	O
for	O
offence	O
miss	O
the	O
referee	O
	
recent	O
Old	O
firm	O
game	O
both	O
be	O
give	O
automatic	O
one	NUMBER
match	O
ban	O
and	O
	
additional	O
disciplinary	O
point	O
for	O
they	O
action	O
that	O
means	O
Novo	O
will	O
miss	O
further	O
two	NUMBER
game	O
because	O
he	O
prior	O
record	O
Camara	PERSON
will	O
miss	O
one	NUMBER
additional	O
game	O
Novo	O
be	O
find	O
guilty	O
stamp	O
celtic	O
Stephen	PERSON
Pearson	PERSON
Camara	PERSON
be	O
punish	O
for	O
kick	O
Gregory	PERSON
vignal	O
	
	
extremely	O
disappointed	O
	
don	O
know	O
there	O
	
lot	O
add	O
that	O
say	O
Rangers	O
manager	O
Alex	PERSON
McLeish	PERSON
Novo	O
punishment	O
	
but	O
what	O
will	O
say	O
that	O
	
	
loss	O
	
why	O
that	O
incident	O
should	O
pick	O
and	O
highlight	O
when	O
there	O
be	O
many	O
other	O
incident	O
during	O
the	O
game	O
both	O
player	O
will	O
miss	O
this	O
weekend	DATE
game	O
when	O
celtic	O
host	O
Dundee	PERSON
United	O
and	O
Rangers	O
visit	O
Kilmarnock	PERSON
unless	O
they	O
decide	O
appeal	O
the	O
additional	O
ban	O
come	O
into	O
effect	O
from	O
	
December	DATE
mean	O
Camara	PERSON
will	O
also	O
unavailable	O
for	O
the	O
home	O
game	O
against	O
Livingston	PERSON
while	O
Novo	O
will	O
miss	O
the	O
meeting	O
with	O
Dundee	PERSON
United	O
and	O
Dunfermline	PERSON
	
sfa	O
spokesman	O
say	O
they	O
have	O
seven	NUMBER
day	DURATION
appeal	O
but	O
with	O
match	O
come	O
along	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
they	O
would	O
need	O
	
before	O
Friday	DATE
	
but	O
they	O
appeal	O
win	O
	
hear	O
before	O
this	O
weekend	DATE
because	O
take	O
bit	O
time	O
seat	O
	
appeal	O
tribunal	O
meanwhile	O
Bob	PERSON
Malcolm	PERSON
and	O
Rangers	O
have	O
be	O
inform	O
letter	O
	
the	O
outcome	O
the	O
hearing	O
regard	O
he	O
reaction	O
Rangers	O
be	O
award	O
penalty	O
the	O
same	O
game	O
Malcolm	PERSON
substitute	O
the	O
day	DURATION
be	O
take	O
from	O
the	O
Rangers	O
dig	O
out	Sports
and	O
speak	O
	
police	O
about	O
allege	O
gesture	O
make	O
but	O
the	O
sfa	O
would	O
not	O
detail	O
what	O
any	O
punishment	O
Malcolm	PERSON
would	O
receive	O
	
once	DATE
Rangers	O
receive	O
we	O
letter	O
will	O
	
position	O
make	O
comment	O
the	O
finding	O
add	O
the	O
spokesman	O
Anelka	PERSON
apologise	O
for	O
criticism	O
Manchester	LOCATION
City	O
striker	O
Nicolas	PERSON
Anelka	PERSON
have	O
issue	O
apology	O
for	O
criticise	O
the	O
ambition	O
the	O
club	O
Anelka	PERSON
be	O
quote	O
	
french	O
newspaper	O
say	O
would	O
like	O
play	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
for	O
bigger	O
club	O
but	O
chairman	O
John	PERSON
Wardle	PERSON
say	O
	
	
speak	O
Nicolas	PERSON
and	O
	
apologise	O
for	O
anything	O
that	O
might	O
have	O
be	O
mistakenly	O
take	O
from	O
the	O
french	O
press	O
	
be	O
big	O
club	O
Nicolas	PERSON
tell	O
that	O
agree	O
with	O
that	O
be	O
big	O
club	O
Wardle	PERSON
be	O
speak	O
the	O
club	O
annual	SET
general	O
meeting	O
where	O
also	O
confirm	O
the	O
club	O
have	O
not	O
receive	O
any	O
bid	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
arsenal	O
and	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
striker	O
the	O
club	O
still	O
owe	O
french	O
club	O
psg	O
#	O
m	O
from	O
the	O
purchase	O
Anelka	PERSON
May	DATE
	
	
	
have	O
be	O
link	O
with	O
move	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
and	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
and	O
red	O
skipper	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
also	O
reveal	O
	
admirer	O
from	O
he	O
time	O
loan	O
Anfield	PERSON
but	O
Wardle	PERSON
add	O
there	O
be	O
bid	O
for	O
Nicolas	PERSON
Anelka	PERSON
	
one	NUMBER
have	O
come	O
	
and	O
say	O
would	O
like	O
buy	O
Nicolas	PERSON
Anelka	PERSON
	
	
bid	O
come	O
for	O
Nicolas	PERSON
Anelka	PERSON
will	O
speak	O
the	O
board	O
and	O
then	O
speak	O
Kevin	PERSON
Keegan	PERSON
	
there	O
be	O
bid	O
and	O
be	O
bid	O
substance	O
and	O
worth	O
take	O
then	O
between	O
	
	
decide	O
	
still	O
owe	O
some	O
money	O
Nicolas	PERSON
which	O
have	O
clear	O
out	Sports
	
would	O
have	O
	
above	O
that	O
Wardle	PERSON
do	O
stress	O
that	O
the	O
club	O
be	O
not	O
invite	O
any	O
offer	O
for	O
England	LOCATION
winger	O
Shaun	PERSON
Wright	PERSON
Phillips	PERSON
	
add	O
	
	
intention	O
sell	O
Shaun	PERSON
Wright	PERSON
Phillips	PERSON
	
someone	O
come	O
with	O
silly	O
bid	O
	
have	O
discuss	O
	
	
but	O
	
not	O
put	O
he	O
the	O
shelf	O
sell	O
	
the	O
heart	O
and	O
soul	O
this	O
club	O
and	O
have	O
he	O
heart	O
and	O
sole	O
this	O
club	O
and	O
would	O
very	O
upset	O
	
put	O
he	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
	
be	O
academy	O
kid	O
here	O
	
just	O
sign	O
new	O
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
deal	O
don	O
think	O
	
	
that	O
unless	O
want	O
play	O
for	O
Manchester	LOCATION
City	O
football	O
Club	O
City	O
recently	DATE
announce	O
debt	O
#	O
m	O
but	O
Wardle	PERSON
confirm	O
they	O
would	O
try	O
and	O
find	O
fund	O
bring	O
player	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
	
say	O
like	O
Kevin	PERSON
	
like	O
see	O
some	O
player	O
come	O
	
	
	
get	O
see	O
what	O
can	O
	
whether	O
	
	
	
Bosman	PERSON
not	O
	
will	O
try	O
	
creative	O
generate	O
some	O
fund	O
but	O
maybe	O
have	O
start	O
look	O
club	O
like	O
Everton	ORGANIZATION
and	O
Bolton	PERSON
see	O
how	O
they	O
have	O
be	O
deal	O
the	O
transfer	O
market	O
and	O
	
similar	O
type	O
thing	O
Ferguson	PERSON
rue	O
failure	O
cut	O
gap	O
Boss	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
be	O
left	O
rue	O
Manchester	LOCATION
United	O
failure	O
close	O
the	O
gap	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Everton	ORGANIZATION
and	O
arsenal	O
after	O
he	O
side	O
	
	
draw	O
with	O
Fulham	PERSON
premiership	O
leader	O
Chelsea	PERSON
and	O
the	O
gunner	O
endure	O
	
	
stalemate	O
Sunday	DATE
give	O
United	O
the	O
chance	O
make	O
some	O
ground	O
the	O
league	O
but	O
Ferguson	PERSON
say	O
	
think	O
what	O
make	O
	
bad	O
that	O
both	O
we	O
rival	O
drop	O
point	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
	
be	O
great	O
opportunity	O
and	O
haven	O
deliver	O
United	O
go	O
ahead	O
through	O
Alan	PERSON
Smith	PERSON
the	O
	
rd	O
minute	DURATION
before	O
Bouba	PERSON
Diop	PERSON
superb	O
	
yard	O
strike	O
cancel	O
out	Sports
the	O
visitor	O
lead	O
the	O
	
th	O
minute	DURATION
Ferguson	PERSON
describe	O
the	O
result	O
	
absolute	O
giveaway	O
after	O
United	O
have	O
earlier	O
miss	O
host	O
opportunity	O
finish	O
off	O
the	O
encounter	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
good	O
performance	O
some	O
the	O
football	O
be	O
fantastic	O
but	O
just	O
didn	O
finish	O
they	O
off	O
	
fairness	O
	
	
fantastic	O
strike	O
from	O
the	O
Fulham	PERSON
player	O
the	O
result	O
leaf	O
Ferguson	PERSON
side	O
fourth	ORDINAL
the	O
league	O
	
point	O
four	NUMBER
point	O
behind	O
arsenal	O
and	O
further	O
five	NUMBER
back	O
from	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Everton	ORGANIZATION
Weir	PERSON
cool	O
Euro	O
hope	O
Everton	ORGANIZATION
defender	O
David	PERSON
Weir	PERSON
have	O
play	O
down	O
talk	O
european	O
football	O
despite	O
he	O
team	O
lie	O
second	ORDINAL
place	O
the	O
premiership	O
after	O
beat	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
Weir	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
radio	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
	
don	O
want	O
rest	O
we	O
laurel	O
and	O
say	O
have	O
achieve	O
anything	O
yet	O
	
think	O
you	O
start	O
take	O
you	O
eye	O
off	O
the	O
ball	O
you	O
make	O
statement	O
and	O
look	O
too	O
far	O
into	O
the	O
future	DATE
	
you	O
start	O
make	O
prediction	O
you	O
soon	O
fall	DATE
back	O
into	O
trouble	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
matter	O
the	O
next	O
game	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
look	O
after	O
each	O
other	O
and	O
hard	O
work	O
go	O
long	Sports
way	O
this	O
league	O
	
have	O
definitely	O
show	O
that	O
	
also	O
injury	O
and	O
suspension	O
haven	O
cost	O
too	O
badly	O
and	O
have	O
lot	O
self	O
belief	O
around	O
the	O
place	O
Spain	LOCATION
coach	O
face	O
racism	O
inquiry	O
Spain	LOCATION
football	O
Federation	O
have	O
initiate	O
disciplinary	O
action	O
against	O
national	O
coach	O
Luis	PERSON
Aragones	PERSON
over	O
racist	O
comment	O
about	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
	
find	O
guilty	O
Aragones	PERSON
could	O
lose	O
he	O
job	O
face	O
fine	O
about	O
#	O
	
	
	
the	O
federation	O
have	O
initially	O
decline	O
take	O
action	O
against	O
Aragones	PERSON
after	O
comment	O
make	O
during	O
national	O
team	O
training	O
session	O
October	DATE
but	O
its	O
president	O
Angel	PERSON
Maria	PERSON
Villar	PERSON
change	O
he	O
mind	O
after	O
request	O
Spain	LOCATION
anti	O
violence	O
commission	O
Aragones	PERSON
insist	O
the	O
comment	O
make	O
Henry	PERSON
arsenal	O
club	O
mate	O
Jose	PERSON
Antonio	PERSON
Reyes	PERSON
be	O
mean	O
motivate	O
the	O
player	O
and	O
be	O
not	O
intend	O
	
offensive	O
	
	
never	O
intend	O
offend	O
anyone	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
have	O
very	O
easy	O
conscience	O
	
say	O
the	O
time	O
	
	
oblige	O
motivate	O
player	O
get	O
the	O
best	O
result	O
	
part	O
that	O
job	O
use	O
colloquial	O
language	O
with	O
which	O
can	O
all	O
understand	O
each	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
framework	O
the	O
football	O
world	O
	
England	LOCATION
player	O
make	O
point	O
wear	O
anti	O
racism	O
	
shirt	O
when	O
training	O
before	O
they	O
friendly	O
against	O
Spain	LOCATION
Madrid	LOCATION
last	O
month	DURATION
but	O
the	O
storm	O
increase	O
follow	O
racist	O
chant	O
spanish	O
fan	O
England	LOCATION
black	PERSON
player	O
during	O
the	O
game	O
which	O
Spain	LOCATION
win	O
	
	
Spain	LOCATION
minister	O
sport	O
Jaime	PERSON
Lissavetzky	PERSON
be	O
quick	O
give	O
he	O
backing	O
the	O
Federation	O
decision	O
	
everyone	O
who	O
have	O
public	O
function	O
have	O
consider	O
they	O
declaration	O
and	O
make	O
sure	O
they	O
not	O
give	O
negative	O
image	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
go	O
have	O
zero	NUMBER
tolerance	O
question	O
racism	O
Spain	LOCATION
coach	O
face	O
racism	O
inquiry	O
Spain	LOCATION
football	O
Federation	O
have	O
initiate	O
disciplinary	O
action	O
against	O
national	O
coach	O
Luis	PERSON
Aragones	PERSON
over	O
racist	O
comment	O
about	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
	
find	O
guilty	O
Aragones	PERSON
could	O
lose	O
he	O
job	O
face	O
fine	O
about	O
#	O
	
	
	
the	O
federation	O
have	O
initially	O
decline	O
take	O
action	O
against	O
Aragones	PERSON
after	O
comment	O
make	O
during	O
national	O
team	O
training	O
session	O
October	DATE
but	O
its	O
president	O
Angel	PERSON
Maria	PERSON
Villar	PERSON
change	O
he	O
mind	O
after	O
request	O
Spain	LOCATION
anti	O
violence	O
commission	O
Aragones	PERSON
insist	O
the	O
comment	O
make	O
Henry	PERSON
arsenal	O
club	O
mate	O
Jose	PERSON
Antonio	PERSON
Reyes	PERSON
be	O
mean	O
motivate	O
the	O
player	O
and	O
be	O
not	O
intend	O
	
offensive	O
	
	
never	O
intend	O
offend	O
anyone	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
reason	O
have	O
very	O
easy	O
conscience	O
	
say	O
the	O
time	O
	
	
oblige	O
motivate	O
player	O
get	O
the	O
best	O
result	O
	
part	O
that	O
job	O
use	O
colloquial	O
language	O
with	O
which	O
can	O
all	O
understand	O
each	O
other	O
within	O
the	O
framework	O
the	O
football	O
world	O
	
England	LOCATION
player	O
make	O
point	O
wear	O
anti	O
racism	O
	
shirt	O
when	O
training	O
before	O
they	O
friendly	O
against	O
Spain	LOCATION
Madrid	LOCATION
last	O
month	DURATION
but	O
the	O
storm	O
increase	O
follow	O
racist	O
chant	O
spanish	O
fan	O
England	LOCATION
black	PERSON
player	O
during	O
the	O
game	O
which	O
Spain	LOCATION
win	O
	
	
Spain	LOCATION
minister	O
sport	O
Jaime	PERSON
Lissavetzky	PERSON
be	O
quick	O
give	O
he	O
backing	O
the	O
Federation	O
decision	O
	
everyone	O
who	O
have	O
public	O
function	O
have	O
consider	O
they	O
declaration	O
and	O
make	O
sure	O
they	O
not	O
give	O
negative	O
image	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
go	O
have	O
zero	NUMBER
tolerance	O
question	O
racism	O
Benitez	PERSON
deflect	O
blame	O
from	O
Dudek	PERSON
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
manager	O
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
have	O
refuse	O
point	O
the	O
finger	O
blame	O
goalkeeper	O
Jerzy	PERSON
Dudek	PERSON
after	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
claim	O
draw	O
Anfield	PERSON
Dudek	PERSON
fumble	O
cross	O
before	O
Lomana	PERSON
LuaLua	PERSON
head	O
home	O
injury	O
time	O
equaliser	O
levelling	O
after	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
put	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
ahead	O
Benitez	PERSON
say	O
	
be	O
difficult	O
for	O
Jerzy	PERSON
	
be	O
unlucky	O
moment	O
	
be	O
expect	O
cross	O
from	O
Matthew	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
and	O
end	O
like	O
shot	O
	
don	O
blame	O
he	O
for	O
what	O
happen	O
Benitez	PERSON
admit	O
be	O
costly	O
loss	O
two	NUMBER
point	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
who	O
follow	O
they	O
derby	O
defeat	O
against	O
Everton	ORGANIZATION
with	O
disappointing	O
draw	O
	
say	O
	
have	O
many	O
opportunity	O
but	O
didn	O
score	NUMBER
and	O
the	O
end	O
	
	
lead	O
be	O
not	O
enough	O
	
you	O
don	O
have	O
any	O
chance	O
you	O
have	O
think	O
other	O
thing	O
but	O
when	O
you	O
be	O
create	O
many	O
chance	O
	
be	O
there	O
nothing	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
the	O
player	O
	
be	O
pity	O
	
lose	O
two	NUMBER
point	O
but	O
have	O
one	NUMBER
more	O
point	O
the	O
table	O
now	DATE
have	O
another	O
difficult	O
game	O
against	O
Newcastle	PERSON
and	O
have	O
recover	O
quickly	O
from	O
that	O
Bellamy	PERSON
fine	O
after	O
row	O
Newcastle	PERSON
have	O
fine	O
they	O
Welsh	O
striker	O
Craig	PERSON
Bellamy	PERSON
two	NUMBER
week	DURATION
wages	O
about	O
#	O
	
	
	
follow	O
he	O
row	O
with	O
manager	O
Graeme	PERSON
Souness	PERSON
but	O
Bellamy	PERSON
	
have	O
not	O
be	O
put	O
the	O
transfer	O
list	O
although	O
do	O
not	O
train	O
with	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
team	O
Tuesday	DATE
Magpies	O
chairman	O
Freddy	PERSON
Shepherd	O
tell	O
the	O
Newcastle	PERSON
even	O
Chronicle	O
	
not	O
about	O
money	O
	
about	O
player	O
think	O
	
bigger	O
than	O
this	O
club	O
	
individual	O
	
	
the	O
chairman	O
the	O
manager	O
	
player	O
Souness	PERSON
drop	O
Bellamy	PERSON
for	O
Sunday	DATE
game	O
against	O
arsenal	O
claim	O
the	O
welshman	O
have	O
feign	O
injury	O
after	O
be	O
ask	O
play	O
out	Sports
position	O
	
when	O
hear	O
what	O
the	O
manager	O
be	O
say	O
be	O
shock	O
Bellamy	PERSON
say	O
	
thought	O
not	O
only	O
have	O
go	O
behind	O
back	O
	
lie	O
	
say	O
response	O
Souness	PERSON
remark	O
and	O
the	O
Wales	LOCATION
international	O
refuse	O
apologise	O
	
win	O
apologise	O
because	O
have	O
do	O
nothing	O
wrong	O
	
tell	O
the	O
even	O
Chronicle	O
	
there	O
	
doubt	O
about	O
	
	
out	Sports
here	O
the	O
difficult	O
relationship	O
between	O
Souness	PERSON
and	O
Bellamy	PERSON
boil	O
over	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
and	O
have	O
lead	O
	
war	O
word	O
the	O
media	O
Bellamy	PERSON
claim	O
that	O
Souness	PERSON
have	O
lie	O
about	O
the	O
background	O
the	O
bust	O
be	O
strongly	O
deny	O
Shepherd	O
who	O
accuse	O
the	O
striker	O
	
cheating	O
the	O
club	O
	
wish	O
put	O
the	O
record	O
straight	O
regard	O
the	O
Bellamy	PERSON
situation	O
say	O
Shepherd	O
	
Craig	PERSON
walk	O
off	O
the	O
training	O
ground	O
say	O
he	O
hamstring	O
be	O
tight	O
	
Friday	DATE
but	O
what	O
fail	O
reveal	O
be	O
that	O
have	O
tell	O
other	O
member	O
the	O
squad	O
before	O
training	O
that	O
intend	O
feign	O
injury	O
	
when	O
Graeme	PERSON
discover	O
this	O
immediately	O
order	O
Bellamy	PERSON
attend	O
meeting	O
	
office	O
	
that	O
meeting	O
Bellamy	PERSON
admit	O
Graeme	PERSON
and	O
that	O
have	O
tell	O
the	O
player	O
that	O
be	O
go	O
	
fake	O
injury	O
training	O
and	O
walk	O
off	O
	
also	O
agree	O
that	O
meeting	O
apologise	O
he	O
team	O
mate	O
for	O
he	O
behaviour	O
	
didn	O
	
this	O
which	O
result	O
the	O
action	O
take	O
the	O
manager	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
which	O
fully	O
support	O
	
	
book	O
this	O
cheating	O
the	O
club	O
the	O
supporter	O
the	O
manager	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
team	O
mate	O
	
	
pay	O
extremely	O
well	O
and	O
consider	O
he	O
behaviour	O
	
totally	O
unacceptable	O
and	O
totally	O
unprofessional	O
Bellamy	PERSON
latest	O
outburst	O
would	O
appear	O
make	O
he	O
chance	O
	
first	ORDINAL
team	O
recall	O
remote	O
but	O
even	O
before	O
Newcastle	PERSON
say	O
the	O
player	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
Bellamy	PERSON
insist	O
have	O
intention	O
hand	O
	
transfer	O
request	O
	
don	O
want	O
the	O
fan	O
think	O
for	O
one	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
that	O
wouldn	O
play	O
for	O
this	O
club	O
	
say	O
	
	
play	O
anywhere	O
for	O
this	O
club	O
even	O
goal	O
	
	
	
very	O
difficult	O
situation	O
for	O
	
the	O
moment	O
but	O
	
never	O
ask	O
leave	O
this	O
club	O
	
this	O
club	O
means	O
much	O
	
	
couldn	O
	
because	O
know	O
couldn	O
come	O
back	O
here	O
and	O
play	O
against	O
Newcastle	PERSON
	
would	O
hurt	O
too	O
much	O
McClaren	PERSON
eye	O
Uefa	O
Cup	O
top	O
spot	O
Steve	PERSON
McClaren	PERSON
want	O
he	O
Middlesbrough	ORGANIZATION
team	O
win	O
they	O
Uefa	O
Cup	O
group	O
beat	O
partizan	O
Belgrade	LOCATION
Boro	PERSON
have	O
already	O
qualify	O
for	O
the	O
knockout	O
stage	O
alongside	O
partizan	O
and	O
Villareal	PERSON
the	O
expense	O
Lazio	PERSON
but	O
boss	O
McClaren	PERSON
look	O
for	O
victory	O
which	O
would	O
mean	O
they	O
avoid	O
team	O
that	O
have	O
play	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
Friday	DATE
third	ORDINAL
round	O
draw	O
	
need	O
win	O
finish	O
top	O
fantastic	O
but	O
	
go	O
	
tough	O
one	NUMBER
McClaren	PERSON
say	O
	
when	O
the	O
draw	O
be	O
make	O
thought	O
be	O
the	O
toughest	O
group	O
they	O
all	O
and	O
	
have	O
prove	O
	
Lazio	PERSON
be	O
favourite	O
Villarreal	PERSON
have	O
be	O
semi	O
finalist	O
and	O
partizan	O
have	O
fantastic	O
experience	O
Europe	LOCATION
	
the	O
please	O
thing	O
	
do	O
the	O
business	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
two	NUMBER
game	O
	
win	O
those	O
two	NUMBER
have	O
put	O
	
great	O
position	O
and	O
have	O
be	O
fantastic	O
experience	O
play	O
these	O
team	O
Spurs	O
sign	O
Iceland	LOCATION
U	O
star	O
Tottenham	PERSON
be	O
prime	O
snap	O
Iceland	LOCATION
under	O
	
international	O
Emil	PERSON
hallfredsson	O
after	O
impressed	O
trial	O
White	PERSON
Hart	PERSON
Lane	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
midfielder	O
who	O
play	O
for	O
Hafnarfjordur	O
also	O
star	O
the	O
Uefa	O
Cup	O
match	O
against	O
scottish	O
side	O
Dunfermline	PERSON
earlier	O
this	O
season	O
Spurs	O
have	O
agree	O
fee	O
for	O
the	O
player	O
who	O
have	O
yet	O
agree	O
personal	O
term	O
	
have	O
offer	O
from	O
two	NUMBER
other	O
club	O
but	O
decide	O
come	O
Tottenham	PERSON
say	O
Spurs	O
sport	O
director	O
Frank	PERSON
Arnesen	PERSON
	
	
left	O
side	O
player	O
position	O
have	O
be	O
look	O
and	O
show	O
much	O
talent	O
he	O
time	O
here	O
that	O
decide	O
take	O
he	O
	
	
down	O
the	O
road	O
bring	O
talent	O
good	O
prospects	O
and	O
give	O
they	O
place	O
Tottenham	PERSON
where	O
they	O
can	O
improve	O
McLeish	PERSON
ready	O
for	O
criticism	O
Rangers	O
manager	O
Alex	PERSON
McLeish	PERSON
accept	O
	
go	O
	
criticise	O
after	O
they	O
disastrous	O
Uefa	O
Cup	O
exit	O
the	O
hand	O
Auxerre	PERSON
Ibrox	PERSON
Wednesday	DATE
McLeish	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
radio	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
	
be	O
pole	O
position	O
get	O
through	O
the	O
next	O
stage	O
but	O
blow	O
	
absolutely	O
blow	O
	
	
there	O
	
use	O
bury	O
you	O
head	O
the	O
sand	O
know	O
be	O
go	O
get	O
lot	O
criticism	O
	
have	O
take	O
	
have	O
do	O
the	O
past	DATE
and	O
must	O
now	DATE
bounce	O
back	O
McLeish	PERSON
admit	O
he	O
team	O
defend	O
be	O
amateurish	O
after	O
watch	O
they	O
lose	O
	
	
Guy	O
Roux	PERSON
french	O
side	O
	
	
	
very	O
disappointed	O
because	O
didn	O
give	O
ourselves	O
chance	O
lose	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
goal	O
from	O
we	O
own	O
corner	O
	
be	O
amateur	O
	
add	O
	
the	O
early	O
goal	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
half	O
give	O
	
mountain	O
climb	O
and	O
never	O
create	O
the	O
same	O
kind	O
chance	O
	
do	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
half	O
	
	
difficult	O
take	O
positive	O
from	O
the	O
game	O
	
	
let	O
the	O
fan	O
down	O
	
Leary	PERSON
agree	O
new	O
Villa	PERSON
contract	O
Aston	PERSON
Villa	PERSON
boss	O
David	PERSON
	
Leary	PERSON
sign	O
three	NUMBER
and	O
	
half	O
year	DURATION
contract	O
extension	O
Thursday	DATE
secure	O
he	O
future	DATE
the	O
club	O
until	O
summer	DATE
	
	
	
	
Leary	PERSON
future	DATE
be	O
question	O
but	O
Villa	PERSON
chairman	O
Doug	PERSON
Ellis	PERSON
say	O
be	O
happy	O
secure	O
the	O
deal	O
	
David	PERSON
record	O
since	O
he	O
arrival	O
	
	
	
excellent	O
and	O
share	O
the	O
board	O
amibition	O
take	O
this	O
club	O
forward	O
	
tell	O
Villa	PERSON
website	O
	
for	O
this	O
reason	O
be	O
important	O
get	O
this	O
right	O
	
Leary	PERSON
put	O
pen	O
paper	O
after	O
deal	O
be	O
sort	O
for	O
he	O
right	O
hand	O
man	O
Roy	PERSON
Aitken	PERSON
and	O
Steve	PERSON
McGregor	PERSON
	
be	O
important	O
	
Roy	PERSON
and	O
Steve	PERSON
integral	O
part	O
	
team	O
should	O
stay	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
	
Leary	PERSON
say	O
Thursday	DATE
ahead	O
signing	O
he	O
new	O
deal	O
	
someone	O
have	O
try	O
and	O
put	O
Aston	PERSON
Villa	PERSON
back	O
where	O
they	O
should	O
belong	O
and	O
	
	
for	O
the	O
challenge	O
earlier	O
December	DATE
there	O
be	O
rumour	O
	
Leary	PERSON
would	O
quit	O
	
not	O
offer	O
new	O
deal	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
season	O
but	O
deny	O
that	O
say	O
be	O
happy	O
take	O
the	O
challenge	O
improve	O
Villa	PERSON
fortune	O
the	O
long	Sports
term	O
	
want	O
make	O
sure	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
five	NUMBER
year	DURATION
would	O
have	O
be	O
charge	O
that	O
Villa	PERSON
be	O
achieve	O
top	O
six	NUMBER
finish	O
the	O
premiership	O
	
regular	O
basis	O
say	O
	
Leary	PERSON
who	O
take	O
over	O
Villa	PERSON
Park	O
May	DATE
	
	
	
but	O
achieve	O
that	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
next	O
step	O
forward	O
	
need	O
bring	O
quality	O
player	O
	
would	O
like	O
couple	O
next	O
month	DURATION
	
all	O
possible	O
set	O
	
the	O
way	O
meanwhile	O
	
Leary	PERSON
have	O
rap	O
skipper	O
olof	O
Mellberg	PERSON
for	O
he	O
comment	O
before	O
Sunday	DATE
derby	O
with	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Mellberg	PERSON
speak	O
he	O
dislike	O
Villa	PERSON
rival	O
ahead	O
the	O
match	O
which	O
Steve	PERSON
Bruce	PERSON
side	O
win	O
	
	
	
	
have	O
more	O
than	O
quiet	O
word	O
with	O
olof	O
	
	
be	O
say	O
within	O
the	O
whole	O
group	O
not	O
	
one	NUMBER
	
one	NUMBER
	
tell	O
Villa	PERSON
website	O
	
you	O
shouldn	O
leave	O
yourself	O
open	O
	
shot	O
down	O
you	O
shouldn	O
give	O
people	O
the	O
chance	O
take	O
cheap	O
shot	O
you	O
and	O
set	O
himself	O
for	O
that	O
gronkjaer	O
agree	O
switch	O
Madrid	LOCATION
jesper	O
gronkjaer	O
have	O
agree	O
move	O
Atletico	ORGANIZATION
Madrid	LOCATION
from	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
City	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
winger	O
spend	O
just	O
five	NUMBER
month	DURATION
	
Andrews	PERSON
follow	O
#	O
	
m	O
move	O
from	O
Chelsea	PERSON
July	DATE
after	O
play	O
for	O
Denmark	LOCATION
Euro	O
	
	
	
	
set	O
move	O
during	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
	
deal	O
rumour	O
	
about	O
#	O
	
m	O
subject	O
	
medical	O
	
will	O
meet	O
with	O
the	O
player	O
representative	O
finalise	O
the	O
contract	O
and	O
decide	O
when	O
will	O
sign	O
say	O
Atletico	ORGANIZATION
sport	O
director	O
Toni	PERSON
Munoz	PERSON
gronkjaer	O
have	O
be	O
target	O
blues	O
fan	O
and	O
be	O
sarcastically	O
applaud	O
when	O
take	O
off	O
against	O
Everton	ORGANIZATION
last	O
month	DURATION
Boss	O
Steve	PERSON
Bruce	PERSON
have	O
say	O
that	O
would	O
happy	O
let	O
the	O
danish	O
international	O
	
the	O
price	O
be	O
right	O
	
add	O
	
	
not	O
go	O
say	O
the	O
decision	O
let	O
he	O
	
down	O
the	O
fan	O
reaction	O
towards	O
he	O
	
	
have	O
have	O
tough	O
time	O
since	O
the	O
summer	DATE
with	O
the	O
loss	O
he	O
mother	O
and	O
finding	O
difficult	O
adjust	O
	
new	O
club	O
and	O
different	O
area	O
	
have	O
be	O
terrific	O
and	O
not	O
miss	O
day	DURATION
training	O
and	O
someone	O
you	O
daughter	O
bring	O
they	O
home	O
you	O
would	O
delighted	O
	
just	O
hasn	O
quite	O
work	O
out	Sports
here	O
for	O
he	O
but	O
	
like	O
get	O
back	O
most	O
what	O
spend	O
Benitez	PERSON
	
launch	O
Morientes	PERSON
bid	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
may	O
launch	O
#	O
m	O
January	DATE
bid	O
for	O
long	Sports
time	O
target	O
Fernando	PERSON
Morientes	PERSON
accord	O
report	O
the	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
striker	O
have	O
be	O
link	O
with	O
move	O
Anfield	PERSON
since	O
the	O
summer	DATE
and	O
currently	DATE
behind	O
Raul	PERSON
Ronaldo	PERSON
and	O
Michael	PERSON
Owen	PERSON
the	O
Bernabeu	PERSON
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
boss	O
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
keen	O
bolster	O
he	O
forward	O
option	O
with	O
Djibril	PERSON
Cisse	PERSON
out	Sports
until	O
next	O
season	O
	
there	O
	
attractive	O
propostition	O
could	O
	
would	O
keen	O
leave	O
admit	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Morientes	PERSON
	
add	O
unfortunately	O
	
not	O
control	O
the	O
situation	O
	
	
under	O
contract	O
real	O
and	O
they	O
will	O
make	O
any	O
decision	O
the	O
fee	O
could	O
put	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
off	O
prospective	O
deal	O
but	O
real	O
be	O
keen	O
net	O
the	O
cash	O
they	O
be	O
report	O
	
prepare	O
massive	O
summer	DATE
bid	O
for	O
Inter	O
Milan	LOCATION
striker	O
Adriano	PERSON
the	O
red	O
be	O
currently	DATE
sixth	ORDINAL
the	O
premiership	O
	
point	O
behind	O
leader	O
Chelsea	PERSON
Robertson	PERSON
out	Sports
retain	O
Euro	O
lure	O
Hearts	O
manager	O
John	PERSON
Robertson	PERSON
hope	O
place	O
the	O
knock	O
out	Sports
stage	O
the	O
Uefa	O
Cup	O
could	O
help	O
keep	O
some	O
he	O
out	Sports
	
contract	O
player	O
the	O
club	O
	
	
could	O
help	O
	
get	O
through	O
and	O
have	O
another	O
european	O
tie	O
may	O
encourage	O
player	O
stay	O
least	O
until	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
season	O
	
say	O
	
	
manage	O
get	O
through	O
show	O
how	O
well	O
the	O
club	O
progress	O
	
they	O
have	O
think	O
whether	O
they	O
be	O
go	O
get	O
other	O
club	O
like	O
that	O
should	O
they	O
decide	O
move	O
	
	
win	O
for	O
Robertson	PERSON
side	O
against	O
ferencvaro	O
would	O
put	O
they	O
through	O
the	O
last	O
	
Basle	LOCATION
fail	O
beat	O
Feyenoord	ORGANIZATION
	
	
very	O
much	O
the	O
player	O
prerogative	O
but	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
	
be	O
play	O
european	O
football	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
three	NUMBER
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
obviously	O
incentive	O
add	O
Robertson	PERSON
	
but	O
want	O
player	O
who	O
want	O
play	O
for	O
the	O
football	O
club	O
who	O
be	O
commit	O
and	O
run	O
Europe	LOCATION
always	O
help	O
little	O
bit	O
with	O
the	O
game	O
be	O
play	O
Murrayfield	PERSON
instead	O
Tynecastle	PERSON
because	O
Uefa	O
regulation	O
Robertson	PERSON
see	O
both	O
positive	O
and	O
negative	O
aspect	O
the	O
change	O
venue	O
	
the	O
pitch	O
not	O
the	O
greatest	O
condition	O
the	O
Heineken	PERSON
Cup	O
game	O
be	O
there	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
and	O
the	O
pitch	O
	
bit	O
threadbare	O
	
say	O
	
	
not	O
ideal	O
but	O
	
the	O
same	O
for	O
both	O
team	O
	
just	O
have	O
	
out	Sports
and	O
there	O
and	O
perform	O
that	O
the	O
most	O
important	O
thing	O
but	O
add	O
	
Tynecastle	PERSON
could	O
have	O
host	O
	
	
	
would	O
have	O
be	O
fantastic	O
but	O
that	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
benefit	O
Murrayfield	PERSON
	
allow	O
	
bring	O
even	O
more	O
we	O
supporter	O
into	O
	
	
there	O
will	O
	
good	O
atmosphere	O
and	O
the	O
Hearts	O
fan	O
have	O
important	O
role	O
play	O
	
need	O
they	O
encouragement	O
need	O
they	O
get	O
right	O
behind	O
the	O
side	O
and	O
make	O
	
good	O
atmosphere	O
possible	O
	
hopefully	O
the	O
player	O
will	O
respond	O
that	O
and	O
know	O
they	O
will	O
because	O
	
	
fantastic	O
european	O
night	TIME
for	O
the	O
club	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
rescue	O
arsenal	O
Sol	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
prove	O
	
unlikely	O
match	O
winner	O
earn	O
arsenal	O
hard	O
fight	O
win	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
the	O
England	LOCATION
defender	O
lash	O
home	O
	
	
yard	O
shot	O
for	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
goal	O
	
month	DURATION
take	O
arsenal	O
back	O
into	O
second	ORDINAL
spot	O
five	NUMBER
point	O
behind	O
Chelsea	PERSON
but	O
before	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
score	NUMBER
the	O
best	O
two	NUMBER
chance	O
the	O
game	O
fall	DATE
Pompey	PERSON
striker	O
Ricardo	PERSON
Fuller	PERSON
	
the	O
first	ORDINAL
half	O
blast	O
wide	O
when	O
clear	O
and	O
he	O
control	O
let	O
he	O
down	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
half	O
when	O
well	O
place	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
get	O
plenty	O
body	O
behind	O
the	O
ball	O
deny	O
arsenal	O
space	O
the	O
early	O
stage	O
but	O
they	O
mark	O
be	O
slack	O
	
corner	O
and	O
Patrick	PERSON
Vieira	PERSON
should	O
have	O
do	O
better	O
when	O
the	O
ball	O
fall	DATE
he	O
	
yard	O
out	Sports
	
mistake	O
Arjan	PERSON
Zeeuw	PERSON
let	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
behind	O
the	O
Pompey	PERSON
defence	O
	
minute	DURATION
but	O
	
bear	O
down	O
goal	O
Linvoy	PERSON
Primus	PERSON
get	O
	
save	O
tackle	O
with	O
just	O
Fuller	PERSON
	
out	Sports
and	O
out	Sports
striker	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
shape	O
make	O
life	O
difficult	O
for	O
arsenal	O
but	O
delightful	O
touch	O
Robin	PERSON
van	O
Persie	PERSON
give	O
Henry	PERSON
sight	O
goal	O
although	O
the	O
angle	O
be	O
too	O
tight	O
for	O
he	O
shot	O
trouble	O
Jamie	PERSON
Ashdown	PERSON
Ashdown	PERSON
cause	O
heart	O
flutter	O
	
minute	DURATION
when	O
miss	O
he	O
punch	O
	
corner	O
and	O
Kolo	PERSON
Toure	PERSON
head	O
just	O
wide	O
and	O
arsenal	O
begin	O
press	O
Van	PERSON
Persie	PERSON
blast	O
over	O
good	O
opportunity	O
after	O
Henry	PERSON
have	O
set	O
he	O
	
Henry	PERSON
take	O
quick	O
return	O
pass	O
from	O
Vieira	PERSON
but	O
Ashdown	PERSON
be	O
out	Sports
quickly	O
block	O
and	O
there	O
be	O
some	O
anxious	O
seconds	DURATION
for	O
Pompey	PERSON
the	O
ball	O
run	O
loose	O
before	O
Matthew	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
clear	O
after	O
play	O
second	ORDINAL
fiddle	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
should	O
have	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
	
minute	DURATION
referee	O
Howard	PERSON
Webb	PERSON
play	O
good	O
advantage	O
allow	O
Steve	PERSON
Stone	O
send	O
Gary	PERSON
	
Neil	PERSON
away	O
but	O
have	O
shrug	O
off	O
Toure	PERSON
the	O
Pompey	PERSON
midfielder	O
plant	O
he	O
shot	O
wide	O
from	O
	
yard	O
	
half	O
time	O
approach	O
Henry	PERSON
tease	O
shot	O
through	O
ruck	O
player	O
and	O
inch	O
wide	O
	
the	O
other	O
end	O
Fuller	PERSON
break	O
clear	O
but	O
fail	O
hit	O
the	O
target	O
Toure	PERSON
close	O
he	O
down	O
Fuller	PERSON
be	O
give	O
the	O
best	O
chance	O
the	O
match	O
far	O
	
minute	DURATION
when	O
Patrik	PERSON
Berger	PERSON
break	O
and	O
slip	O
pass	O
play	O
he	O
clear	O
but	O
poor	O
first	ORDINAL
touch	O
lose	O
he	O
the	O
opportunity	O
and	O
even	O
when	O
check	O
back	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
under	O
Vieira	PERSON
challenge	O
referee	O
Webb	PERSON
be	O
not	O
interested	O
Fuller	PERSON
pay	O
the	O
price	O
when	O
give	O
way	O
	
minute	DURATION
Aiyegbeni	PERSON
Yakubu	PERSON
who	O
return	O
after	O
six	NUMBER
week	DURATION
out	Sports
with	O
knee	O
injury	O
but	O
need	O
alert	O
reflex	O
and	O
safe	O
handle	O
from	O
Ashdown	PERSON
cling	O
	
Van	PERSON
Persie	PERSON
shot	O
Henry	PERSON
sniff	O
for	O
scrap	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
be	O
grow	O
confidence	O
and	O
keeper	O
Manuel	PERSON
Almunia	PERSON
have	O
stand	O
he	O
ground	O
beat	O
away	O
powerful	O
shot	O
from	O
Berger	PERSON
arsenal	O
be	O
struggle	O
find	O
they	O
rhythm	O
but	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
through	O
the	O
unlikely	O
source	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
the	O
England	LOCATION
defender	O
need	O
little	O
invitation	O
Pompey	PERSON
back	O
off	O
stride	O
forward	O
and	O
lash	O
ferocious	O
shot	O
past	DATE
Ashdown	PERSON
arsenal	O
might	O
have	O
stretch	O
they	O
lead	O
two	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
later	O
when	O
Mathieu	PERSON
Flamini	PERSON
escape	O
he	O
marker	O
flash	O
header	O
wide	O
from	O
Henry	PERSON
free	O
kick	O
Almunia	PERSON
go	O
full	O
length	O
grab	O
Berger	PERSON
long	Sports
range	O
shot	O
while	O
Ashdown	PERSON
palm	O
away	O
substitute	O
Dennis	PERSON
Bergkamp	PERSON
shot	O
Ashdown	PERSON
Griffin	PERSON
Zeeuw	PERSON
Primus	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
Stone	O
	
Neil	PERSON
Faye	PERSON
Berkovic	PERSON
	
	
Berger	PERSON
LuaLua	PERSON
Fuller	PERSON
Yakubu	PERSON
	
	
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Hislop	PERSON
Quashie	PERSON
Cisse	PERSON
Almunia	PERSON
Lauren	PERSON
Toure	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
Cole	O
Pires	PERSON
Flamini	PERSON
Vieira	PERSON
Clichy	PERSON
Van	PERSON
Persie	PERSON
Bergkamp	PERSON
	
	
Henry	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Lehmann	PERSON
Fabregas	PERSON
Senderos	PERSON
Hoyte	PERSON
Cole	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
Webb	PERSON
	
Yorkshire	ORGANIZATION
	
red	O
sink	O
	
man	O
Magpies	O
Titus	O
bramble	O
own	O
goal	O
put	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
the	O
comeback	O
trail	O
injury	O
hit	O
Newcastle	PERSON
be	O
well	O
beat	O
Anfield	PERSON
Patrick	PERSON
Kluivert	PERSON
close	O
range	O
finish	O
put	O
Newcastle	PERSON
ahead	O
after	O
	
minute	DURATION
but	O
they	O
be	O
peg	O
back	O
bramble	O
head	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
corner	O
Neil	PERSON
Mellor	PERSON
give	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
the	O
lead	O
before	O
half	O
time	O
from	O
Milan	LOCATION
baro	O
pass	O
before	O
the	O
Czech	MISC
add	O
third	ORDINAL
after	O
round	O
Shay	PERSON
give	O
the	O
hour	DURATION
Newcastle	PERSON
then	O
have	O
Lee	PERSON
Bowyer	PERSON
send	O
off	O
for	O
two	NUMBER
bookable	O
offence	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
bring	O
back	O
Luis	PERSON
Garcia	PERSON
after	O
hamstring	O
injury	O
while	O
Newcastle	PERSON
be	O
force	O
draft	O
Kluivert	PERSON
after	O
Craig	PERSON
Bellamy	PERSON
be	O
late	O
withdrawal	O
with	O
back	O
injury	O
sustained	O
the	O
warm	O
	
and	O
Garcia	PERSON
should	O
have	O
crown	O
he	O
return	O
with	O
goal	O
inside	O
the	O
open	O
minute	DURATION
when	O
take	O
pass	O
from	O
baro	O
but	O
shot	O
wildly	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
from	O
eight	NUMBER
yard	O
Olivier	PERSON
Bernard	PERSON
be	O
only	O
inch	O
away	O
from	O
give	O
Newcastle	PERSON
the	O
lead	O
after	O
	
minute	DURATION
when	O
fire	O
just	O
wide	O
from	O
free	O
kick	O
	
yard	O
out	Sports
but	O
Souness	PERSON
side	O
do	O
ahead	O
	
minute	DURATION
later	O
highly	O
controversial	O
circumstance	O
Kluivert	PERSON
look	O
suspiciously	O
offside	O
when	O
Kieron	PERSON
Dyer	PERSON
set	O
Bowyer	PERSON
free	O
but	O
the	O
dutchman	O
be	O
then	O
perfectly	O
place	O
score	NUMBER
from	O
six	NUMBER
yard	O
the	O
lead	O
last	O
three	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
with	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
back	O
term	O
bramble	O
head	O
Gerrard	PERSON
corner	O
into	O
he	O
own	O
net	O
under	O
pressure	O
from	O
Sami	PERSON
Hyypia	PERSON
and	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
be	O
ahead	O
after	O
	
minute	DURATION
when	O
baro	O
slide	O
perfect	O
pass	O
into	O
Mellor	PERSON
path	O
for	O
the	O
youngster	O
slip	O
slide	O
rule	O
finish	O
into	O
give	O
bottom	O
corner	O
Garcia	PERSON
finish	O
be	O
wayward	O
and	O
be	O
wasteful	O
again	O
first	ORDINAL
half	O
injury	O
time	O
shooting	O
tamely	O
give	O
after	O
good	O
work	O
Xabi	PERSON
Alonso	PERSON
any	O
hope	O
	
Newcastle	PERSON
recovery	O
look	O
	
snuff	O
out	Sports
the	O
hour	DURATION
when	O
brilliant	O
turn	O
and	O
pass	O
Harry	PERSON
Kewell	PERSON
set	O
baro	O
free	O
and	O
round	O
give	O
score	NUMBER
Jermaine	PERSON
Jenas	PERSON
then	O
miss	O
glorious	O
chance	O
throw	O
Newcastle	PERSON
lifeline	O
shooting	O
over	O
from	O
just	O
eight	NUMBER
yard	O
out	Sports
from	O
Shola	PERSON
Ameobi	PERSON
cross	O
then	O
Bowyer	PERSON
who	O
have	O
already	O
be	O
book	O
for	O
foul	O
Alonso	PERSON
be	O
deservedly	O
show	O
the	O
red	O
card	O
referee	O
Graham	PERSON
Poll	O
for	O
wild	O
challenge	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
substitute	O
Florent	PERSON
sinama	O
Pongolle	PERSON
Dudek	PERSON
Finnan	PERSON
Hyypia	PERSON
Carragher	PERSON
Riise	PERSON
Luis	PERSON
Garcia	PERSON
Nunez	PERSON
	
	
Gerrard	PERSON
Alonso	PERSON
Kewell	PERSON
Traore	PERSON
	
	
baro	O
Mellor	PERSON
sinama	O
Pongolle	PERSON
	
	
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Hamann	PERSON
Harrison	PERSON
bramble	O
	
	
Mellor	PERSON
	
baro	O
	
	
give	O
Andrew	PERSON
	
Brien	PERSON
Elliott	PERSON
bramble	O
Bernard	PERSON
Bowyer	PERSON
Dyer	PERSON
ambrose	O
	
	
Jenas	PERSON
Milner	PERSON
	
Zogbia	PERSON
	
	
Kluivert	PERSON
Robert	PERSON
	
	
Ameobi	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Harper	PERSON
Bowyer	PERSON
	
	
	
Bowyer	PERSON
Elliott	PERSON
Bernard	PERSON
Kluivert	PERSON
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
Poll	O
Hertfordshire	LOCATION
	
Strachan	PERSON
turn	O
down	O
Pompey	PERSON
Former	O
Southampton	LOCATION
manager	O
Gordon	PERSON
Strachan	PERSON
have	O
reject	O
the	O
chance	O
become	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
new	O
boss	O
the	O
Scot	PERSON
be	O
Pompey	PERSON
chairman	O
Milan	LOCATION
Mandaric	PERSON
first	ORDINAL
choice	O
replace	O
Harry	PERSON
Redknapp	PERSON
who	O
left	O
Fratton	PERSON
Park	O
for	O
rival	O
Saints	O
earlier	O
December	DATE
	
think	O
	
	
fantastic	O
job	O
for	O
anybody	O
apart	O
from	O
somebody	O
who	O
have	O
just	O
be	O
the	O
Southampton	LOCATION
manager	O
Strachan	PERSON
tell	O
the	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Club	O
director	O
Terry	PERSON
Brady	PERSON
hold	O
initial	O
talk	O
with	O
Strachan	PERSON
Saturday	DATE
the	O
former	O
Scotland	LOCATION
international	O
add	O
that	O
join	O
Southampton	LOCATION
local	O
rival	O
would	O
not	O
	
wise	O
move	O
	
	
get	O
everything	O
go	O
for	O
but	O
	
get	O
too	O
many	O
memory	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
and	O
don	O
want	O
sour	O
those	O
memory	O
	
say	O
	
everything	O
right	O
	
	
	
minute	DURATION
away	O
there	O
be	O
good	O
player	O
there	O
good	O
set	O
	
good	O
atmosphere	O
the	O
ground	O
	
there	O
lot	O
	
but	O
	
not	O
right	O
for	O
somebody	O
who	O
have	O
just	O
be	O
the	O
Southampton	LOCATION
manager	O
since	O
Redknapp	PERSON
departure	O
executive	O
director	O
Velimir	PERSON
Zajec	PERSON
and	O
coach	O
Joe	PERSON
Jordan	PERSON
have	O
oversee	O
first	ORDINAL
team	O
affair	O
the	O
duo	O
have	O
go	O
five	NUMBER
match	O
unbeaten	O
until	O
Sunday	DATE
	
	
defeat	O
home	O
champion	O
arsenal	O
but	O
the	O
club	O
be	O
still	O
	
respectable	O
	
th	O
place	O
the	O
premiership	O
table	O
Strachan	PERSON
left	O
Mary	PERSON
	
February	DATE
after	O
earlier	O
announce	O
he	O
intention	O
take	O
break	O
from	O
the	O
game	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
	
	
	
season	O
he	O
previous	O
managerial	O
experience	O
come	O
Coventry	O
whom	O
lead	O
for	O
five	NUMBER
year	DURATION
from	O
Henry	PERSON
tip	O
for	O
Fifa	O
award	O
Fifa	O
president	O
Sepp	PERSON
Blatter	PERSON
hope	O
arsenal	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
will	O
name	O
World	O
Player	O
the	O
year	DURATION
Monday	DATE
Henry	PERSON
	
the	O
Fifa	O
shortlist	O
with	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
Ronaldinho	LOCATION
and	O
newly	O
crown	O
european	O
footballer	O
the	O
year	DURATION
Milan	LOCATION
Andriy	PERSON
Shevchenko	PERSON
Blatter	PERSON
say	O
Henry	PERSON
for	O
	
the	O
personality	O
the	O
field	O
	
the	O
man	O
who	O
can	O
run	O
and	O
organise	O
the	O
game	O
the	O
winner	O
the	O
accolade	O
will	O
name	O
	
glitter	O
ceremony	O
Zurich	LOCATION
Opera	O
house	O
the	O
three	NUMBER
shortlist	O
candidate	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
award	O
be	O
Mia	PERSON
Hamm	PERSON
the	O
United	O
States	O
Germany	LOCATION
Birgit	PERSON
Prinz	PERSON
and	O
brazilian	O
youngster	O
Marta	PERSON
Hamm	PERSON
who	O
recently	DATE
retire	O
	
look	O
regain	O
the	O
woman	O
award	O
which	O
she	O
lose	O
last	O
year	DURATION
striker	O
Prinz	PERSON
Fifa	O
have	O
change	O
the	O
panel	O
voter	O
for	O
this	O
year	DURATION
award	O
male	O
and	O
female	O
captain	O
every	O
national	O
team	O
will	O
able	O
vote	O
well	O
they	O
coach	O
and	O
fipro	O
the	O
global	O
organisation	O
for	O
professional	O
player	O
Newcastle	PERSON
join	O
Morientes	PERSON
race	O
Newcastle	PERSON
have	O
join	O
the	O
race	O
sign	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
striker	O
Fernando	PERSON
Morientes	PERSON
and	O
scupper	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
bid	O
snap	O
the	O
player	O
accord	O
report	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
be	O
report	O
have	O
bid	O
#	O
	
m	O
for	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
spanish	O
international	O
this	O
week	DURATION
but	O
the	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
Echo	O
newspaper	O
have	O
say	O
Anfield	PERSON
boss	O
rafa	O
Benitez	PERSON
will	O
avoid	O
bidding	O
war	O
and	O
instead	O
turn	O
he	O
attention	O
Nicolas	PERSON
Anelka	PERSON
real	O
be	O
believe	O
still	O
want	O
#	O
m	O
before	O
sell	O
Morientes	PERSON
Monaco	PERSON
be	O
also	O
the	O
race	O
for	O
the	O
player	O
they	O
have	O
loan	O
last	O
season	O
report	O
suggest	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
will	O
lift	O
they	O
offer	O
#	O
m	O
the	O
highest	O
they	O
be	O
willing	O
	
before	O
bow	O
out	Sports
any	O
deal	O
	
Tuesday	DATE
Morientes	PERSON
have	O
say	O
	
like	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
and	O
	
pleased	O
that	O
club	O
they	O
stature	O
want	O
buy	O
	
	
have	O
tell	O
Madrid	LOCATION
that	O
want	O
	
happen	O
	
Madrid	LOCATION
know	O
situation	O
and	O
they	O
know	O
they	O
must	O
something	O
about	O
	
they	O
must	O
sort	O
out	Sports
the	O
situation	O
be	O
sensible	O
	
	
	
position	O
where	O
want	O
play	O
and	O
will	O
have	O
look	O
elsewhere	O
	
that	O
	
Madrid	LOCATION
not	O
want	O
then	O
	
	
the	O
best	O
interest	O
everyone	O
that	O
they	O
be	O
realistic	O
	
	
haven	O
speak	O
rafa	O
Benitez	PERSON
but	O
have	O
always	O
appreciate	O
he	O
work	O
and	O
would	O
like	O
play	O
for	O
he	O
but	O
Benitez	PERSON
could	O
yet	O
turn	O
he	O
attention	O
the	O
younger	O
Anelka	PERSON
should	O
Morientes	PERSON
reluctant	O
pledge	O
he	O
future	DATE
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
Anelka	PERSON
previously	DATE
play	O
Anfield	PERSON
under	O
Gerard	PERSON
Houllier	PERSON
before	O
seal	O
he	O
permanent	O
switch	O
Manchester	LOCATION
City	O
blues	O
slam	O
Blackburn	PERSON
over	O
savage	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
have	O
confirm	O
Blackburn	PERSON
make	O
bid	O
for	O
Robbie	PERSON
savage	O
but	O
manage	O
director	O
Karen	PERSON
Brady	PERSON
have	O
call	O
	
derisory	O
	
rover	O
have	O
reportedly	O
offer	O
#	O
	
	
	
front	O
for	O
the	O
Wales	LOCATION
star	O
	
with	O
the	O
fee	O
rise	O
#	O
	
m	O
but	O
Brady	PERSON
tell	O
the	O
Sun	PERSON
the	O
bid	O
be	O
	
waste	O
fax	O
paper	O
and	O
time	O
	
she	O
add	O
the	O
way	O
thing	O
be	O
go	O
all	O
this	O
could	O
affect	O
the	O
relationship	O
between	O
the	O
club	O
they	O
get	O
into	O
Robbie	PERSON
head	O
but	O
	
not	O
for	O
sale	O
savage	O
future	DATE
Birmingham	LOCATION
have	O
be	O
the	O
source	O
speculation	O
for	O
several	O
week	DURATION
with	O
some	O
fan	O
criticise	O
he	O
performance	O
for	O
the	O
club	O
earlier	O
the	O
season	O
however	O
good	O
display	O
against	O
West	O
Brom	O
and	O
Aston	PERSON
Villa	PERSON
have	O
impressed	O
blues	O
fan	O
	
the	O
crowd	O
give	O
	
massive	O
standing	O
ovation	O
when	O
come	O
off	O
Saturday	DATE
which	O
be	O
nice	O
	
say	O
	
be	O
fantastic	O
even	O
though	O
be	O
criticise	O
	
number	O
they	O
recent	O
week	DURATION
and	O
Saturday	DATE
show	O
how	O
much	O
mean	O
they	O
	
	
not	O
for	O
	
say	O
about	O
transfer	O
rumour	O
	
	
between	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
club	O
	
haven	O
create	O
the	O
speculation	O
myself	O
haven	O
phone	O
every	O
national	O
newspaper	O
say	O
Blackburn	PERSON
be	O
try	O
buy	O
	
	
	
not	O
	
	
Birmingham	LOCATION
manager	O
Steve	PERSON
Bruce	PERSON
insist	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
sell	O
savage	O
	
lot	O
say	O
and	O
write	O
about	O
sav	O
but	O
have	O
be	O
terrific	O
for	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
City	O
the	O
last	O
two	NUMBER
and	O
half	O
year	DURATION
	
say	O
	
the	O
fan	O
love	O
he	O
because	O
epitomise	O
they	O
	
work	O
hard	O
they	O
like	O
people	O
like	O
that	O
and	O
there	O
be	O
not	O
many	O
like	O
he	O
	
and	O
why	O
the	O
hell	O
should	O
sell	O
he	O
someone	O
else	O
	
not	O
interested	O
Gerrard	PERSON
happy	O
Anfield	PERSON
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
captain	O
Steven	PERSON
Gerrard	PERSON
have	O
reiterate	O
he	O
desire	O
stay	O
Anfield	PERSON
and	O
win	O
trophy	O
with	O
the	O
club	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
England	LOCATION
midfielder	O
determine	O
see	O
out	Sports
he	O
contract	O
despite	O
report	O
interest	O
from	O
Chelsea	PERSON
	
say	O
	
	
sign	O
here	O
for	O
this	O
season	O
and	O
another	O
two	NUMBER
there	O
	
situation	O
there	O
	
lot	O
speculation	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
down	O
	
	
	
club	O
captain	O
all	O
want	O
	
help	O
get	O
back	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
again	O
Gerrard	PERSON
look	O
set	O
move	O
Chelsea	PERSON
during	O
the	O
summer	DATE
and	O
speculation	O
	
switch	O
Stamford	LOCATION
Bridge	O
have	O
again	O
arise	O
with	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
approach	O
	
raise	O
doubt	O
about	O
he	O
red	O
future	DATE
when	O
say	O
want	O
the	O
club	O
prove	O
they	O
be	O
title	O
challenger	O
the	O
very	O
near	O
future	DATE
	
might	O
leave	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
boss	O
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
have	O
insist	O
that	O
Gerrard	PERSON
have	O
promise	O
he	O
want	O
stay	O
Anfield	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
say	O
	
say	O
Steven	PERSON
that	O
be	O
sure	O
want	O
stay	O
here	O
and	O
say	O
	
	
	
	
then	O
say	O
he	O
look	O
you	O
want	O
win	O
title	O
you	O
want	O
medal	O
and	O
you	O
want	O
Liverpool	ORGANIZATION
have	O
these	O
thing	O
then	O
	
go	O
need	O
you	O
help	O
	
	
really	O
think	O
want	O
stay	O
now	DATE
what	O
must	O
	
make	O
the	O
squad	O
stronger	O
for	O
he	O
meanwhile	O
Gerrard	PERSON
have	O
urge	O
the	O
Anfield	PERSON
board	O
sign	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
striker	O
Fernando	PERSON
Morientes	PERSON
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
Morientes	PERSON
	
have	O
already	O
express	O
willingness	O
come	O
England	LOCATION
Gerrard	PERSON
add	O
	
	
great	O
player	O
	
score	NUMBER
goal	O
the	O
league	O
cup	O
competition	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
Champions	O
League	O
	
don	O
think	O
	
	
able	O
play	O
for	O
	
Europe	LOCATION
this	O
season	O
but	O
	
be	O
able	O
get	O
hold	O
he	O
	
	
get	O
ourselves	O
great	O
player	O
	
	
	
have	O
spanish	O
coach	O
spanish	O
manager	O
and	O
have	O
get	O
three	NUMBER
four	NUMBER
spanish	O
player	O
here	O
now	DATE
they	O
help	O
he	O
settle	O
	
	
Rafael	PERSON
Benitez	PERSON
know	O
what	O
want	O
and	O
know	O
how	O
strengthen	O
the	O
squad	O
	
get	O
and	O
the	O
right	O
player	O
become	O
available	O
the	O
right	O
price	O
	
sure	O
will	O
strengthen	O
	
would	O
certainly	O
nice	O
see	O
few	O
new	O
face	O
January	DATE
freshen	O
thing	O
Beckham	PERSON
rule	O
out	Sports
management	O
move	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
midfielder	O
David	PERSON
Beckham	PERSON
have	O
plan	O
become	O
manager	O
when	O
he	O
play	O
career	O
over	O
	
	
not	O
interested	O
be	O
coach	O
but	O
would	O
like	O
have	O
football	O
school	O
the	O
England	LOCATION
captain	O
say	O
television	O
station	O
Canal	O
plus	O
	
have	O
want	O
	
that	O
since	O
go	O
the	O
Bobby	PERSON
Charlton	PERSON
school	O
	
	
go	O
open	O
one	NUMBER
London	LOCATION
and	O
one	NUMBER
	
	
	
second	ORDINAL
passion	O
charity	O
work	O
	
	
ambassador	O
for	O
Unicef	ORGANIZATION
and	O
give	O
great	O
pride	O
but	O
Beckham	PERSON
reveal	O
that	O
he	O
immediate	O
priority	O
be	O
win	O
the	O
spanish	O
league	O
title	O
with	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
real	O
slip	O
	
point	O
behind	O
leader	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
with	O
	
	
defeat	O
the	O
hand	O
Sevilla	PERSON
Wednesday	DATE
Beckham	PERSON
admit	O
	
	
disappointing	O
and	O
frustrate	O
see	O
the	O
result	O
consider	O
the	O
team	O
have	O
	
would	O
really	O
like	O
win	O
Liga	PERSON
with	O
real	O
Madrid	LOCATION
	
have	O
be	O
here	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
and	O
still	O
have	O
not	O
do	O
	
	
wide	O
range	O
interview	O
Beckham	PERSON
also	O
reveal	O
that	O
he	O
send	O
off	O
against	O
Argentina	LOCATION
and	O
the	O
result	O
media	O
storm	O
have	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
significant	O
moment	O
he	O
career	O
ask	O
for	O
he	O
worst	O
memory	O
say	O
	
send	O
off	O
against	O
Argentina	LOCATION
	
be	O
not	O
for	O
the	O
send	O
off	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
happen	O
afterwards	O
	
be	O
lucky	O
because	O
have	O
manager	O
Sir	O
Alex	PERSON
Ferguson	PERSON
who	O
support	O
and	O
strong	O
family	O
behind	O
but	O
believe	O
that	O
change	O
	
	
believe	O
change	O
for	O
the	O
better	O
Mexicans	MISC
tracking	O
unhappy	O
Juninho	PERSON
mexican	O
outfit	O
Red	O
shark	O
Veracruz	LOCATION
hope	O
sign	O
Juninho	PERSON
the	O
brazilian	O
decide	O
leave	O
celtic	O
frustrated	O
he	O
lack	O
first	ORDINAL
team	O
action	O
they	O
president	O
Gustavo	PERSON
Parente	PERSON
Sanchez	PERSON
say	O
Juninho	PERSON
do	O
not	O
wish	O
remain	O
scottish	O
football	O
anymore	O
	
Agent	O
Brian	PERSON
Hassell	PERSON
insist	O
that	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
brazilian	O
midfielder	O
determine	O
win	O
back	O
he	O
place	O
	
but	O
the	O
manager	O
not	O
go	O
pick	O
he	O
that	O
	
different	O
ball	O
game	O
	
tell	O
the	O
Sun	PERSON
	
that	O
something	O
	
have	O
look	O
	
Juninho	PERSON
deserve	O
respect	O
	
not	O
little	O
kid	O
Hassell	PERSON
warn	O
that	O
Juninho	PERSON
could	O
reconsider	O
he	O
future	DATE
celtic	O
unless	O
	
give	O
run	O
game	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
January	DATE
transfer	O
window	O
Juninho	PERSON
be	O
sign	O
from	O
Middlesbrough	ORGANIZATION
during	O
the	O
summer	DATE
but	O
have	O
fail	O
live	O
	
high	O
expectation	O
and	O
have	O
lose	O
he	O
place	O
	
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Aiden	PERSON
McGeady	PERSON
	
have	O
	
cap	O
for	O
Brazil	LOCATION
and	O
	
the	O
best	O
signing	O
celtic	O
ever	O
make	O
insist	O
Hassell	PERSON
	
want	O
play	O
for	O
Martin	PERSON
	
Neill	PERSON
but	O
do	O
Martin	PERSON
	
Neill	PERSON
want	O
play	O
he	O
Juninho	PERSON
not	O
someone	O
who	O
have	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
celtic	O
rank	O
	
deserve	O
much	O
more	O
respect	O
Sanchez	PERSON
bullish	O
about	O
he	O
hope	O
prise	O
Juninho	PERSON
from	O
the	O
scottish	O
champion	O
although	O
Hassell	PERSON
believe	O
Mexico	LOCATION
would	O
not	O
he	O
prefer	O
destination	O
	
have	O
already	O
speak	O
with	O
Juninho	PERSON
and	O
say	O
	
have	O
firm	O
offer	O
from	O
club	O
Spain	LOCATION
Veracruz	LOCATION
will	O
he	O
destination	O
Sanchez	PERSON
tell	O
he	O
club	O
official	O
website	O
celtic	O
manager	O
	
Neill	PERSON
	
respecter	O
reputation	O
	
the	O
onus	O
	
Juninho	PERSON
force	O
he	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
team	O
	
say	O
	
player	O
get	O
game	O
merit	O
that	O
the	O
way	O
have	O
always	O
be	O
and	O
that	O
certainly	O
the	O
case	O
celtic	O
Park	O
celtic	O
unhappy	O
over	O
Bulgaria	LOCATION
date	O
Martin	PERSON
	
Neill	PERSON
hope	O
block	O
stilian	O
Petrov	PERSON
call	O
	
Bulgaria	LOCATION
during	O
celtic	O
busy	O
festive	O
programme	O
the	O
celtic	O
manager	O
do	O
not	O
view	O
the	O
friendly	O
against	O
Valenciana	PERSON
	
region	O
Spain	LOCATION
	
	
December	DATE
important	O
	
can	O
say	O
be	O
overly	O
pleased	O
the	O
fixture	O
be	O
play	O
just	O
after	O
Christmas	DATE
say	O
	
Neill	PERSON
	
will	O
have	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
bulgarian	O
	
	
	
they	O
prerogative	O
for	O
they	O
arrange	O
fixture	O
and	O
we	O
prerogative	O
how	O
handle	O
	
Bulgaria	LOCATION
game	O
come	O
between	O
celtic	O
Boxing	O
day	DURATION
meeting	O
with	O
Hearts	O
and	O
they	O
January	DATE
fixture	O
against	O
Livingston	PERSON
	
Neill	PERSON
believe	O
the	O
extra	O
game	O
will	O
not	O
help	O
midfielder	O
whose	O
season	O
have	O
already	O
be	O
affect	O
injury	O
	
they	O
have	O
organise	O
game	O
	
rather	O
awkward	O
time	O
	
add	O
	
when	O
be	O
out	Sports
play	O
Barcelona	ORGANIZATION
speak	O
with	O
the	O
bulgarian	O
manager	O
Hristo	PERSON
Stoichkov	PERSON
and	O
mention	O
this	O
game	O
	
	
	
pay	O
he	O
wages	O
be	O
the	O
one	NUMBER
that	O
	
awkward	O
fixture	O
go	O
	
play	O
some	O
stage	O
another	O
should	O
	
we	O
benefit	O
rather	O
than	O
anyone	O
else	O
	
have	O
say	O
this	O
before	O
but	O
Bulgaria	LOCATION
be	O
the	O
one	NUMBER
nation	O
who	O
seem	O
organise	O
lot	O
friendly	O
game	O
Robben	PERSON
and	O
Cole	O
earn	O
Chelsea	PERSON
win	O
Cheslea	PERSON
salvage	O
win	O
against	O
battle	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
side	O
just	O
	
look	O
like	O
the	O
premiership	O
leader	O
would	O
have	O
settle	O
for	O
point	O
Arjen	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
curl	O
	
late	O
deflect	O
left	O
foot	O
shot	O
from	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
Pompey	PERSON
box	O
break	O
the	O
home	O
side	O
brave	O
resistance	O
Chelsea	PERSON
have	O
be	O
continually	O
frustrated	O
but	O
Joe	PERSON
Cole	O
add	O
second	ORDINAL
with	O
	
	
yard	O
shot	O
injury	O
time	O
Nigel	PERSON
Quashie	PERSON
have	O
Pompey	PERSON
best	O
chance	O
when	O
he	O
effort	O
be	O
tip	O
over	O
the	O
Fratton	PERSON
Park	O
crowd	O
be	O
good	O
voice	O
usual	O
and	O
even	O
though	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
more	O
than	O
hold	O
they	O
own	O
Chelsea	PERSON
still	O
manage	O
carve	O
out	Sports
two	NUMBER
early	O
chance	O
striker	O
Didier	PERSON
Drogba	PERSON
snap	O
	
angled	O
shot	O
force	O
home	O
keeper	O
shaka	PERSON
Hislop	PERSON
into	O
smart	O
save	O
while	O
unmarked	O
Frank	PERSON
Lampard	PERSON
have	O
strike	O
block	O
Arjan	PERSON
Zeeuw	PERSON
but	O
Pompey	PERSON
chase	O
harry	O
and	O
unsettled	O
Chelsea	PERSON
side	O
the	O
south	O
coast	O
side	O
start	O
gain	O
the	O
upper	O
hand	O
and	O
almost	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
through	O
Quashie	PERSON
the	O
midfielder	O
strike	O
swerve	O
long	Sports
range	O
shot	O
which	O
keeper	O
Petr	PERSON
Cech	PERSON
tip	O
over	O
full	O
stretch	O
Pompey	PERSON
stretch	O
arsenal	O
the	O
limit	O
recently	DATE
and	O
be	O
provide	O
similarly	O
tough	O
obstacle	O
overcome	O
for	O
Chelsea	PERSON
team	O
struggle	O
exert	O
any	O
pressure	O
Velimir	PERSON
Zajec	PERSON
player	O
stand	O
firm	O
the	O
visitor	O
come	O
out	Sports
lively	O
fashion	O
after	O
the	O
break	O
but	O
just	O
they	O
take	O
stranglehold	O
the	O
match	O
the	O
visitor	O
launch	O
counter	O
attack	O
Drogba	PERSON
spin	O
get	O
sight	O
goal	O
and	O
strike	O
fierce	O
shot	O
which	O
rock	O
keeper	O
Hislop	PERSON
back	O
	
block	O
before	O
Arjan	PERSON
Zeeuw	PERSON
clear	O
the	O
danger	O
the	O
home	O
side	O
be	O
also	O
left	O
breathing	O
sigh	O
relief	O
when	O
Glen	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
header	O
fall	DATE
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
who	O
have	O
he	O
back	O
goal	O
	
crowd	O
Pompey	PERSON
goalmouth	O
the	O
icelandic	O
forward	O
try	O
acrobatically	O
direct	O
the	O
ball	O
into	O
goal	O
but	O
put	O
he	O
effort	O
over	O
but	O
just	O
like	O
against	O
arsenal	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
let	O
	
late	O
goal	O
when	O
Robben	PERSON
shot	O
take	O
deflection	O
off	O
Matthew	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
its	O
way	O
past	DATE
wrong	O
foot	O
Hislop	PERSON
and	O
Cole	O
put	O
bit	O
gloss	O
	
hard	O
fight	O
win	O
when	O
put	O
low	O
shot	O
into	O
the	O
bottom	O
the	O
Pompey	PERSON
net	O
Hislop	PERSON
Griffin	PERSON
Primus	PERSON
Zeeuw	PERSON
Taylor	PERSON
Stone	O
Cisse	PERSON
	
	
Quashie	PERSON
Berkovic	PERSON
	
	
Faye	PERSON
	
Neil	PERSON
Kamara	PERSON
Fuller	PERSON
	
	
Yakubu	PERSON
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Berger	PERSON
Ashdown	PERSON
Kamara	PERSON
Cech	PERSON
Paulo	PERSON
Ferreira	PERSON
Gallas	PERSON
Terry	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
Duff	PERSON
Makelele	PERSON
smertin	O
Cole	O
	
	
Lampard	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
Geremi	PERSON
	
	
Drogba	PERSON
Gudjohnsen	PERSON
	
	
sub	O
not	O
use	O
Cudicini	PERSON
Bridge	O
Paulo	PERSON
Ferreira	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
Lampard	PERSON
Robben	PERSON
	
Cole	O
	
	
	
	
	
	
wiley	O
Staffordshire	LOCATION
	
Newcastle	PERSON
line	O
Babayaro	PERSON
Newcastle	PERSON
manager	O
Graeme	PERSON
Souness	PERSON
close	O
	
signing	O
Chelsea	PERSON
defender	O
Celestine	PERSON
Babayaro	PERSON
when	O
the	O
transfer	O
window	O
reopen	O
Souness	PERSON
bidding	O
bolster	O
he	O
defence	O
and	O
accord	O
report	O
contract	O
negotiation	O
be	O
	
advance	O
stage	O
with	O
the	O
player	O
Babayaro	PERSON
have	O
be	O
the	O
premiership	O
since	O
	
	
when	O
move	O
Chelsea	PERSON
for	O
#	O
	
m	O
from	O
Anderlecht	PERSON
but	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
have	O
be	O
surplus	O
requirement	O
this	O
season	O
Souness	PERSON
would	O
not	O
draw	O
specifics	O
over	O
individual	O
player	O
but	O
say	O
all	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
chairman	O
have	O
work	O
really	O
hard	O
the	O
last	O
couple	O
month	DURATION
try	O
	
deal	O
	
have	O
say	O
from	O
day	DURATION
one	NUMBER
want	O
strengthen	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
be	O
hope	O
	
the	O
come	O
week	DURATION
Mourinho	PERSON
take	O
swipe	O
arsenal	O
Chelsea	PERSON
boss	O
Jose	PERSON
Mourinho	PERSON
have	O
attempt	O
pile	O
the	O
pressure	O
title	O
rival	O
arsenal	O
ahead	O
the	O
gunner	O
face	O
Newcastle	PERSON
Wednesday	DATE
arsenal	O
will	O
play	O
the	O
Magpies	O
day	DURATION
after	O
Chelsea	PERSON
beat	O
Portsmouth	LOCATION
during	O
busy	O
festive	O
programme	O
and	O
Mourinho	PERSON
say	O
they	O
always	O
seem	O
have	O
two	NUMBER
three	NUMBER
day	DURATION
rest	O
which	O
recover	O
perhaps	O
	
something	O
	
with	O
the	O
television	O
schedule	O
	
all	O
player	O
be	O
tired	O
especially	O
John	PERSON
Terry	PERSON
Chelsea	PERSON
boss	O
Jose	PERSON
Mourinho	PERSON
admit	O
he	O
side	O
be	O
lucky	O
win	O
Fratton	PERSON
Park	O
but	O
still	O
unhappy	O
with	O
the	O
amount	O
game	O
such	O
short	O
space	O
time	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
year	DURATION
	
add	O
	
have	O
have	O
play	O
two	NUMBER
match	O
three	NUMBER
day	DURATION
which	O
foreign	O
many	O
	
player	O
and	O
although	O
understand	O
the	O
tradition	O
football	O
here	O
this	O
time	O
year	DURATION
	
not	O
good	O
for	O
you	O
health	O
	
	
	
you	O
can	O
sit	O
back	O
and	O
smoke	O
cigar	O
one	NUMBER
after	O
another	O
and	O
	
good	O
life	O
but	O
	
not	O
actually	O
good	O
for	O
you	O
	
play	O
many	O
game	O
certainly	O
not	O
healthy	O
especially	O
for	O
team	O
who	O
still	O
have	O
european	O
commitment	O
Wenger	PERSON
shock	O
Newcastle	PERSON
dip	O
arsenal	O
manager	O
Arsene	PERSON
Wenger	PERSON
have	O
admit	O
	
	
loss	O
explain	O
why	O
Newcastle	PERSON
be	O
languish	O
the	O
bottom	O
half	O
the	O
table	O
the	O
gunner	O
travel	O
	
James	PERSON
Park	O
Wednesday	DATE
with	O
Newcastle	PERSON
	
th	O
the	O
premiership	O
after	O
trouble	O
season	O
and	O
Wenger	PERSON
say	O
	
the	O
begin	O
the	O
season	O
you	O
would	O
expect	O
they	O
	
fight	O
for	O
the	O
top	O
four	NUMBER
	
don	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
get	O
	
where	O
they	O
be	O
	
look	O
	
from	O
the	O
outside	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
many	O
injury	O
arsenal	O
into	O
the	O
game	O
the	O
back	O
	
	
victory	O
over	O
Fulham	PERSON
Sunday	DATE
and	O
Wenger	PERSON
add	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
prepare	O
for	O
game	O
	
win	O
the	O
previous	O
one	NUMBER
	
will	O
	
Newcastle	PERSON
good	O
shape	O
	
fatigue	O
win	O
play	O
too	O
big	O
part	O
the	O
next	O
few	O
week	DURATION
	
have	O
player	O
come	O
back	O
	
can	O
rotate	O
bit	O
more	O
	
	
not	O
play	O
season	O
with	O
	
player	O
and	O
believe	O
that	O
all	O
we	O
squad	O
deserve	O
chance	O
the	O
team	O
striker	O
Thierry	PERSON
Henry	PERSON
along	O
with	O
Robert	PERSON
Pires	PERSON
score	NUMBER
against	O
Fulham	PERSON
