consist	O
document	O
from	O
the	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
website	O
correspond	O
sport	O
news	O
article	O
five	NUMBER
topical	O
area	O
from	O
	
	
	
	
	
document	O
	
	
term	O
	
	
natural	O
class	O
	
athletics	O
cricket	O
football	O
rugby	O
tennis	O
you	O
make	O
use	O
the	O
dataset	O
please	O
consider	O
cite	O
the	O
publication	O
	
	
Greene	PERSON
and	O
	
Cunningham	PERSON
	
Practical	O
Solutions	O
the	O
Problem	O
diagonal	O
dominance	O
Kernel	PERSON
Document	O
clustering	O
Proc	O
icml	O
	
	
	
all	O
rights	O
include	O
copyright	O
the	O
content	O
the	O
original	O
article	O
be	O
own	O
the	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
contact	O
Derek	PERSON
Greene	PERSON
derek	PERSON
greene	O
ucd	O
	
for	O
further	O
information	O
http	O
	
mlg	O
ucd	O
	
dataset	O
bbc	O
html	O
Claxton	PERSON
hunting	O
first	ORDINAL
major	O
medal	O
british	O
hurdler	O
Sarah	PERSON
Claxton	PERSON
confident	O
she	O
can	O
win	O
she	O
first	ORDINAL
major	O
medal	O
next	O
month	DURATION
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
Madrid	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
have	O
already	O
smash	O
the	O
british	O
record	O
over	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
twice	O
this	O
season	O
set	O
new	O
mark	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
win	O
the	O
aaa	O
title	O
	
	
quite	O
confident	O
say	O
Claxton	PERSON
	
but	O
take	O
each	O
race	O
	
come	O
	
long	Sports
	
keep	O
	
training	O
but	O
not	O
too	O
much	O
think	O
there	O
	
chance	O
	
medal	O
Claxton	PERSON
have	O
win	O
the	O
national	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
title	O
for	O
the	O
past	DATE
three	NUMBER
year	DURATION
but	O
have	O
struggle	O
translate	O
she	O
domestic	O
success	O
the	O
international	O
stage	O
now	DATE
the	O
Scotland	LOCATION
bear	O
athlete	O
own	O
the	O
equal	O
fifth	ORDINAL
fastest	O
time	O
the	O
world	O
this	O
year	DURATION
and	O
last	O
week	DURATION
Birmingham	LOCATION
Grand	O
Prix	O
Claxton	PERSON
left	O
european	O
medal	O
favourite	O
russian	O
Irina	PERSON
Shevchenko	PERSON
trail	O
sixth	ORDINAL
spot	O
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
time	O
Claxton	PERSON
have	O
only	O
be	O
prepare	O
for	O
campaign	O
over	O
the	O
hurdle	O
which	O
could	O
explain	O
she	O
leap	O
form	O
	
previous	O
season	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
also	O
contest	O
the	O
long	Sports
jump	Sports
but	O
since	O
move	O
from	O
Colchester	PERSON
London	LOCATION
she	O
have	O
	
focus	O
she	O
attention	O
Claxton	PERSON
will	O
see	O
she	O
new	O
training	O
regime	O
pay	O
dividend	O
the	O
european	O
indoors	O
which	O
take	O
place	O
	
	
March	DATE
	
Sullivan	PERSON
could	O
run	O
world	O
Sonia	PERSON
	
Sullivan	PERSON
have	O
indicate	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
like	O
participate	O
next	O
month	DURATION
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
	
etienne	O
Athletics	O
Ireland	LOCATION
have	O
hint	O
that	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Cobh	PERSON
runner	O
may	O
include	O
the	O
official	O
line	O
for	O
the	O
event	O
France	LOCATION
	
	
	
March	DATE
provincial	O
team	O
be	O
select	O
after	O
last	O
Saturday	DATE
national	O
Santry	PERSON
and	O
will	O
officially	O
announce	O
this	O
week	DURATION
	
Sullivan	PERSON
	
present	DATE
prepare	O
for	O
the	O
London	LOCATION
marathon	O
	
April	DATE
the	O
participation	O
	
Sullivan	PERSON
currentily	O
training	O
she	O
base	O
Australia	LOCATION
would	O
boost	O
the	O
Ireland	LOCATION
team	O
who	O
win	O
the	O
bronze	O
three	NUMBER
year	DURATION
agio	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
three	NUMBER
Santry	PERSON
last	O
Saturday	DATE
Jolene	PERSON
Byrne	PERSON
Maria	PERSON
McCambridge	PERSON
and	O
fionnualla	O
Britton	PERSON
be	O
automatic	O
selection	O
and	O
will	O
most	O
likely	O
form	O
part	O
the	O
long	Sports
course	O
team	O
	
Sullivan	PERSON
will	O
also	O
take	O
part	O
the	O
Bupa	PERSON
Great	O
Ireland	LOCATION
Run	O
	
April	DATE
Dublin	LOCATION
Greene	PERSON
set	O
sight	O
world	O
title	O
Maurice	PERSON
Greene	PERSON
aim	O
wipe	O
out	Sports
the	O
pain	O
lose	O
he	O
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
title	O
Athens	LOCATION
win	O
fourth	ORDINAL
World	O
Championship	O
crown	O
this	O
summer	DATE
	
have	O
settle	O
for	O
bronze	O
Greece	LOCATION
behind	O
fellow	O
American	MISC
Justin	PERSON
Gatlin	PERSON
and	O
Francis	PERSON
Obikwelu	PERSON
Portugal	LOCATION
	
really	O
hurt	O
look	O
that	O
medal	O
	
be	O
mistake	O
	
lose	O
because	O
the	O
thing	O
do	O
say	O
Greene	PERSON
who	O
race	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Friday	DATE
	
	
never	O
go	O
happen	O
again	O
	
goal	O
	
	
go	O
win	O
the	O
world	O
Greene	PERSON
cross	O
the	O
line	O
just	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
behind	O
Gatlin	PERSON
who	O
win	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
one	NUMBER
the	O
closest	O
and	O
fastest	O
sprint	O
all	O
time	O
but	O
Greene	PERSON
believe	O
lose	O
the	O
race	O
and	O
he	O
title	O
the	O
semi	O
final	O
	
	
semi	O
final	O
race	O
should	O
have	O
win	O
the	O
race	O
but	O
be	O
conserve	O
energy	O
	
that	O
when	O
Francis	PERSON
Obikwelu	PERSON
come	O
and	O
take	O
third	ORDINAL
because	O
didn	O
know	O
be	O
there	O
	
believe	O
that	O
what	O
put	O
	
lane	O
seven	NUMBER
the	O
final	O
and	O
while	O
be	O
lane	O
seven	NUMBER
couldn	O
feel	O
anything	O
the	O
race	O
	
	
just	O
feel	O
like	O
be	O
run	O
all	O
alone	O
	
believe	O
	
be	O
the	O
middle	O
the	O
race	O
would	O
have	O
be	O
able	O
react	O
people	O
that	O
come	O
ahead	O
	
	
Greene	PERSON
be	O
also	O
deny	O
Olympic	MISC
gold	O
the	O
x	O
	
m	O
man	O
relay	O
when	O
could	O
not	O
catch	Sports
Britain	LOCATION
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
the	O
final	O
leg	O
the	O
Kansas	LOCATION
star	O
set	O
	
head	O
	
head	O
with	O
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
again	O
Friday	DATE
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
Grand	O
Prix	O
the	O
pair	O
contest	O
the	O
	
m	O
the	O
distance	O
over	O
which	O
Greene	PERSON
currently	DATE
hold	O
the	O
world	O
record	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
	
then	O
have	O
another	O
indoor	O
meeting	O
France	LOCATION
before	O
resume	O
training	O
for	O
the	O
outdoor	O
season	O
and	O
the	O
task	O
recapture	O
he	O
world	O
title	O
Helsinki	LOCATION
August	DATE
Greene	PERSON
believe	O
Gatlin	PERSON
will	O
again	O
prove	O
the	O
biggest	O
threat	O
he	O
ambition	O
Finland	LOCATION
but	O
also	O
admit	O
face	O
more	O
than	O
one	NUMBER
rival	O
for	O
the	O
world	O
crown	O
	
there	O
always	O
someone	O
else	O
come	O
	
think	O
when	O
be	O
come	O
	
would	O
say	O
there	O
be	O
and	O
Ato	PERSON
Boldon	PERSON
the	O
young	O
crowd	O
Greene	PERSON
say	O
	
now	DATE
you	O
get	O
about	O
five	NUMBER
six	NUMBER
young	O
guy	O
come	O
	
the	O
same	O
time	O
iaaf	O
launch	O
fight	O
against	O
drug	O
the	O
iaaf	O
athletics	O
world	O
govern	O
body	O
have	O
meet	O
anti	O
doping	O
official	O
coach	O
and	O
athlete	O
	
ordinate	O
the	O
fight	O
against	O
drug	O
sport	O
two	NUMBER
task	O
force	O
have	O
be	O
set	O
	
examine	O
doping	O
and	O
nutrition	O
issue	O
	
be	O
also	O
agree	O
that	O
programme	O
	
	
mystify	O
the	O
issue	O
athlete	O
the	O
public	O
and	O
the	O
media	O
be	O
priority	O
	
nothing	O
be	O
decide	O
change	O
thing	O
	
be	O
more	O
have	O
forum	O
the	O
stakeholder	O
allow	O
they	O
express	O
themselves	O
say	O
iaaf	O
spokesman	O
	
get	O
everyone	O
together	O
give	O
	
lot	O
food	O
for	O
thought	O
about	O
	
people	O
attend	O
Sunday	DATE
meeting	O
Monaco	PERSON
include	O
iaaf	O
chief	O
lamine	O
Diack	PERSON
and	O
namibian	O
athlete	O
Frankie	PERSON
frederick	O
now	DATE
member	O
the	O
athlete	O
Commission	O
	
	
very	O
happy	O
see	O
you	O
all	O
member	O
the	O
athletics	O
family	O
respond	O
positively	O
the	O
iaaf	O
call	O
sit	O
together	O
and	O
discuss	O
what	O
more	O
can	O
	
the	O
fight	O
against	O
doping	O
say	O
Diack	PERSON
	
be	O
the	O
lead	O
Federation	O
this	O
field	O
and	O
	
we	O
duty	O
keep	O
we	O
sport	O
clean	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
task	O
force	O
will	O
report	O
back	O
the	O
iaaf	O
Council	O
its	O
April	DATE
meeting	O
Qatar	LOCATION
Dibaba	PERSON
break	O
	
	
m	O
world	O
record	O
Ethiopia	LOCATION
Tirunesh	PERSON
Dibaba	PERSON
set	O
new	O
world	O
record	O
win	O
the	O
woman	O
	
	
	
m	O
the	O
Boston	LOCATION
indoor	O
Games	O
Dibaba	PERSON
win	O
	
minute	DURATION
	
	
seconds	DURATION
erase	O
the	O
previous	O
world	O
indoor	O
mark	O
	
	
	
	
set	O
another	O
ethiopian	O
Berhane	PERSON
Adera	PERSON
Stuttgart	LOCATION
last	O
year	DURATION
but	O
compatriot	O
Kenenisa	PERSON
Bekele	PERSON
record	O
hope	O
be	O
dash	O
when	O
miscount	O
he	O
lap	O
the	O
man	O
	
	
	
m	O
and	O
stage	O
he	O
sprint	O
finish	O
lap	O
too	O
soon	O
Ireland	LOCATION
Alistair	PERSON
Cragg	PERSON
win	O
	
	
	
	
Bekele	PERSON
battle	O
second	ORDINAL
	
	
	
	
	
	
didn	O
want	O
sit	O
back	O
and	O
get	O
out	Sports
kick	O
say	O
Cragg	PERSON
	
	
keep	O
the	O
pace	O
the	O
plan	O
be	O
	
with	O
	
m	O
	
matter	O
what	O
but	O
when	O
Bekele	PERSON
make	O
the	O
mistake	O
that	O
be	O
	
the	O
race	O
be	O
mine	O
Sweden	LOCATION
Carolina	PERSON
Kluft	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
heptathlon	O
champion	O
and	O
Slovenia	LOCATION
Jolanda	PERSON
Ceplak	PERSON
have	O
win	O
performance	O
too	O
Kluft	O
take	O
the	O
long	Sports
jump	Sports
	
	
m	O
while	O
Ceplak	PERSON
easily	O
win	O
the	O
woman	O
	
	
m	O
	
	
	
	
	
Isinbayeva	PERSON
claim	O
new	O
world	O
best	O
Pole	O
vaulter	O
Yelena	PERSON
Isinbayeva	PERSON
break	O
she	O
own	O
indoor	O
world	O
record	O
clearing	O
	
	
metre	O
Lievin	LOCATION
Saturday	DATE
	
be	O
the	O
russian	O
	
th	O
world	O
record	O
she	O
career	O
and	O
come	O
just	O
few	O
day	DURATION
after	O
she	O
clear	O
	
	
m	O
the	O
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
Grand	O
Prix	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
the	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
go	O
	
attempt	O
	
	
m	O
the	O
meeting	O
France	LOCATION
but	O
fail	O
clear	O
that	O
height	O
	
the	O
man	O
	
m	O
former	O
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
champion	O
Maurice	PERSON
Greene	PERSON
could	O
only	O
finish	O
second	ORDINAL
Leonard	PERSON
Scott	PERSON
	
be	O
Greene	PERSON
second	ORDINAL
consecutive	O
defeat	O
the	O
hand	O
he	O
fellow	O
American	MISC
who	O
also	O
win	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
last	O
week	DURATION
	
run	O
race	O
perfectly	O
say	O
Scott	PERSON
who	O
win	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
he	O
best	O
time	O
indoors	O
	
	
happy	O
even	O
	
know	O
that	O
Maurice	PERSON
	
long	Sports
way	O
from	O
be	O
he	O
peak	O
the	O
start	O
the	O
season	O
	
Sullivan	PERSON
commit	O
Dublin	LOCATION
race	O
Sonia	PERSON
	
Sullivan	PERSON
will	O
seek	O
regain	O
she	O
title	O
the	O
Bupa	PERSON
Great	O
Ireland	LOCATION
Run	O
	
April	DATE
Dublin	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
be	O
beat	O
into	O
fourth	ORDINAL
last	O
year	DURATION
event	O
have	O
win	O
	
year	DURATION
earlier	O
	
understand	O
she	O
have	O
solid	O
winter	DATE
training	O
down	O
Australia	LOCATION
after	O
recover	O
from	O
minor	O
injury	O
say	O
race	O
director	O
Matthew	PERSON
Turnbull	PERSON
Mark	PERSON
Carroll	PERSON
irish	O
record	O
holder	O
	
km	O
km	O
and	O
	
km	O
will	O
make	O
he	O
debut	O
the	O
mass	O
participation	O
	
km	O
race	O
Carroll	PERSON
have	O
step	O
he	O
form	O
recent	O
week	DURATION
and	O
late	O
January	DATE
score	NUMBER
impressive	O
	
	
m	O
victory	O
over	O
lead	O
American	MISC
Alan	PERSON
Webb	PERSON
Boston	LOCATION
Carroll	PERSON
will	O
face	O
stiff	O
competition	O
from	O
australian	O
Craig	PERSON
Mottram	PERSON
winner	O
Dublin	LOCATION
for	O
the	O
last	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
Hansen	PERSON
delay	O
return	O
until	O
	
	
british	O
triple	O
jumper	O
Ashia	PERSON
Hansen	PERSON
have	O
rule	O
out	Sports
comeback	O
this	O
year	DURATION
after	O
setback	O
she	O
recovery	O
from	O
bad	O
knee	O
injury	O
accord	O
report	O
Hansen	PERSON
the	O
Commonwealth	O
and	O
european	O
champion	O
have	O
be	O
sideline	O
since	O
the	O
european	O
Cup	O
Poland	LOCATION
June	DATE
	
	
	
be	O
hope	O
she	O
would	O
able	O
return	O
this	O
summer	DATE
but	O
the	O
wound	O
from	O
the	O
injury	O
have	O
be	O
very	O
slow	O
heal	O
she	O
coach	O
Aston	PERSON
Moore	PERSON
tell	O
the	O
Times	O
	
	
not	O
look	O
any	O
sooner	O
than	O
	
	
not	O
	
triple	O
jumper	O
Moore	PERSON
say	O
Hansen	PERSON
may	O
able	O
return	O
sprint	O
and	O
long	Sports
jump	Sports
sooner	O
but	O
there	O
	
short	O
term	O
prospect	O
she	O
be	O
involve	O
again	O
she	O
specialist	O
event	O
	
there	O
be	O
problem	O
with	O
the	O
wound	O
healing	O
and	O
set	O
back	O
she	O
rehabilitation	O
about	O
two	NUMBER
month	DURATION
but	O
that	O
have	O
be	O
solve	O
and	O
can	O
push	O
ahead	O
now	DATE
	
say	O
	
the	O
aim	O
for	O
she	O
get	O
fit	O
	
athlete	O
then	O
will	O
start	O
look	O
sprint	O
and	O
the	O
long	Sports
jump	Sports
	
introduction	O
back	O
the	O
competitive	O
arena	O
Moore	PERSON
say	O
	
confident	O
Hansen	PERSON
can	O
make	O
back	O
top	O
level	O
competition	O
though	O
	
unclear	O
that	O
will	O
	
time	O
for	O
the	O
Commonwealth	O
Games	O
Melbourne	LOCATION
next	O
March	DATE
when	O
she	O
will	O
	
	
	
	
be	O
frustrate	O
time	O
for	O
she	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
faze	O
she	O
determination	O
	
add	O
off	O
colour	O
gardener	O
storm	O
win	O
Britain	LOCATION
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
shake	O
off	O
upset	O
stomach	O
win	O
the	O
	
m	O
Sunday	DATE
Leipzig	LOCATION
International	O
meeting	O
gardener	O
clock	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
equal	O
the	O
meeting	O
record	O
and	O
finish	O
well	O
ahead	O
Germany	LOCATION
Marc	PERSON
Blume	PERSON
who	O
cross	O
the	O
line	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
the	O
world	O
indoor	O
champion	O
say	O
	
get	O
the	O
airport	O
and	O
stomach	O
be	O
upset	O
and	O
be	O
vomit	O
	
almost	O
go	O
home	O
	
feel	O
little	O
better	O
Sunday	DATE
morning	TIME
but	O
decide	O
	
only	O
run	O
the	O
main	O
race	O
then	O
everything	O
go	O
perfectly	O
gardener	O
part	O
the	O
Great	O
Britain	LOCATION
x	O
	
m	O
quartet	O
that	O
win	O
gold	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
will	O
now	DATE
turn	O
he	O
attention	O
next	O
weekend	DATE
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
european	O
indoor	O
trial	O
Sheffield	PERSON
	
give	O
	
still	O
off	O
colour	O
know	O
there	O
plenty	O
more	O
the	O
tank	O
and	O
expect	O
get	O
faster	O
the	O
next	O
few	O
week	DURATION
	
say	O
	
	
just	O
case	O
chip	O
away	O
	
have	O
do	O
previous	O
year	DURATION
and	O
the	O
result	O
will	O
come	O
Scotland	LOCATION
Ian	PERSON
Mackie	PERSON
be	O
also	O
action	O
Leipzig	LOCATION
	
step	O
down	O
from	O
he	O
favour	O
	
m	O
	
	
m	O
finish	O
third	ORDINAL
	
	
	
sec	DURATION
Germany	LOCATION
Alexander	PERSON
Kosenkow	PERSON
win	O
the	O
race	O
	
	
	
sec	DURATION
with	O
dutchman	O
Patrick	PERSON
van	O
balkom	O
second	ORDINAL
	
	
	
sec	DURATION
there	O
be	O
plenty	O
other	O
senior	O
british	O
athlete	O
show	O
they	O
indoor	O
form	O
over	O
the	O
weekend	DATE
promising	O
	
m	O
hurdler	O
clock	O
new	O
record	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
	
meeting	O
Norway	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
reach	O
the	O
mark	O
she	O
heat	O
but	O
have	O
settle	O
for	O
joint	O
first	ORDINAL
place	O
with	O
former	O
aaa	O
champion	O
Diane	PERSON
Allahgreen	PERSON
the	O
final	O
	
who	O
break	O
onto	O
the	O
international	O
scene	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
Games	O
last	O
season	O
set	O
indoor	O
personal	O
best	O
	
	
	
m	O
the	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
	
meeting	O
Ghent	O
that	O
leap	O
	
cm	O
short	O
brazilian	O
winner	O
Jadel	PERSON
Gregorio	PERSON
effort	O
be	O
good	O
enough	O
qualify	O
for	O
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
	
the	O
same	O
meeting	O
finish	O
third	ORDINAL
	
	
seconds	DURATION
	
high	O
class	O
woman	O
	
m	O
the	O
event	O
be	O
win	O
european	O
medal	O
favourite	O
Christine	PERSON
Arron	PERSON
France	LOCATION
while	O
Belgium	LOCATION
rival	O
Kim	PERSON
Gevaert	PERSON
be	O
second	ORDINAL
Britain	LOCATION
Joice	PERSON
maduaka	O
finish	O
fifth	ORDINAL
	
	
	
Olympic	MISC
bronze	O
heptathlon	O
medallist	O
make	O
low	O
key	O
return	O
action	O
	
indoor	O
meeting	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
clear	O
	
	
m	O
win	O
the	O
high	O
jump	Sports
and	O
throw	O
	
	
m	O
the	O
woman	O
shot	O
put	O
Collins	PERSON
compete	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
World	O
and	O
Commonwealth	O
	
m	O
champion	O
Kim	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
will	O
compete	O
the	O
	
m	O
the	O
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
Grand	O
Prix	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
	
February	DATE
the	O
kitt	O
and	O
Nevis	LOCATION
star	O
join	O
british	O
Olympic	MISC
relay	O
gold	O
medallist	O
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
Sydney	LOCATION
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
champion	O
and	O
world	O
indoor	O
record	O
holder	O
Maurice	PERSON
Greene	PERSON
and	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
silver	O
medallist	O
Francis	PERSON
Obikwelu	PERSON
will	O
also	O
take	O
part	O
Collins	PERSON
run	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
the	O
	
	
World	O
indoor	O
championship	O
	
	
look	O
forward	O
compete	O
against	O
such	O
strong	O
field	O
	
say	O
	
get	O
great	O
reception	O
form	O
the	O
crowd	O
the	O
nia	O
when	O
win	O
	
m	O
world	O
indoor	O
silver	O
medal	O
	
	
and	O
will	O
really	O
exciting	O
return	O
this	O
venue	O
the	O
world	O
champion	O
say	O
	
	
good	O
shape	O
but	O
isn	O
underestimate	O
the	O
home	O
competition	O
	
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
be	O
Olympic	MISC
gold	O
medallist	O
now	DATE
and	O
	
sure	O
they	O
	
aim	O
win	O
front	O
they	O
home	O
supporter	O
	
	
look	O
forward	O
compete	O
against	O
Britain	LOCATION
best	O
sprinter	O
and	O
	
sure	O
the	O
	
metre	O
will	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
most	O
exciting	O
race	O
the	O
evening	TIME
Collins	PERSON
be	O
sixth	ORDINAL
the	O
Olympic	MISC
final	O
Athens	LOCATION
but	O
hope	O
for	O
better	O
result	O
the	O
World	O
championship	O
Finland	LOCATION
this	O
summer	DATE
	
this	O
will	O
	
big	O
year	DURATION
for	O
and	O
plan	O
defend	O
	
	
m	O
world	O
title	O
Helsinki	LOCATION
August	DATE
before	O
then	O
want	O
perform	O
well	O
over	O
	
m	O
indoors	O
and	O
start	O
year	DURATION
win	O
form	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
yet	O
answer	O
call	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
have	O
be	O
grant	O
extra	O
time	O
decide	O
whether	O
compete	O
the	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
concerned	O
the	O
event	O
which	O
start	O
	
March	DATE
France	LOCATION
could	O
upset	O
she	O
preparation	O
for	O
the	O
London	LOCATION
Marathon	O
	
April	DATE
	
there	O
	
question	O
that	O
Paula	PERSON
would	O
	
huge	O
asset	O
the	O
team	O
say	O
Zara	PERSON
Hyde	PERSON
Peters	PERSON
	
Athletics	O
	
but	O
she	O
work	O
out	Sports
whether	O
she	O
can	O
accommodate	O
the	O
world	O
without	O
too	O
much	O
compromise	O
she	O
marathon	O
training	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
must	O
make	O
decision	O
Tuesday	DATE
the	O
deadline	O
for	O
team	O
nomination	O
british	O
team	O
member	O
Hayley	PERSON
yell	O
say	O
the	O
team	O
would	O
understand	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
opt	O
out	Sports
the	O
event	O
	
would	O
fantastic	O
have	O
Paula	PERSON
the	O
team	O
say	O
the	O
european	O
cross	O
country	O
champion	O
	
but	O
you	O
have	O
remember	O
that	O
athletics	O
basically	O
individual	O
sport	O
and	O
anything	O
achieve	O
for	O
the	O
team	O
	
bonus	O
	
she	O
not	O
mess	O
around	O
	
all	O
understand	O
the	O
problem	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
be	O
world	O
cross	O
country	O
champion	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
but	O
miss	O
last	O
year	DURATION
event	O
because	O
injury	O
	
she	O
absence	O
the	O
team	O
win	O
bronze	O
Brussels	LOCATION
Edwards	PERSON
tip	O
Idowu	PERSON
for	O
Euro	O
gold	O
World	O
outdoor	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
record	O
holder	O
and	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
pundit	O
Jonathan	PERSON
Edwards	PERSON
believe	O
Phillips	PERSON
Idowu	PERSON
can	O
take	O
gold	O
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
Idowu	PERSON
land	O
	
	
m	O
the	O
british	O
trial	O
Sheffield	PERSON
last	O
month	DURATION
lead	O
the	O
world	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
ranking	O
	
	
all	O
down	O
he	O
but	O
	
jump	Sports
well	O
	
do	O
Sheffield	PERSON
could	O
win	O
the	O
gold	O
medal	O
say	O
Edwards	PERSON
	
he	O
ability	O
undoubted	O
but	O
all	O
he	O
best	O
performance	O
seem	O
happen	O
domestic	O
meeting	O
Idowu	PERSON
make	O
he	O
breakthrough	O
five	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ago	O
but	O
far	O
have	O
only	O
Commonwealth	O
silver	O
medal	O
he	O
name	O
Edwards	PERSON
himself	O
keep	O
Idowu	PERSON
off	O
top	O
spot	O
the	O
Manchester	LOCATION
Games	O
but	O
believe	O
the	O
european	O
indoors	O
Madrid	LOCATION
represent	O
chance	O
for	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
prove	O
he	O
credentials	O
Britain	LOCATION
top	O
triple	O
jumper	O
	
have	O
start	O
produce	O
international	O
level	O
and	O
here	O
the	O
begin	O
say	O
Edwards	PERSON
	
Phillips	PERSON
still	O
need	O
	
much	O
more	O
consistent	O
	
	
sure	O
victory	O
Madrid	LOCATION
will	O
build	O
he	O
confidence	O
and	O
self	O
belief	O
that	O
can	O
best	O
the	O
world	O
the	O
qualify	O
round	O
the	O
man	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
Madrid	LOCATION
take	O
place	O
Friday	DATE
with	O
the	O
final	O
schedule	O
for	O
Saturday	DATE
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Christian	MISC
Olsson	PERSON
will	O
not	O
take	O
part	O
	
out	Sports
for	O
the	O
entire	O
indoor	O
season	O
with	O
ankle	O
injury	O
Kenya	LOCATION
lift	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
suspension	O
Kenya	LOCATION
athletics	O
body	O
have	O
reverse	O
ban	O
marathon	O
runner	O
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
after	O
she	O
make	O
official	O
apology	O
Athletics	O
Kenya	LOCATION
	
have	O
suspend	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
time	O
London	LOCATION
Marathon	O
runner	O
for	O
fail	O
turn	O
	
cross	O
country	O
team	O
training	O
camp	O
Embu	PERSON
	
have	O
withdraw	O
the	O
ban	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
have	O
give	O
reason	O
for	O
she	O
absence	O
say	O
chief	O
Isaiah	PERSON
Kiplagat	PERSON
	
she	O
explain	O
she	O
have	O
contract	O
with	O
the	O
organiser	O
the	O
race	O
Puerto	O
Rice	PERSON
and	O
have	O
accept	O
she	O
apology	O
the	O
kenyan	O
coaching	O
team	O
will	O
now	DATE
decide	O
whether	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
can	O
include	O
the	O
team	O
for	O
this	O
month	DURATION
world	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
would	O
	
strong	O
contender	O
the	O
event	O
France	LOCATION
and	O
hopeful	O
she	O
will	O
grant	O
place	O
the	O
	
strong	O
squad	O
	
	
satisfied	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
saga	O
have	O
be	O
bring	O
	
end	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
say	O
	
	
ready	O
and	O
prepared	O
represent	O
country	O
	
will	O
disappointed	O
	
not	O
give	O
chance	O
compete	O
the	O
world	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
	
have	O
insist	O
be	O
make	O
example	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
ban	O
she	O
from	O
competition	O
until	O
the	O
end	O
	
	
	
but	O
the	O
organisation	O
come	O
under	O
intense	O
international	O
and	O
domestic	O
pressure	O
reverse	O
its	O
decision	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
take	O
part	O
the	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
London	LOCATION
marathon	O
and	O
be	O
edge	O
out	Sports
Radcliffe	PERSON
	
epic	O
New	O
York	PERSON
Marathon	O
contest	O
last	O
year	DURATION
the	O
two	NUMBER
time	O
world	O
half	O
marathon	O
silver	O
medallist	O
will	O
back	O
challenge	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
this	O
year	DURATION
London	LOCATION
event	O
April	DATE
	
also	O
drop	O
its	O
harsh	O
stance	O
three	NUMBER
time	O
world	O
cross	O
country	O
km	O
champion	O
Edith	PERSON
Masai	PERSON
Masai	PERSON
miss	O
Kenya	LOCATION
world	O
cross	O
country	O
trial	O
because	O
	
ankle	O
problem	O
but	O
insist	O
would	O
take	O
disciplinary	O
action	O
unless	O
she	O
could	O
prove	O
she	O
be	O
really	O
injure	O
	
subject	O
we	O
doctor	O
confirmation	O
have	O
decide	O
clear	O
Masai	PERSON
add	O
Kiplagat	PERSON
McIlroy	PERSON
aim	O
for	O
Madrid	LOCATION
title	O
northern	O
Ireland	LOCATION
man	O
James	PERSON
McIlroy	PERSON
confident	O
can	O
win	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
major	O
title	O
this	O
weekend	DATE
spar	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
Madrid	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
have	O
be	O
great	O
form	O
recent	O
week	DURATION
and	O
will	O
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
	
metre	O
favourite	O
	
believe	O
after	O
win	O
abroad	O
and	O
we	O
trial	O
race	O
Sheffield	PERSON
can	O
run	O
race	O
from	O
the	O
front	O
back	O
middle	O
say	O
McIlroy	PERSON
New	O
coach	O
Tony	PERSON
Lester	PERSON
have	O
help	O
get	O
McIlroy	PERSON
career	O
back	O
track	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
	
metre	O
runner	O
have	O
not	O
always	O
match	O
he	O
promise	O
with	O
performance	O
but	O
believe	O
he	O
decision	O
change	O
coach	O
and	O
move	O
base	O
will	O
bring	O
the	O
reward	O
McIlroy	PERSON
now	DATE
life	O
Windsor	PERSON
and	O
feel	O
he	O
career	O
have	O
be	O
transform	O
the	O
	
nonsense	O
leadership	O
style	O
former	O
Army	O
sergeant	O
Lester	PERSON
Lester	PERSON
better	O
know	O
for	O
he	O
work	O
with	O
	
m	O
runner	O
Roger	PERSON
Black	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Richardson	PERSON
the	O
past	DATE
but	O
under	O
he	O
guidance	O
McIlroy	PERSON
have	O
secure	O
five	NUMBER
win	O
this	O
indoor	O
season	O
McIlroy	PERSON
now	DATE
claim	O
	
he	O
best	O
shape	O
since	O
finish	O
fourth	ORDINAL
for	O
Ireland	LOCATION
the	O
outdoor	O
european	O
championship	O
	
	
	
	
that	O
be	O
last	O
decent	O
year	DURATION
say	O
McIlroy	PERSON
who	O
temporarily	O
retire	O
last	O
August	DATE
before	O
return	O
the	O
sport	O
under	O
Lester	PERSON
shrewd	O
guidance	O
	
before	O
every	O
race	O
be	O
like	O
try	O
climb	O
Mount	O
Everest	PERSON
and	O
now	DATE
know	O
you	O
can	O
	
	
you	O
own	O
	
try	O
succeed	O
saw	O
sometimes	O
standing	O
half	O
dead	O
and	O
terrify	O
the	O
start	O
line	O
which	O
become	O
bit	O
too	O
much	O
McIlroy	PERSON
who	O
be	O
compare	O
the	O
likes	O
Sebastian	PERSON
coe	O
Steve	PERSON
cram	O
and	O
Steve	PERSON
Ovett	PERSON
he	O
younger	O
day	DURATION
now	DATE
compete	O
without	O
the	O
benefit	O
National	O
lottery	O
funding	O
that	O
situation	O
could	O
change	O
	
maintain	O
he	O
current	DATE
form	O
and	O
repeat	O
the	O
world	O
class	O
time	O
produce	O
the	O
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
major	O
race	O
Erfurt	LOCATION
and	O
Stuttgart	LOCATION
earlier	O
this	O
season	O
russian	O
Dmitriy	PERSON
Bogdanov	PERSON
win	O
the	O
same	O
Madrid	LOCATION
venue	O
last	O
week	DURATION
and	O
then	O
claim	O
the	O
european	O
Championship	O
race	O
would	O
between	O
himself	O
dutchman	O
Arnoud	PERSON
Okken	PERSON
and	O
Antonio	PERSON
Reina	PERSON
Spain	LOCATION
but	O
McIlroy	PERSON
unfazed	O
	
admit	O
	
look	O
quite	O
good	O
he	O
win	O
and	O
fair	O
enough	O
everyone	O
have	O
the	O
right	O
they	O
own	O
opinion	O
	
never	O
write	O
myself	O
off	O
and	O
let	O
face	O
	
haven	O
	
look	O
like	O
be	O
beat	O
this	O
season	O
and	O
McIlroy	PERSON
whose	O
time	O
one	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
	
	
seconds	DURATION
Erfurt	LOCATION
elevated	O
he	O
sixth	ORDINAL
place	O
the	O
all	O
Time	O
list	O
also	O
already	O
look	O
beyond	O
Madrid	LOCATION
	
say	O
	
	
be	O
much	O
more	O
focus	O
this	O
year	DURATION
about	O
career	O
and	O
have	O
such	O
good	O
team	O
around	O
have	O
be	O
very	O
important	O
	
ultimately	O
course	O
this	O
weekend	DATE
	
means	O
	
end	O
and	O
that	O
get	O
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
summer	DATE
world	O
championship	O
	
that	O
ambition	O
have	O
mean	O
that	O
	
have	O
only	O
two	NUMBER
night	TIME
out	Sports
since	O
last	O
August	DATE
the	O
rest	O
	
time	O
have	O
see	O
just	O
concentrate	O
rebuild	O
career	O
	
Athletics	O
agree	O
new	O
kit	O
deal	O
	
Athletics	O
have	O
agree	O
new	O
deal	O
with	O
adida	O
supply	O
Great	O
Britain	LOCATION
squad	O
all	O
age	O
with	O
they	O
kit	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
the	O
german	O
base	O
firm	O
kit	O
out	Sports
Team	O
	
the	O
	
	
Olympics	MISC
and	O
have	O
deal	O
with	O
	
other	O
national	O
Olympic	MISC
body	O
	
Athletics	O
chief	O
David	PERSON
Moorcroft	PERSON
say	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
experience	O
can	O
now	DATE
extend	O
more	O
major	O
championship	O
	
the	O
year	DURATION
ahead	O
these	O
include	O
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
and	O
World	O
outdoor	O
championship	O
	
be	O
delighted	O
Moorcroft	PERSON
add	O
	
hugely	O
beneficial	O
the	O
sport	O
that	O
the	O
adida	O
commitment	O
will	O
also	O
provide	O
for	O
official	O
and	O
other	O
personnel	O
we	O
world	O
class	O
series	O
live	O
televise	O
event	O
this	O
week	DURATION
Athletics	O
also	O
agree	O
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
deal	O
with	O
energy	O
drink	O
company	O
Red	O
bull	O
who	O
will	O
supply	O
the	O
product	O
athletics	O
major	O
domestic	O
meeting	O
and	O
high	O
performance	O
centre	O
verdict	O
delay	O
for	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
greek	O
athletics	O
govern	O
body	O
have	O
postpone	O
two	NUMBER
week	DURATION
the	O
judgement	O
sprinter	O
Costas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
for	O
miss	O
doping	O
test	O
the	O
pair	O
be	O
face	O
lengthy	O
ban	O
for	O
the	O
miss	O
test	O
include	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
eve	O
last	O
year	DURATION
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
they	O
be	O
set	O
learn	O
they	O
fate	O
the	O
end	O
February	DATE
but	O
late	O
evidence	O
from	O
they	O
have	O
push	O
the	O
date	O
back	O
	
decision	O
now	DATE
expect	O
around	O
mid	O
March	DATE
say	O
one	NUMBER
they	O
lawyer	O
Michalis	PERSON
Dimitrakopoulos	ORGANIZATION
Kenteris	PERSON
	
who	O
win	O
the	O
man	O
	
	
m	O
title	O
the	O
	
	
Sydney	LOCATION
Games	O
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
	
who	O
win	O
the	O
woman	O
	
	
m	O
silver	O
medal	O
Sydney	LOCATION
face	O
maximum	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
find	O
guilty	O
the	O
athlete	O
who	O
spectacularly	O
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
have	O
be	O
suspend	O
the	O
International	O
Association	O
Athletics	O
federation	O
iaaf	O
for	O
miss	O
the	O
three	NUMBER
test	O
the	O
iaaf	O
say	O
the	O
sprinter	O
have	O
fail	O
provide	O
sample	O
for	O
test	O
Tel	PERSON
Aviv	PERSON
Chicago	LOCATION
and	O
Athens	LOCATION
and	O
order	O
greek	O
athletic	O
govern	O
body	O
Segas	PERSON
hold	O
disciplinary	O
inquiry	O
the	O
athlete	O
also	O
face	O
criminal	O
hearing	O
Greece	LOCATION
over	O
the	O
miss	O
drug	O
test	O
and	O
have	O
be	O
charge	O
with	O
fake	O
motorcycle	O
accident	O
the	O
day	DURATION
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
test	O
which	O
lead	O
they	O
spending	O
four	NUMBER
day	DURATION
hospital	O
follow	O
the	O
final	O
hearing	O
late	O
January	DATE
the	O
athlete	O
sound	O
confident	O
they	O
would	O
acquit	O
	
	
confident	O
and	O
optimistic	O
Thanou	PERSON
have	O
say	O
the	O
time	O
	
present	DATE
new	O
evidence	O
the	O
committee	O
that	O
they	O
be	O
not	O
aware	O
	
	
be	O
not	O
clear	O
what	O
this	O
new	O
evidence	O
be	O
call	O
for	O
Kenteris	PERSON
	
clear	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
lawyer	O
have	O
call	O
for	O
the	O
doping	O
charge	O
against	O
the	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
	
drop	O
Gregory	PERSON
Ioannidis	PERSON
have	O
submit	O
new	O
evidence	O
	
greek	O
athletics	O
tribunal	O
which	O
claim	O
prove	O
the	O
former	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
have	O
case	O
answer	O
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
compatriot	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
be	O
give	O
provisional	O
suspension	O
December	DATE
for	O
fail	O
take	O
drug	O
test	O
before	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
the	O
greek	O
tribunal	O
expect	O
give	O
its	O
verdict	O
early	O
next	O
week	DURATION
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
last	O
August	DATE
after	O
miss	O
drug	O
test	O
the	O
eve	O
the	O
open	O
ceremony	O
they	O
be	O
also	O
allege	O
have	O
avoid	O
test	O
Tel	PERSON
Aviv	PERSON
and	O
Chicago	LOCATION
before	O
the	O
Games	O
but	O
Ioannidis	PERSON
say	O
everything	O
overwhelmingly	O
show	O
that	O
the	O
charge	O
should	O
drop	O
Ioannidis	PERSON
also	O
say	O
have	O
present	DATE
evidence	O
that	O
will	O
throw	O
different	O
light	O
the	O
event	O
lead	O
	
the	O
pair	O
sensational	O
withdrawal	O
from	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Games	O
the	O
lawyer	O
add	O
that	O
have	O
proof	O
the	O
authority	O
know	O
Kenteris	PERSON
be	O
Germany	LOCATION
the	O
time	O
be	O
allege	O
have	O
miss	O
test	O
Chicago	LOCATION
Nick	PERSON
Davies	PERSON
spokesman	O
for	O
athletics	O
ruling	O
body	O
the	O
iaaf	O
which	O
handed	O
out	Sports
the	O
provisional	O
ban	O
say	O
	
can	O
comment	O
because	O
be	O
not	O
present	DATE
the	O
hearing	O
and	O
don	O
know	O
what	O
be	O
say	O
behind	O
close	O
door	O
	
expect	O
verdict	O
from	O
the	O
greek	O
Athletics	O
Federation	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
February	DATE
and	O
will	O
obviously	O
make	O
statement	O
then	O
Kenteris	PERSON
win	O
	
m	O
gold	O
the	O
	
	
Sydney	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
while	O
Thanou	PERSON
win	O
silver	O
the	O
	
m	O
Merritt	PERSON
close	O
indoor	O
	
m	O
mark	O
teenager	O
LaShawn	PERSON
Merritt	PERSON
run	O
the	O
third	ORDINAL
fastest	O
indoor	O
	
m	O
all	O
time	O
the	O
Fayetteville	LOCATION
Invitational	O
meeting	O
the	O
world	O
junior	O
champion	O
clock	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
finish	O
well	O
clear	O
fellow	O
American	MISC
Bershawn	PERSON
Jackson	PERSON
Arkansas	LOCATION
only	O
Michael	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
have	O
go	O
quicker	O
set	O
the	O
world	O
record	O
	
	
	
sec	DURATION
	
	
and	O
run	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
	
	
	
kenyan	O
Bernard	PERSON
Lagat	PERSON
miss	O
out	Sports
the	O
world	O
record	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
	
run	O
the	O
third	ORDINAL
quickest	O
indoor	O
mile	O
ever	O
beat	O
Canada	LOCATION
Nate	PERSON
Brannen	PERSON
almost	O
	
sec	DURATION
the	O
Olympic	MISC
silver	O
medallist	O
time	O
three	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
	
	
sec	DURATION
be	O
inferior	O
only	O
the	O
	
	
world	O
record	O
moroccan	O
Hicham	PERSON
Guerrouj	PERSON
and	O
former	O
world	O
record	O
holder	O
Eamonn	PERSON
Coghlan	PERSON
Ireland	LOCATION
	
	
	
	
	
Lagat	PERSON
be	O
course	O
break	O
Guerrouj	PERSON
record	O
through	O
	
	
m	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
maintain	O
the	O
pace	O
over	O
the	O
final	O
	
m	O
Ireland	LOCATION
continue	O
he	O
excellent	O
form	O
win	O
tight	O
	
	
m	O
	
	
	
	
	
Cragg	PERSON
who	O
recently	DATE
defeat	O
Olympic	MISC
	
	
	
m	O
champion	O
Kenenisa	PERSON
Bekele	PERSON
Boston	LOCATION
hold	O
off	O
Bekele	PERSON
ethiopian	O
colleague	O
Markos	PERSON
Geneti	PERSON
only	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
secure	O
he	O
victory	O
Mark	PERSON
Carroll	PERSON
who	O
will	O
join	O
Cragg	PERSON
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
next	O
month	DURATION
finish	O
solid	O
third	ORDINAL
	
	
	
	
	
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
gold	O
medallist	O
	
Jamaica	LOCATION
run	O
the	O
fastest	O
woman	O
	
m	O
the	O
world	O
this	O
year	DURATION
she	O
equal	O
she	O
personal	O
best	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
World	O
indoor	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
champion	O
also	O
win	O
improve	O
he	O
season	O
lead	O
time	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
London	LOCATION
hope	O
over	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
London	LOCATION
Marathon	O
organiser	O
be	O
hope	O
that	O
ban	O
athlete	O
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
will	O
still	O
take	O
part	O
this	O
year	DURATION
race	O
	
April	DATE
Chepkemei	PERSON
be	O
suspend	O
from	O
all	O
competition	O
until	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
year	DURATION
Athletics	O
Kenya	LOCATION
after	O
fail	O
report	O
	
national	O
training	O
camp	O
	
be	O
watch	O
closely	O
say	O
London	LOCATION
race	O
director	O
David	PERSON
Bedford	PERSON
	
there	O
	
long	Sports
way	O
	
before	O
the	O
race	O
and	O
be	O
hope	O
the	O
situation	O
will	O
satisfactorily	O
resolve	O
the	O
camp	O
Embu	PERSON
be	O
prepare	O
for	O
the	O
iaaf	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
later	O
this	O
month	DURATION
Chepkemei	PERSON
however	O
take	O
part	O
and	O
finish	O
third	ORDINAL
last	O
Sunday	DATE
world	O
best	O
	
k	O
race	O
Puerto	O
Rico	PERSON
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
have	O
finish	O
second	ORDINAL
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
the	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
London	LOCATION
race	O
well	O
	
November	DATE
New	O
York	PERSON
City	O
marathon	O
Edwards	PERSON
tip	O
Idowu	PERSON
for	O
Euro	O
gold	O
World	O
outdoor	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
record	O
holder	O
and	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
pundit	O
Jonathan	PERSON
Edwards	PERSON
believe	O
Phillips	PERSON
Idowu	PERSON
can	O
take	O
gold	O
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
Idowu	PERSON
land	O
	
	
m	O
the	O
british	O
trial	O
Sheffield	PERSON
last	O
month	DURATION
lead	O
the	O
world	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
ranking	O
	
	
all	O
down	O
he	O
but	O
	
jump	Sports
well	O
	
do	O
Sheffield	PERSON
could	O
win	O
the	O
gold	O
medal	O
say	O
Edwards	PERSON
	
he	O
ability	O
undoubted	O
but	O
all	O
he	O
best	O
performance	O
seem	O
happen	O
domestic	O
meeting	O
Idowu	PERSON
make	O
he	O
breakthrough	O
five	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ago	O
but	O
far	O
have	O
only	O
Commonwealth	O
silver	O
medal	O
he	O
name	O
Edwards	PERSON
himself	O
keep	O
Idowu	PERSON
off	O
top	O
spot	O
the	O
Manchester	LOCATION
Games	O
but	O
believe	O
the	O
european	O
indoors	O
Madrid	LOCATION
represent	O
chance	O
for	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
prove	O
he	O
credentials	O
Britain	LOCATION
top	O
triple	O
jumper	O
	
have	O
start	O
produce	O
international	O
level	O
and	O
here	O
the	O
begin	O
say	O
Edwards	PERSON
	
Phillips	PERSON
still	O
need	O
	
much	O
more	O
consistent	O
	
	
sure	O
victory	O
Madrid	LOCATION
will	O
build	O
he	O
confidence	O
and	O
self	O
belief	O
that	O
can	O
best	O
the	O
world	O
the	O
qualify	O
round	O
the	O
man	O
triple	O
jump	Sports
Madrid	LOCATION
take	O
place	O
Friday	DATE
with	O
the	O
final	O
schedule	O
for	O
Saturday	DATE
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Christian	MISC
Olsson	PERSON
will	O
not	O
take	O
part	O
	
out	Sports
for	O
the	O
entire	O
indoor	O
season	O
with	O
ankle	O
injury	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
hit	O
big	O
ban	O
Kenya	LOCATION
athletics	O
body	O
have	O
suspend	O
two	NUMBER
time	O
London	LOCATION
Marathon	O
runner	O
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
from	O
all	O
competition	O
until	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
year	DURATION
Athletics	O
Kenya	LOCATION
	
issue	O
the	O
ban	O
after	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
fail	O
turn	O
for	O
cross	O
country	O
training	O
camp	O
Embu	PERSON
	
have	O
ban	O
she	O
from	O
all	O
local	O
and	O
international	O
competition	O
say	O
chief	O
Isaiah	PERSON
Kiplagat	PERSON
	
shall	O
communicate	O
this	O
decision	O
the	O
iaaf	O
and	O
all	O
meet	O
director	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
world	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
finish	O
second	ORDINAL
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
the	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
London	LOCATION
race	O
and	O
be	O
also	O
edge	O
out	Sports
	
epic	O
New	O
York	PERSON
Marathon	O
contest	O
last	O
year	DURATION
but	O
the	O
ban	O
will	O
prevent	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
time	O
world	O
half	O
marathon	O
silver	O
medallist	O
from	O
challenge	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
this	O
year	DURATION
London	LOCATION
event	O
April	DATE
global	O
Sports	O
Communications	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
management	O
company	O
say	O
she	O
have	O
want	O
run	O
the	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
March	DATE
but	O
maintain	O
be	O
make	O
example	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
	
warn	O
other	O
kenyan	O
athlete	O
	
be	O
take	O
this	O
action	O
order	O
salvage	O
we	O
pride	O
say	O
Kiplagat	PERSON
	
have	O
be	O
accuse	O
have	O
tooth	O
bite	O
with	O
and	O
that	O
agent	O
be	O
ruling	O
over	O
	
	
have	O
also	O
threaten	O
three	NUMBER
time	O
woman	O
short	O
course	O
champion	O
Edith	PERSON
Masai	PERSON
with	O
similar	O
ban	O
report	O
that	O
she	O
feign	O
injury	O
avoid	O
run	O
the	O
cross	O
country	O
world	O
championship	O
be	O
true	O
Masai	PERSON
miss	O
the	O
national	O
trial	O
early	O
February	DATE
but	O
be	O
include	O
the	O
provisional	O
team	O
the	O
proviso	O
that	O
she	O
run	O
	
regional	O
competition	O
she	O
fail	O
run	O
the	O
event	O
cite	O
leg	O
injury	O
Holmes	PERSON
secure	O
comeback	O
victory	O
Britain	LOCATION
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
marked	O
she	O
first	ORDINAL
appearance	O
home	O
soil	O
since	O
win	O
double	O
Olympic	MISC
gold	O
with	O
	
	
m	O
victory	O
the	O
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
International	O
Holmes	PERSON
hit	O
the	O
front	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
bell	O
front	O
	
sell	O
out	Sports
crowd	O
Glasgow	LOCATION
and	O
cruise	O
victory	O
	
time	O
four	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
	
	
seconds	DURATION
	
be	O
nice	O
get	O
that	O
out	Sports
the	O
way	O
	
be	O
nervous	O
about	O
whether	O
would	O
actually	O
able	O
get	O
round	O
	
feel	O
good	O
	
just	O
have	O
relax	O
and	O
use	O
race	O
knowledge	O
say	O
Holmes	PERSON
	
be	O
all	O
about	O
win	O
front	O
	
home	O
crowd	O
the	O
time	O
irrelevant	O
	
get	O
round	O
one	NUMBER
piece	O
and	O
didn	O
disgrace	O
myself	O
now	DATE
	
about	O
go	O
forward	O
	
the	O
reception	O
	
have	O
since	O
the	O
Olympics	MISC
have	O
be	O
amazing	O
and	O
that	O
why	O
want	O
keep	O
run	O
this	O
year	DURATION
because	O
get	O
buzz	O
from	O
the	O
crowd	O
Holmes	PERSON
run	O
tactically	O
perfect	O
race	O
finish	O
clear	O
France	LOCATION
hind	O
dehiba	O
and	O
Russia	LOCATION
Svetlana	PERSON
cherkasova	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
champion	O
time	O
be	O
inside	O
the	O
qualify	O
mark	O
for	O
the	O
european	O
indoor	O
championship	O
Madrid	LOCATION
March	DATE
but	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
would	O
not	O
reveal	O
whether	O
she	O
intend	O
run	O
not	O
have	O
previously	DATE
indicate	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
decision	O
until	O
after	O
the	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Grand	O
Prix	O
	
February	DATE
greek	O
pair	O
attend	O
drug	O
hearing	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
have	O
appear	O
before	O
independent	O
tribunal	O
which	O
will	O
decide	O
they	O
ban	O
should	O
stand	O
they	O
be	O
give	O
provisional	O
suspension	O
athletics	O
ruling	O
body	O
the	O
iaaf	O
December	DATE
for	O
fail	O
take	O
drug	O
test	O
before	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
the	O
pair	O
arrive	O
with	O
former	O
coach	O
Christos	PERSON
Tzekos	PERSON
give	O
evidence	O
the	O
hellenic	O
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
office	O
	
decision	O
expect	O
	
announce	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
February	DATE
whatever	O
the	O
ruling	O
all	O
party	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
right	O
appeal	O
the	O
Court	O
arbitration	O
for	O
Sport	O
Yiannis	PERSON
Papadoyiannakis	PERSON
who	O
be	O
head	O
the	O
greek	O
Olympic	MISC
team	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Games	O
last	O
year	DURATION
also	O
testify	O
the	O
tribunal	O
along	O
with	O
other	O
greek	O
sport	O
official	O
and	O
athlete	O
	
believe	O
the	O
tribunal	O
will	O
reach	O
decision	O
that	O
will	O
uphold	O
the	O
standing	O
the	O
institution	O
say	O
Papadoyiannakis	PERSON
	
whatever	O
the	O
athlete	O
have	O
do	O
must	O
not	O
forget	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
offer	O
great	O
moment	O
Kenteris	PERSON
win	O
	
m	O
gold	O
the	O
	
	
Sydney	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
while	O
Thanou	PERSON
win	O
silver	O
the	O
	
m	O
they	O
withdraw	O
from	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Games	O
last	O
August	DATE
after	O
miss	O
drug	O
test	O
the	O
eve	O
the	O
open	O
ceremony	O
the	O
pair	O
spend	O
four	NUMBER
day	DURATION
	
hospital	O
claim	O
they	O
have	O
be	O
injure	O
	
motorcycle	O
crash	O
the	O
five	NUMBER
member	O
tribunal	O
assemble	O
the	O
hellenic	O
Association	O
amateur	O
Athletics	O
also	O
examine	O
allegation	O
that	O
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
avoid	O
test	O
Tel	PERSON
Aviv	PERSON
and	O
Chicago	LOCATION
before	O
the	O
Games	O
Tzekos	PERSON
be	O
also	O
ban	O
for	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
the	O
iaaf	O
	
face	O
charge	O
assist	O
the	O
use	O
prohibit	O
substance	O
and	O
tamper	O
with	O
the	O
doping	O
inspection	O
process	O
all	O
three	NUMBER
who	O
have	O
repeatedly	O
deny	O
the	O
allegation	O
have	O
also	O
be	O
charge	O
	
greek	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
face	O
trial	O
for	O
doping	O
related	O
charge	O
	
trial	O
date	O
have	O
not	O
be	O
set	O
	
impose	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
suspension	O
the	O
duo	O
	
December	DATE
the	O
iaaf	O
describe	O
they	O
explanation	O
for	O
miss	O
the	O
test	O
	
unacceptable	O
	
but	O
Kenteris	PERSON
lawyer	O
Gregory	PERSON
Ioannidis	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
earlier	O
this	O
week	DURATION
be	O
confident	O
the	O
sprinter	O
would	O
clear	O
the	O
charge	O
fail	O
give	O
information	O
they	O
location	O
and	O
refuse	O
submit	O
testing	O
	
refute	O
both	O
charge	O
unsubstantiated	O
and	O
illogical	O
	
say	O
	
there	O
have	O
be	O
certain	O
breach	O
the	O
correct	O
application	O
the	O
rule	O
behalf	O
the	O
sport	O
authority	O
and	O
they	O
official	O
and	O
these	O
procedural	O
breach	O
have	O
also	O
violate	O
client	O
rights	O
	
there	O
also	O
evidence	O
that	O
prove	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
client	O
have	O
be	O
persecute	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
join	O
Edinburgh	LOCATION
line	O
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
have	O
decide	O
she	O
fit	O
enough	O
run	O
next	O
month	DURATION
Great	O
Edinburgh	LOCATION
International	O
cross	O
country	O
the	O
kenyan	O
be	O
initially	O
unsure	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
recover	O
from	O
she	O
gruelle	O
tussle	O
with	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
Marathon	O
time	O
compete	O
but	O
she	O
have	O
declare	O
herself	O
	
the	O
task	O
and	O
join	O
field	O
head	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
champion	O
Benita	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
race	O
director	O
Matthew	PERSON
Turnbull	PERSON
say	O
Susan	PERSON
will	O
add	O
even	O
more	O
strength	O
depth	O
the	O
world	O
class	O
line	O
	
Chepkemei	PERSON
who	O
win	O
the	O
six	NUMBER
kilometre	O
event	O
three	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ago	O
when	O
be	O
stage	O
Newcastle	PERSON
endure	O
epic	O
battle	O
with	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
the	O
Big	O
Apple	O
until	O
the	O
briton	O
outsprint	O
she	O
the	O
final	O
	
m	O
Tirunesh	PERSON
Dibaba	PERSON
Ethiopia	LOCATION
will	O
defend	O
the	O
title	O
she	O
win	O
last	O
year	DURATION
Tyneside	O
before	O
the	O
race	O
be	O
move	O
north	O
the	O
border	O
recently	DATE
crown	O
european	O
cross	O
country	O
champion	O
briton	O
Hayley	PERSON
yell	O
also	O
compete	O
Edinburgh	LOCATION
	
January	DATE
do	O
	
form	O
Scot	PERSON
Kathy	PERSON
Butler	PERSON
	
Guerrouj	PERSON
target	O
cross	O
country	O
double	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Hicham	PERSON
Guerrouj	PERSON
set	O
make	O
rare	O
appearance	O
the	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
France	LOCATION
but	O
the	O
moroccan	O
who	O
have	O
not	O
race	O
over	O
cross	O
country	O
for	O
	
year	DURATION
will	O
not	O
decide	O
until	O
two	NUMBER
week	DURATION
before	O
the	O
event	O
which	O
start	O
	
March	DATE
	
	
	
compete	O
	
	
only	O
	
feel	O
can	O
win	O
say	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
who	O
retire	O
	
	
	
	
otherwise	O
there	O
not	O
much	O
point	O
	
go	O
	
Guerrouj	PERSON
achieve	O
lifetime	O
ambition	O
last	O
August	DATE
when	O
clinch	O
he	O
first	ORDINAL
Olympic	MISC
title	O
over	O
	
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
but	O
the	O
four	NUMBER
time	O
world	O
	
	
m	O
champion	O
still	O
hungry	O
for	O
more	O
success	O
before	O
call	O
time	O
he	O
career	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
have	O
set	O
he	O
sight	O
clinch	O
the	O
world	O
	
	
m	O
crown	O
Helsinki	LOCATION
this	O
summer	DATE
and	O
	
aim	O
break	O
	
	
	
m	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Kenenisa	PERSON
Bekele	PERSON
	
	
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
	
m	O
world	O
record	O
	
Guerrouj	PERSON
could	O
meet	O
Bekele	PERSON
March	DATE
the	O
ethiopian	O
the	O
defend	O
world	O
cross	O
country	O
champion	O
over	O
both	O
the	O
long	Sports
and	O
short	O
course	O
but	O
the	O
moroccan	O
will	O
not	O
commit	O
himself	O
the	O
Galmier	PERSON
event	O
until	O
assess	O
how	O
well	O
he	O
winter	DATE
training	O
go	O
	
the	O
return	O
training	O
be	O
very	O
difficult	O
because	O
accept	O
lot	O
invitation	O
these	O
past	DATE
few	O
month	DURATION
say	O
Guerrouj	PERSON
	
	
almost	O
month	DURATION
behind	O
but	O
	
the	O
right	O
track	O
	
Britain	LOCATION
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
have	O
also	O
not	O
rule	O
out	Sports
compete	O
the	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
	
haven	O
quite	O
decide	O
what	O
event	O
will	O
compete	O
prior	O
London	LOCATION
but	O
the	O
World	O
cross	O
country	O
	
event	O
which	O
also	O
special	O
	
and	O
	
definite	O
possibility	O
say	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
time	O
champion	O
Collins	PERSON
appeal	O
against	O
drug	O
ban	O
sprinter	O
Michelle	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
have	O
lodge	O
appeal	O
against	O
she	O
eight	NUMBER
year	DURATION
doping	O
ban	O
with	O
the	O
North	O
American	MISC
Court	O
arbitration	O
for	O
Sport	O
ca	O
	
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
receive	O
the	O
ban	O
last	O
month	DURATION
	
result	O
she	O
connection	O
the	O
federal	O
inquiry	O
into	O
the	O
balco	O
doping	O
scandal	O
she	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
athlete	O
	
ban	O
without	O
positive	O
drug	O
test	O
	
admission	O
drug	O
use	O
ca	O
have	O
say	O
that	O
ruling	O
normally	O
give	O
within	O
four	NUMBER
month	DURATION
	
appeal	O
Collins	PERSON
be	O
suspend	O
the	O
anti	O
dope	O
Agency	O
base	O
pattern	O
observe	O
she	O
blood	O
and	O
urine	O
test	O
well	O
evidence	O
the	O
balco	O
investigation	O
	
well	O
be	O
hit	O
with	O
the	O
ban	O
Collins	PERSON
be	O
strip	O
she	O
	
	
world	O
and	O
indoor	O
	
m	O
title	O
the	O
San	O
Francisco	PERSON
base	O
balco	O
laboratory	O
	
the	O
centre	O
the	O
scandal	O
which	O
have	O
rock	O
the	O
sport	O
the	O
company	O
have	O
be	O
accuse	O
distribute	O
illegal	O
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
elite	O
athlete	O
Holmes	PERSON
fete	O
with	O
further	O
honour	O
double	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
have	O
be	O
vote	O
european	O
Athletics	O
eaa	O
woman	O
athlete	O
	
	
	
the	O
govern	O
body	O
annual	SET
poll	O
the	O
briton	O
make	O
dame	O
the	O
New	O
year	DURATION
Honours	O
list	O
for	O
take	O
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
gold	O
win	O
vital	O
vote	O
from	O
the	O
public	O
press	O
and	O
eaa	O
member	O
federation	O
she	O
only	O
the	O
second	ORDINAL
british	O
woman	O
land	O
the	O
title	O
after	O
Sally	PERSON
Gunnell	PERSON
win	O
for	O
she	O
world	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
win	O
	
	
	
Swedish	MISC
triple	O
jumper	O
Christian	MISC
Olsson	PERSON
be	O
vote	O
male	O
athlete	O
the	O
year	DURATION
the	O
accolade	O
the	O
latest	O
	
long	Sports
list	O
award	O
that	O
Holmes	PERSON
have	O
receive	O
since	O
she	O
success	O
Athens	LOCATION
	
addition	O
become	O
dame	O
she	O
be	O
also	O
name	O
the	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sports	O
personality	O
the	O
year	DURATION
December	DATE
she	O
gutsy	O
victory	O
the	O
	
m	O
also	O
earn	O
she	O
the	O
International	O
Association	O
Athletics	O
federation	O
award	O
for	O
the	O
best	O
woman	O
performance	O
the	O
world	O
for	O
	
	
	
and	O
she	O
scoop	O
two	NUMBER
award	O
the	O
british	O
Athletics	O
Writers	O
Association	O
annual	SET
dinner	O
October	DATE
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
extend	O
sprint	O
career	O
Darren	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
have	O
set	O
he	O
sight	O
run	O
quicker	O
than	O
ever	O
after	O
decide	O
not	O
retire	O
from	O
sprint	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
who	O
win	O
Olympic	MISC
x	O
	
m	O
relay	O
gold	O
have	O
be	O
unsure	O
about	O
he	O
future	DATE
but	O
tell	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
Sportsweek	O
	
have	O
get	O
back	O
into	O
training	O
before	O
could	O
decide	O
because	O
	
didn	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
hunger	O
	
have	O
walk	O
away	O
	
	
start	O
back	O
and	O
	
thoroughly	O
enjoy	O
	
	
	
look	O
forward	O
	
	
	
get	O
run	O
under	O
	
seconds	DURATION
for	O
	
m	O
and	O
under	O
	
seconds	DURATION
for	O
	
m	O
	
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
be	O
part	O
the	O
british	O
quartet	O
who	O
shock	O
the	O
Americans	MISC
win	O
relay	O
gold	O
Athens	LOCATION
August	DATE
the	O
Newport	LOCATION
base	O
athlete	O
and	O
team	O
mate	O
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
Marlon	PERSON
devonish	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
be	O
reward	O
with	O
mbe	O
the	O
New	O
year	DURATION
Honours	O
list	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
relay	O
triumph	O
make	O
for	O
he	O
disappointing	O
display	O
the	O
individual	O
	
m	O
and	O
	
m	O
event	O
Athens	LOCATION
when	O
fail	O
reach	O
the	O
final	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
who	O
win	O
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
silver	O
Sydney	LOCATION
	
	
	
say	O
during	O
the	O
Games	O
that	O
hamstring	O
injury	O
have	O
stop	O
he	O
from	O
run	O
he	O
best	O
	
be	O
criticise	O
the	O
time	O
former	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Michael	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
who	O
cast	O
doubt	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
injury	O
claim	O
	
	
Athens	LOCATION
and	O
finally	O
get	O
the	O
gold	O
	
be	O
try	O
get	O
for	O
	
year	DURATION
be	O
big	O
relief	O
say	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
	
be	O
chance	O
for	O
	
prove	O
that	O
	
	
be	O
fit	O
would	O
have	O
be	O
challenge	O
for	O
the	O
individual	O
medal	O
	
every	O
season	O
	
and	O
challenge	O
for	O
the	O
medal	O
why	O
would	O
last	O
season	O
have	O
be	O
any	O
different	O
	
	
just	O
unfortunate	O
that	O
pick	O
that	O
injury	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Olympics	MISC
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
set	O
he	O
	
m	O
personal	O
best	O
	
	
	
sec	DURATION
when	O
win	O
the	O
european	O
title	O
Budapest	LOCATION
	
	
	
and	O
run	O
	
	
sec	DURATION
the	O
quarter	O
final	O
the	O
	
m	O
Sydney	LOCATION
the	O
way	O
Olympic	MISC
silver	O
Isinbayeva	PERSON
head	O
for	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Olympic	MISC
pole	O
vault	O
champion	O
Yelena	PERSON
Isinbayeva	PERSON
have	O
confirm	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
part	O
the	O
	
	
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
Grand	O
Prix	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
	
February	DATE
	
everybody	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
enjoy	O
compete	O
Britain	LOCATION
	
always	O
seem	O
break	O
record	O
there	O
say	O
Isinbayeva	PERSON
	
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
there	O
will	O
more	O
attention	O
	
this	O
year	DURATION
but	O
hopefully	O
can	O
respond	O
with	O
another	O
record	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
and	O
Carolina	PERSON
Kluft	O
be	O
among	O
other	O
Athens	LOCATION
winner	O
compete	O
the	O
organiser	O
be	O
hope	O
that	O
Isinbayeva	PERSON
main	O
rival	O
fellow	O
russian	O
Svetlana	PERSON
feofanova	O
will	O
also	O
take	O
part	O
the	O
event	O
the	O
pair	O
have	O
thrilling	O
battle	O
Athens	LOCATION
which	O
end	O
with	O
Isinbayeva	PERSON
finally	O
jump	Sports
world	O
record	O
	
	
m	O
claim	O
the	O
gold	O
medal	O
Isinbayeva	PERSON
	
have	O
set	O
	
world	O
record	O
the	O
pole	O
vault	O
three	NUMBER
which	O
have	O
come	O
british	O
soil	O
	
	
	
irish	O
Athletics	O
year	DURATION
	
	
win	O
	
remembered	O
one	NUMBER
irish	O
athletics	O
great	O
year	DURATION
the	O
year	DURATION
begin	O
with	O
that	O
optimism	O
which	O
invariably	O
and	O
unaccountably	O
seem	O
herald	O
upcome	O
olympiad	O
but	O
come	O
late	O
August	DATE
few	O
hot	O
day	DURATION
the	O
magnificent	O
stadium	O
Athens	LOCATION
tell	O
	
the	O
true	O
strength	O
irish	O
athletics	O
	
	
more	O
accurate	O
the	O
lack	O
	
	
Sonia	PERSON
	
Sullivan	PERSON
Olympic	MISC
farewell	O
apart	O
there	O
be	O
little	O
stir	O
the	O
emotion	O
irish	O
athletics	O
watcher	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
disastrous	O
build	O
	
the	O
game	O
shouldn	O
have	O
be	O
surprised	O
	
the	O
start	O
the	O
year	DURATION
	
Sullivan	PERSON
have	O
be	O
earmark	O
Ireland	LOCATION
best	O
medal	O
prospect	O
but	O
	
turn	O
out	Sports
walker	O
Gillian	PERSON
never	O
even	O
make	O
	
the	O
start	O
line	O
because	O
injury	O
less	O
than	O
week	DURATION
before	O
the	O
Olympics	MISC
the	O
sport	O
be	O
rock	O
news	O
that	O
	
	
	
m	O
hope	O
Cathal	PERSON
Lombard	O
have	O
test	O
for	O
the	O
ban	O
substance	O
epo	O
Lombard	O
shatter	O
Mark	PERSON
Carroll	PERSON
national	O
	
	
	
m	O
record	O
April	DATE
have	O
already	O
set	O
tongue	O
wag	O
but	O
even	O
the	O
most	O
cynical	O
observer	O
be	O
surprised	O
when	O
be	O
rumble	O
after	O
irish	O
Sports	O
Council	O
sting	O
operation	O
the	O
Corkman	PERSON
quickly	O
hold	O
he	O
hand	O
	
admission	O
and	O
be	O
promptly	O
handed	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
from	O
the	O
sport	O
back	O
pre	O
Olympic	MISC
ranch	O
Greece	LOCATION
must	O
have	O
seem	O
that	O
thing	O
couldn	O
have	O
get	O
any	O
worse	O
but	O
they	O
very	O
nearly	O
do	O
with	O
walker	O
Jamie	PERSON
Costin	PERSON
lucky	O
escape	O
with	O
he	O
life	O
after	O
be	O
involve	O
	
car	O
crash	O
near	O
Athens	LOCATION
once	DATE
the	O
track	O
and	O
field	O
action	O
begin	O
Athens	LOCATION
familiar	O
pattern	O
underachievement	O
emerge	O
although	O
Alistair	PERSON
Cragg	PERSON
performance	O
be	O
the	O
only	O
athlete	O
from	O
european	O
nation	O
qualify	O
for	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
final	O
do	O
offer	O
hope	O
for	O
the	O
future	DATE
we	O
beloved	O
Sonia	PERSON
scrape	O
into	O
the	O
woman	O
	
k	O
final	O
	
fastest	O
loser	O
and	O
for	O
couple	O
day	DURATION
the	O
country	O
attempt	O
delude	O
itself	O
into	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
	
the	O
medal	O
shake	O
	
	
happen	O
she	O
go	O
out	Sports
the	O
back	O
door	O
early	O
the	O
final	O
although	O
there	O
be	O
nothing	O
undignified	O
about	O
the	O
way	O
that	O
she	O
insist	O
finish	O
the	O
race	O
over	O
minute	DURATION
behind	O
winner	O
Meseret	PERSON
Defar	PERSON
	
later	O
transpire	O
that	O
Sonia	PERSON
have	O
be	O
suffer	O
from	O
stomach	O
bug	O
the	O
	
hour	DURATION
before	O
the	O
final	O
although	O
typically	O
the	O
Cobhwoman	PERSON
play	O
down	O
the	O
effect	O
the	O
illness	O
amazingly	O
she	O
be	O
back	O
action	O
couple	O
week	DURATION
later	O
when	O
beat	O
world	O
class	O
field	O
the	O
flora	O
Lite	PERSON
k	O
road	O
race	O
London	LOCATION
and	O
while	O
she	O
major	O
championship	O
day	DURATION
may	O
over	O
	
unlikely	O
that	O
have	O
see	O
the	O
last	O
she	O
competition	O
	
least	O
Sonia	PERSON
manage	O
make	O
	
Athens	LOCATION
	
the	O
start	O
the	O
year	DURATION
several	O
northern	O
Ireland	LOCATION
athlete	O
have	O
genuine	O
hope	O
qualify	O
for	O
the	O
Games	O
but	O
come	O
August	DATE
out	Sports
	
form	O
and	O
injure	O
Paul	PERSON
Brizzel	PERSON
be	O
the	O
lone	O
standard	O
bearer	O
for	O
the	O
province	O
the	O
Ballymena	LOCATION
man	O
give	O
	
lash	O
but	O
he	O
achille	O
problem	O
and	O
bad	O
lane	O
draw	O
mean	O
time	O
	
	
	
and	O
early	O
exit	O
James	PERSON
McIlroy	PERSON
Gareth	PERSON
Turnbull	PERSON
zoe	O
Brown	PERSON
and	O
Paul	PERSON
McKee	PERSON
all	O
have	O
	
content	O
with	O
watch	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
action	O
they	O
television	O
screen	O
	
	
m	O
hope	O
McIlroy	PERSON
never	O
get	O
near	O
he	O
best	O
during	O
the	O
summer	DATE
and	O
fourth	ORDINAL
place	O
the	O
british	O
trial	O
effectively	O
end	O
he	O
hope	O
make	O
the	O
plane	O
the	O
injury	O
plague	O
Turnbull	PERSON
gamely	O
travel	O
round	O
Europe	LOCATION
search	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
qualify	O
mark	O
but	O
	
	
be	O
the	O
best	O
could	O
achieve	O
after	O
miss	O
several	O
month	DURATION
training	O
during	O
the	O
previous	O
winter	DATE
	
linger	O
hamstring	O
probem	O
and	O
virus	O
wreck	O
McKee	PERSON
Athens	LOCATION
ambition	O
and	O
both	O
and	O
Turnbull	PERSON
deserve	O
slice	O
better	O
fortune	O
	
	
	
Pole	O
vaulter	O
Brown	PERSON
have	O
hope	O
for	O
vote	O
confidence	O
from	O
the	O
british	O
selector	O
after	O
she	O
have	O
achieve	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
standard	O
but	O
the	O
call	O
never	O
come	O
	
the	O
summer	DATE
end	O
stalwart	O
Catherina	PERSON
McKiernan	PERSON
and	O
Dermot	PERSON
Donnelly	PERSON
hung	O
they	O
competitive	O
spike	O
McKiernan	PERSON
have	O
candidly	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
time	O
have	O
creep	O
	
she	O
after	O
several	O
injury	O
ravage	O
year	DURATION
Donnelly	PERSON
and	O
he	O
Annadale	LOCATION
strider	O
team	O
mate	O
later	O
suffer	O
tragedy	O
when	O
they	O
friend	O
and	O
clubman	O
Andy	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
be	O
find	O
dead	O
he	O
home	O
	
December	DATE
	
large	O
turnout	O
athletics	O
loving	O
folk	O
turn	O
out	Sports
west	O
Belfast	LOCATION
offer	O
they	O
respects	O
the	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
family	O
and	O
Andy	PERSON
many	O
friend	O
	
only	O
death	O
can	O
put	O
the	O
year	DURATION
athletics	O
happening	O
	
sharp	O
perspective	O
sprinter	O
Walker	PERSON
quit	O
athletics	O
Former	O
european	O
	
m	O
champion	O
Dougie	PERSON
Walker	PERSON
	
retire	O
from	O
athletics	O
after	O
series	O
six	NUMBER
operation	O
left	O
he	O
struggle	O
for	O
fitness	O
Walker	PERSON
have	O
hope	O
compete	O
the	O
New	O
year	DURATION
Sprint	O
which	O
stage	O
Musselburgh	LOCATION
racecourse	O
near	O
Edinburgh	LOCATION
Tuesday	DATE
and	O
Wednesday	DATE
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
Scot	PERSON
be	O
suspend	O
for	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
	
	
after	O
testing	O
positive	O
for	O
nandrolone	O
	
have	O
intend	O
race	O
but	O
	
run	O
like	O
goon	O
say	O
Walker	PERSON
	
tell	O
the	O
Herald	O
newspaper	O
	
	
not	O
great	O
shape	O
after	O
miss	O
about	O
month	DURATION
training	O
	
miss	O
big	O
chunk	O
speed	O
work	O
over	O
about	O
three	NUMBER
week	DURATION
and	O
then	O
another	O
week	DURATION
work	O
America	LOCATION
	
	
	
have	O
half	O
decent	O
mark	O
might	O
have	O
motivate	O
more	O
but	O
win	O
	
race	O
	
still	O
enjoy	O
training	O
but	O
feel	O
	
time	O
move	O
	
and	O
concentrate	O
	
career	O
Bekele	PERSON
set	O
sight	O
world	O
mark	O
Olympic	MISC
	
	
	
m	O
champion	O
Kenenisa	PERSON
Bekele	PERSON
determine	O
add	O
the	O
world	O
indoor	O
two	NUMBER
mile	O
record	O
February	DATE
Norwich	LOCATION
Union	O
Grand	O
Prix	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
will	O
again	O
chase	O
record	O
hold	O
he	O
compatriot	O
and	O
mentor	O
Haile	PERSON
Gebrselassie	PERSON
who	O
set	O
the	O
mark	O
the	O
same	O
meeting	O
	
	
	
	
	
still	O
hungry	O
	
much	O
	
can	O
this	O
sport	O
say	O
Bekele	PERSON
	
and	O
aim	O
for	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
mile	O
world	O
record	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
the	O
next	O
those	O
target	O
Gebrselassie	PERSON
current	DATE
record	O
stand	O
eight	NUMBER
minute	DURATION
	
	
seconds	DURATION
and	O
Bekele	PERSON
	
stranger	O
overhaul	O
world	O
mark	O
the	O
National	O
indoor	O
arena	O
the	O
ethiopian	O
break	O
the	O
world	O
indoor	O
	
	
m	O
record	O
he	O
debut	O
the	O
meeting	O
last	O
year	DURATION
compatriot	O
mulugeta	O
Wondimu	PERSON
Abiyote	PERSON
Abate	PERSON
and	O
Markos	PERSON
Geneti	PERSON
the	O
world	O
indoor	O
bronze	O
medallist	O
over	O
	
	
m	O
will	O
race	O
against	O
Bekele	PERSON
	
February	DATE
the	O
meet	O
have	O
already	O
attract	O
crop	O
Olympic	MISC
talent	O
Britain	LOCATION
	
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
champion	O
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
take	O
part	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
Swedish	MISC
heptathlon	O
gold	O
medallist	O
Carolina	PERSON
Kluft	O
will	O
contest	O
the	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
while	O
man	O
	
x	O
	
m	O
relay	O
gold	O
medallist	O
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
will	O
head	O
	
head	O
the	O
	
m	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
suspend	O
iaaf	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
have	O
be	O
suspend	O
after	O
fail	O
take	O
drug	O
test	O
before	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
Athletics	O
ruling	O
body	O
the	O
iaaf	O
say	O
explanation	O
from	O
the	O
pair	O
and	O
they	O
former	O
coach	O
	
why	O
they	O
miss	O
the	O
test	O
be	O
unacceptable	O
	
add	O
that	O
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
have	O
be	O
provisionally	O
suspend	O
pend	O
the	O
resolution	O
they	O
case	O
	
they	O
face	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
find	O
guilty	O
the	O
greek	O
Athletics	O
Federation	O
the	O
suspension	O
also	O
cover	O
the	O
athlete	O
controversial	O
coach	O
Christos	PERSON
Tzekos	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
the	O
	
	
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
champion	O
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
the	O
woman	O
	
	
m	O
silver	O
medallist	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Games	O
Sydney	LOCATION
also	O
face	O
criminal	O
hearing	O
Greece	LOCATION
over	O
the	O
miss	O
test	O
they	O
fail	O
appear	O
give	O
sample	O
Chicago	LOCATION
and	O
Tel	PERSON
Aviv	PERSON
shortly	O
before	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Games	O
and	O
again	O
Athens	LOCATION
	
August	DATE
the	O
eve	O
the	O
open	O
ceremony	O
greek	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
also	O
charge	O
they	O
with	O
fake	O
midnight	TIME
motorcycle	O
crash	O
which	O
lead	O
they	O
spending	O
four	NUMBER
day	DURATION
hospital	O
some	O
medical	O
staff	O
have	O
be	O
charge	O
with	O
write	O
false	O
medical	O
report	O
Wednesday	DATE
statement	O
say	O
the	O
greek	O
Federation	O
sega	O
would	O
convene	O
disciplinary	O
hearing	O
for	O
the	O
trio	O
determine	O
whether	O
there	O
have	O
be	O
doping	O
violation	O
	
there	O
will	O
	
final	O
right	O
appeal	O
from	O
the	O
decision	O
the	O
greek	O
Federation	O
the	O
Court	O
arbitration	O
for	O
Sport	O
the	O
iaaf	O
say	O
Tzekos	PERSON
insist	O
and	O
the	O
runner	O
have	O
nothing	O
hide	O
	
the	O
iaaf	O
decision	O
means	O
nothing	O
	
say	O
	
	
	
present	DATE
all	O
we	O
argument	O
sega	O
	
	
innocent	O
Athens	LOCATION
memory	O
soar	O
above	O
low	O
well	O
	
goodbye	O
another	O
Olympic	MISC
year	DURATION
and	O
usual	O
there	O
be	O
plenty	O
high	O
and	O
low	O
Athens	LOCATION
obviously	O
there	O
	
get	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
differ	O
fortune	O
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
and	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
but	O
want	O
remind	O
you	O
	
few	O
more	O
event	O
that	O
make	O
	
	
another	O
year	DURATION
remember	O
	
forget	O
for	O
athletics	O
	
	
one	NUMBER
	
favourite	O
Olympic	MISC
moment	O
be	O
Kelly	PERSON
success	O
the	O
	
m	O
win	O
that	O
race	O
be	O
the	O
key	O
she	O
success	O
because	O
she	O
win	O
that	O
then	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
would	O
	
bit	O
	
formality	O
Kelly	PERSON
have	O
be	O
full	O
	
should	O
	
shouldn	O
	
	
thought	O
about	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
double	O
Athens	LOCATION
	
thought	O
why	O
wouldn	O
you	O
the	O
	
m	O
	
you	O
best	O
event	O
be	O
such	O
good	O
fun	O
commentate	O
she	O
	
	
m	O
and	O
be	O
nice	O
	
able	O
	
part	O
she	O
Athens	LOCATION
story	O
	
	
the	O
victory	O
for	O
the	O
british	O
man	O
	
x	O
	
m	O
relay	O
team	O
be	O
bit	O
	
surprise	O
but	O
great	O
climax	O
the	O
Games	O
	
think	O
the	O
four	NUMBER
they	O
Jason	PERSON
gardener	O
Darren	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
Marlon	PERSON
devonish	O
and	O
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
know	O
deep	O
down	O
that	O
be	O
they	O
best	O
chance	O
	
medal	O
the	O
lad	O
have	O
run	O
poorly	O
the	O
individual	O
sprint	O
maybe	O
they	O
do	O
lift	O
they	O
game	O
when	O
they	O
know	O
something	O
be	O
really	O
stake	O
	
	
Hicham	PERSON
Guerrouj	PERSON
Olympic	MISC
double	O
	
much	O
bigger	O
achievement	O
than	O
Kelly	PERSON
	
global	O
scale	O
	
be	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
man	O
since	O
for	O
	
year	DURATION
win	O
both	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
and	O
	
	
m	O
title	O
	
soon	O
	
have	O
add	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
crown	O
and	O
have	O
finish	O
commentate	O
jump	Sports
	
run	O
down	O
the	O
stair	O
push	O
everyone	O
out	Sports
the	O
way	O
and	O
just	O
give	O
he	O
big	O
hug	O
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
few	O
African	MISC
runner	O
who	O
have	O
embrace	O
the	O
tradition	O
the	O
mile	O
and	O
love	O
hear	O
all	O
the	O
Roger	PERSON
Bannister	PERSON
story	O
Hicham	PERSON
someone	O
enjoy	O
have	O
bit	O
time	O
with	O
even	O
though	O
french	O
and	O
he	O
English	MISC
be	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
	
	
what	O
happen	O
Paula	PERSON
Athens	LOCATION
this	O
year	DURATION
the	O
obvious	O
low	O
	
personal	O
level	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
expectation	O
the	O
nation	O
well	O
there	O
be	O
set	O
circumstance	O
around	O
Athens	LOCATION
that	O
conspire	O
produce	O
very	O
dramatic	O
end	O
which	O
think	O
have	O
be	O
greatly	O
misunderstand	O
drop	O
out	Sports
the	O
marathon	O
be	O
the	O
right	O
thing	O
	
but	O
start	O
the	O
	
	
	
m	O
five	NUMBER
day	DURATION
later	O
be	O
not	O
wise	O
that	O
be	O
she	O
heart	O
and	O
not	O
she	O
head	O
react	O
Paula	PERSON
have	O
lot	O
little	O
thing	O
go	O
wrong	O
she	O
preparation	O
and	O
the	O
day	DURATION
thing	O
like	O
niggle	O
injury	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
	
all	O
she	O
run	O
session	O
and	O
feeling	O
the	O
pressure	O
the	O
race	O
loom	O
ahead	O
she	O
	
think	O
she	O
come	O
the	O
start	O
line	O
Athens	LOCATION
physically	O
and	O
emotionally	O
drain	O
and	O
even	O
the	O
smallest	O
thing	O
doesn	O
feel	O
right	O
when	O
you	O
be	O
prepare	O
race	O
marathon	O
	
mile	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
will	O
hit	O
you	O
like	O
brick	O
wall	O
the	O
positive	O
thing	O
take	O
from	O
Paula	PERSON
Olympics	MISC
that	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
learn	O
lot	O
from	O
and	O
will	O
lot	O
people	O
include	O
	
	
	
purely	O
	
race	O
Paula	PERSON
victory	O
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
Marathon	O
have	O
	
down	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
most	O
thrilling	O
	
be	O
nip	O
and	O
tuck	O
between	O
she	O
and	O
Kenya	LOCATION
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
and	O
you	O
don	O
usually	O
get	O
that	O
kind	O
excitement	O
marathon	O
	
be	O
also	O
real	O
delight	O
for	O
all	O
athletics	O
fan	O
because	O
use	O
one	NUMBER
	
favourite	O
word	O
Paula	PERSON
show	O
real	O
bouncebackability	O
	
and	O
be	O
bit	O
	
rarity	O
for	O
too	O
because	O
genuinely	O
do	O
not	O
have	O
inkling	O
how	O
the	O
race	O
be	O
go	O
pan	O
out	Sports
	
	
Kelly	PERSON
and	O
the	O
x	O
	
m	O
boy	O
victory	O
paper	O
over	O
the	O
crack	O
the	O
general	O
performance	O
the	O
british	O
team	O
	
should	O
concerned	O
that	O
	
not	O
produce	O
enough	O
people	O
who	O
be	O
capable	O
reach	O
final	O
senior	O
level	O
the	O
only	O
individual	O
man	O
finalist	O
the	O
track	O
be	O
Michael	PERSON
East	O
the	O
	
	
m	O
	
begin	O
look	O
down	O
and	O
wonder	O
where	O
be	O
the	O
new	O
breed	O
and	O
that	O
where	O
thing	O
begin	O
look	O
even	O
gloomier	O
for	O
british	O
athletics	O
	
do	O
not	O
win	O
any	O
medal	O
the	O
world	O
junior	O
championship	O
Italy	LOCATION
Dani	PERSON
Barnes	PERSON
come	O
fourth	ORDINAL
the	O
	
	
m	O
and	O
she	O
be	O
the	O
highest	O
finisher	O
for	O
Team	O
	
the	O
thing	O
	
don	O
have	O
athlete	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
final	O
junior	O
level	O
then	O
really	O
doesn	O
look	O
good	O
for	O
the	O
Beijing	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
and	O
beyond	O
	
	
	
tell	O
you	O
what	O
really	O
enjoy	O
this	O
year	DURATION
Benita	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
win	O
the	O
world	O
cross	O
country	O
championship	O
back	O
March	DATE
	
the	O
absence	O
Paula	PERSON
tend	O
think	O
the	O
event	O
something	O
	
African	MISC
preserve	O
	
have	O
australian	O
come	O
and	O
deliver	O
such	O
surprise	O
be	O
something	O
special	O
	
	
	
	
honest	O
	
get	O
bore	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
drug	O
scandal	O
especially	O
balco	O
	
just	O
wish	O
the	O
whole	O
thing	O
would	O
come	O
	
head	O
	
can	O
move	O
	
have	O
say	O
that	O
	
always	O
pleased	O
when	O
drug	O
cheat	O
be	O
catch	Sports
because	O
show	O
the	O
sport	O
standing	O
	
and	O
not	O
turn	O
blind	O
eye	O
anymore	O
and	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
positive	O
thing	O
come	O
out	Sports
balco	O
people	O
be	O
start	O
blow	O
the	O
whistle	O
	
need	O
more	O
people	O
come	O
forward	O
and	O
help	O
the	O
authority	O
kick	O
out	Sports
the	O
cheat	O
	
regard	O
the	O
case	O
against	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
well	O
suspicion	O
have	O
be	O
hang	O
over	O
Kenteris	PERSON
for	O
while	O
the	O
bottom	O
line	O
	
can not	O O
keep	O
let	O
drug	O
damage	O
the	O
sport	O
because	O
	
then	O
stop	O
everyone	O
enjoy	O
Collins	PERSON
ban	O
landmark	O
case	O
sprinter	O
Michelle	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
have	O
receive	O
eight	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
for	O
doping	O
offence	O
after	O
hearing	O
the	O
North	O
American	MISC
Court	O
arbitration	O
for	O
Sport	O
ca	O
	
America	LOCATION
former	O
world	O
indoor	O
	
m	O
champion	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
athlete	O
	
suspend	O
without	O
positive	O
drug	O
test	O
	
admission	O
drug	O
use	O
Collins	PERSON
ban	O
	
result	O
she	O
connection	O
the	O
federal	O
inquiry	O
into	O
the	O
balco	O
doping	O
scandal	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
be	O
find	O
guilty	O
use	O
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
the	O
anti	O
dope	O
Agency	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
decide	O
press	O
charge	O
against	O
Collins	PERSON
the	O
summer	DATE
the	O
sprinter	O
have	O
consistently	O
protest	O
she	O
innocence	O
but	O
the	O
ca	O
have	O
uphold	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
finding	O
	
the	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
have	O
prove	O
beyond	O
reasonable	O
doubt	O
that	O
Collins	PERSON
take	O
epo	O
the	O
testosterone	O
epitestosterone	O
cream	O
and	O
thg	O
say	O
ca	O
statement	O
	
Collins	PERSON
use	O
these	O
substance	O
enhance	O
she	O
performance	O
and	O
elude	O
the	O
drug	O
testing	O
that	O
be	O
available	O
the	O
time	O
	
far	O
total	O
	
athlete	O
have	O
be	O
sanction	O
for	O
violation	O
involve	O
drug	O
associate	O
with	O
the	O
balco	O
doping	O
scandal	O
World	O
record	O
holder	O
Tim	PERSON
Montgomery	PERSON
also	O
face	O
lifetime	O
ban	O
after	O
be	O
charge	O
the	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
he	O
hearing	O
before	O
the	O
CSA	O
have	O
be	O
reschedule	O
for	O
June	DATE
next	O
year	DURATION
drug	O
enforcement	O
chief	O
the	O
have	O
vow	O
crack	O
down	O
cheat	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
chief	O
executive	O
officer	O
Terry	PERSON
Madden	PERSON
say	O
the	O
action	O
take	O
against	O
Collins	PERSON
be	O
further	O
proof	O
that	O
	
the	O
ca	O
panel	O
decision	O
confirm	O
that	O
those	O
who	O
violate	O
the	O
rule	O
will	O
sanction	O
part	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
ongoing	O
effort	O
protect	O
the	O
rights	O
the	O
overwhelming	O
majority	O
	
athlete	O
that	O
compete	O
drug	O
free	O
say	O
Madden	PERSON
the	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
have	O
build	O
its	O
case	O
verbal	O
evidence	O
give	O
the	O
federal	O
investigation	O
into	O
balco	O
rather	O
than	O
test	O
result	O
the	O
San	O
Francisco	PERSON
base	O
balco	O
laboratory	O
face	O
steroid	O
distribution	O
and	O
money	O
laundering	O
charge	O
the	O
trial	O
expect	O
open	O
next	O
March	DATE
Jones	PERSON
doping	O
probe	O
begin	O
	
investigation	O
into	O
doping	O
claim	O
against	O
Marion	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
have	O
be	O
open	O
the	O
International	O
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
IOC	ORGANIZATION
president	O
Jacques	PERSON
Rogge	PERSON
have	O
set	O
	
disciplinary	O
body	O
look	O
into	O
claim	O
Victor	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
balco	O
Laboratories	O
Jones	PERSON
who	O
say	O
she	O
innocent	O
could	O
lose	O
all	O
she	O
Olympic	MISC
medal	O
after	O
Conte	PERSON
say	O
give	O
she	O
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
before	O
the	O
Sydney	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
but	O
Rogge	PERSON
say	O
be	O
too	O
early	O
speculate	O
about	O
that	O
hope	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
truth	O
will	O
emerge	O
	
any	O
decision	O
the	O
medal	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
IOC	ORGANIZATION
executive	O
board	O
and	O
could	O
hinge	O
interpretation	O
	
rule	O
state	O
that	O
Olympic	MISC
decision	O
can	O
only	O
challenge	O
within	O
three	NUMBER
year	DURATION
the	O
Games	O
close	O
the	O
Sydney	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
end	O
more	O
than	O
four	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ago	O
but	O
World	O
anti	O
dope	O
Agency	O
chief	O
Dick	PERSON
pound	O
say	O
the	O
rule	O
may	O
not	O
apply	O
because	O
the	O
allegation	O
be	O
only	O
come	O
out	Sports
now	DATE
	
will	O
find	O
way	O
deal	O
with	O
that	O
pound	O
say	O
	
statement	O
release	O
through	O
she	O
attorney	O
Rich	O
Nichols	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
repeat	O
she	O
innocence	O
and	O
vow	O
she	O
would	O
clear	O
	
Victor	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
allegation	O
be	O
not	O
true	O
and	O
the	O
truth	O
will	O
reveal	O
for	O
the	O
world	O
see	O
the	O
legal	O
process	O
move	O
forward	O
she	O
say	O
	
Conte	PERSON
someone	O
who	O
under	O
federal	O
indictment	O
and	O
have	O
record	O
issue	O
contradictory	O
inconsistent	O
statement	O
Johnson	PERSON
accuse	O
british	O
sprinter	O
Former	O
Olympic	MISC
champion	O
Michael	PERSON
Johnson	PERSON
have	O
accuse	O
Britain	LOCATION
top	O
sprinter	O
lack	O
pride	O
and	O
ambition	O
	
	
the	O
moment	O
the	O
biggest	O
factor	O
the	O
mind	O
british	O
sprinter	O
	
number	O
one	NUMBER
Britain	LOCATION
the	O
world	O
	
m	O
and	O
	
m	O
record	O
holder	O
tell	O
five	NUMBER
Live	O
	
Athletics	O
the	O
moment	O
all	O
about	O
international	O
competition	O
and	O
they	O
need	O
show	O
little	O
more	O
pride	O
however	O
Linford	PERSON
Christie	PERSON
counter	O
	
	
easy	O
criticise	O
when	O
you	O
haven	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
system	O
here	O
Johnson	PERSON
be	O
involve	O
	
verbal	O
spat	O
with	O
Britain	LOCATION
Darren	PERSON
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
earlier	O
this	O
year	DURATION
the	O
American	MISC
have	O
cast	O
doubt	O
Campbell	ORGANIZATION
claim	O
have	O
tear	O
hamstring	O
the	O
wake	O
he	O
failure	O
reach	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
and	O
	
m	O
final	O
and	O
the	O
American	MISC
remains	O
highly	O
critical	O
aspect	O
british	O
sprint	O
	
the	O
only	O
time	O
you	O
see	O
british	O
sprinter	O
get	O
upset	O
rile	O
when	O
there	O
	
debate	O
	
which	O
one	NUMBER
better	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
	
claim	O
	
athlete	O
here	O
have	O
compete	O
more	O
outside	O
the	O
	
they	O
focus	O
have	O
	
be	O
the	O
best	O
the	O
world	O
and	O
not	O
just	O
be	O
the	O
top	O
british	O
sprinter	O
speak	O
	
elite	O
coach	O
conference	O
Birmingham	LOCATION
Johnson	PERSON
also	O
argue	O
that	O
although	O
there	O
have	O
be	O
more	O
investment	O
the	O
sport	O
Britain	LOCATION
have	O
not	O
necessarily	O
reap	O
the	O
reward	O
	
you	O
can	O
fix	O
everything	O
with	O
money	O
	
admit	O
	
you	O
contrast	O
the	O
situation	O
here	O
that	O
some	O
athlete	O
who	O
have	O
funding	O
	
those	O
who	O
aren	O
fund	O
might	O
hungrier	O
and	O
more	O
motivate	O
because	O
they	O
road	O
success	O
	
lot	O
more	O
difficult	O
and	O
challenge	O
	
when	O
they	O
get	O
the	O
top	O
they	O
be	O
more	O
appreciative	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
prove	O
doubter	O
wrong	O
this	O
win	O
	
down	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
greatest	O
marathon	O
Paula	PERSON
career	O
but	O
	
test	O
character	O
be	O
the	O
toughest	O
race	O
she	O
ever	O
take	O
part	O
	
	
win	O
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
marathon	O
doesn	O
make	O
for	O
the	O
disappointment	O
Athens	LOCATION
any	O
shape	O
form	O
but	O
will	O
offer	O
hope	O
and	O
reassurance	O
for	O
next	O
year	DURATION
	
Paula	PERSON
last	O
experience	O
the	O
year	DURATION
have	O
be	O
Athens	LOCATION
would	O
have	O
be	O
very	O
difficult	O
look	O
forward	O
with	O
any	O
optimism	O
she	O
can	O
now	DATE
draw	O
line	O
under	O
this	O
year	DURATION
and	O
make	O
plan	O
about	O
she	O
future	DATE
even	O
she	O
lose	O
this	O
race	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
be	O
lot	O
positive	O
take	O
out	Sports
	
	
she	O
know	O
she	O
can	O
dig	O
deep	O
she	O
need	O
	
	
be	O
strong	O
field	O
with	O
number	O
the	O
girl	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
race	O
with	O
expectation	O
win	O
and	O
although	O
two	NUMBER
hour	DURATION
	
minute	DURATION
wasn	O
one	NUMBER
Paula	PERSON
best	O
time	O
wasn	O
far	O
off	O
the	O
record	O
	
difficult	O
course	O
	
be	O
speak	O
Paula	PERSON
the	O
lead	O
	
this	O
race	O
and	O
she	O
say	O
that	O
many	O
way	O
she	O
be	O
face	O
	
win	O
situation	O
she	O
thought	O
that	O
she	O
win	O
people	O
would	O
say	O
why	O
couldn	O
she	O
that	O
Athens	LOCATION
and	O
she	O
lose	O
people	O
would	O
say	O
she	O
career	O
be	O
over	O
and	O
lot	O
people	O
be	O
wonder	O
what	O
would	O
happen	O
Paula	PERSON
be	O
force	O
drop	O
out	Sports
this	O
race	O
she	O
do	O
the	O
marathon	O
and	O
	
	
	
m	O
Athens	LOCATION
but	O
that	O
be	O
never	O
the	O
card	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
be	O
beat	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
keep	O
run	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
be	O
force	O
pull	O
out	Sports
Athens	LOCATION
the	O
niggle	O
injury	O
she	O
lack	O
energy	O
and	O
the	O
oppressive	O
condition	O
weren	O
	
play	O
here	O
the	O
only	O
question	O
be	O
what	O
position	O
she	O
could	O
finish	O
	
most	O
important	O
all	O
despite	O
all	O
the	O
hype	O
the	O
media	O
ahead	O
this	O
race	O
there	O
be	O
never	O
doubt	O
Paula	PERSON
mind	O
	
she	O
wasn	O
confident	O
she	O
wouldn	O
have	O
run	O
after	O
all	O
you	O
the	O
best	O
the	O
world	O
	
event	O
you	O
always	O
have	O
expectation	O
win	O
now	DATE
Paula	PERSON
will	O
take	O
part	O
the	O
Run	O
London	LOCATION
	
km	O
race	O
London	LOCATION
the	O
end	O
the	O
year	DURATION
have	O
well	O
earn	O
rest	O
over	O
Christmas	DATE
and	O
into	O
next	O
year	DURATION
with	O
lot	O
optimism	O
Jones	PERSON
medal	O
must	O
	
guilty	O
World	O
anti	O
dope	O
Agency	O
WADA	PERSON
chief	O
Dick	PERSON
pound	O
say	O
Marion	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
should	O
strip	O
all	O
she	O
medal	O
find	O
guilty	O
take	O
ban	O
substance	O
Victor	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
balco	O
Laboratories	O
claim	O
the	O
American	MISC
sprinter	O
regularly	O
use	O
drug	O
enhance	O
she	O
performance	O
	
she	O
find	O
guilty	O
she	O
should	O
strip	O
all	O
she	O
medal	O
and	O
ban	O
for	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
say	O
pound	O
ask	O
there	O
be	O
timescale	O
	
what	O
medal	O
could	O
take	O
pound	O
say	O
that	O
not	O
issue	O
all	O
however	O
under	O
International	O
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
IOC	ORGANIZATION
rule	O
athlete	O
can	O
only	O
strip	O
they	O
medal	O
catch	Sports
within	O
three	NUMBER
year	DURATION
the	O
event	O
Jones	PERSON
who	O
win	O
five	NUMBER
medal	O
the	O
	
	
Olympics	MISC
deny	O
use	O
drug	O
and	O
say	O
she	O
will	O
take	O
legal	O
action	O
over	O
Conte	PERSON
allegation	O
balco	O
Laboratories	O
the	O
firm	O
the	O
centre	O
	
wide	O
reach	O
investigation	O
into	O
doping	O
the	O
	
pound	O
continue	O
	
she	O
have	O
indeed	O
take	O
drug	O
	
go	O
	
big	O
disappointment	O
for	O
lot	O
people	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
tackle	O
marathon	O
task	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
face	O
arguably	O
the	O
biggest	O
test	O
she	O
career	O
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
City	O
Marathon	O
Sunday	DATE
back	O
under	O
the	O
spotlight	O
public	O
scrutiny	O
she	O
will	O
attempt	O
erase	O
the	O
double	O
disappointment	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
where	O
she	O
fail	O
finish	O
the	O
marathon	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
	
	
	
m	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
examine	O
the	O
challenge	O
face	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
ahead	O
the	O
big	O
race	O
	
the	O
ability	O
run	O
gruelle	O
	
	
mile	O
rely	O
largely	O
upon	O
athlete	O
belief	O
that	O
they	O
can	O
	
	
every	O
runner	O
will	O
hit	O
the	O
wall	O
some	O
stage	O
and	O
see	O
write	O
	
	
be	O
you	O
strong	O
enough	O
finish	O
the	O
question	O
could	O
hit	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
hard	O
after	O
she	O
be	O
unable	O
complete	O
she	O
last	O
two	NUMBER
race	O
high	O
profile	O
and	O
emotional	O
circumstance	O
Sports	O
psychologist	O
Hugh	PERSON
Richards	PERSON
say	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
must	O
draw	O
she	O
past	DATE
achievement	O
conquer	O
potential	O
crisis	O
confidence	O
	
there	O
	
old	O
adage	O
get	O
straight	O
back	O
the	O
horse	O
that	O
throw	O
you	O
	
Richards	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
	
Paula	PERSON
have	O
get	O
all	O
those	O
great	O
run	O
she	O
history	O
well	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
upset	O
Athens	LOCATION
	
she	O
must	O
not	O
lose	O
faith	O
what	O
have	O
already	O
be	O
prove	O
	
very	O
effective	O
strategy	O
for	O
distance	O
run	O
	
she	O
be	O
change	O
she	O
preparation	O
and	O
tactic	O
that	O
would	O
madness	O
	
she	O
want	O
start	O
rebuild	O
she	O
confidence	O
through	O
performance	O
accomplishment	O
for	O
much	O
the	O
watch	O
media	O
and	O
public	O
there	O
can	O
only	O
two	NUMBER
possible	O
outcome	O
New	O
York	PERSON
win	O
lose	O
	
Radcliffe	PERSON
cross	O
the	O
line	O
first	ORDINAL
she	O
will	O
have	O
prove	O
she	O
critic	O
wrong	O
but	O
she	O
fail	O
triumph	O
she	O
risk	O
be	O
label	O
have	O
be	O
and	O
she	O
profile	O
will	O
suffer	O
and	O
for	O
any	O
athlete	O
that	O
can	O
have	O
repercussion	O
term	O
sponsorship	O
appearance	O
fee	O
well	O
further	O
self	O
esteem	O
issue	O
	
athlete	O
need	O
try	O
and	O
stay	O
focus	O
they	O
internal	O
control	O
and	O
ignore	O
external	O
question	O
explain	O
Richards	PERSON
who	O
have	O
work	O
with	O
past	DATE
olympian	O
	
she	O
must	O
not	O
get	O
catch	Sports
	
someone	O
else	O
agenda	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
best	O
friend	O
and	O
fellow	O
distance	O
runner	O
Liz	PERSON
yell	O
reveal	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
already	O
aware	O
she	O
will	O
expose	O
herself	O
more	O
public	O
scrutiny	O
New	O
York	PERSON
	
she	O
just	O
thought	O
well	O
they	O
can	O
think	O
any	O
worse	O
	
now	DATE
	
yell	O
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
	
she	O
just	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
want	O
	
and	O
not	O
think	O
about	O
the	O
consequence	O
	
	
Radcliffe	PERSON
describe	O
she	O
decision	O
enter	O
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
marathon	O
	
impulsive	O
but	O
she	O
certain	O
have	O
tick	O
list	O
personal	O
goal	O
she	O
aim	O
could	O
	
simple	O
complete	O
race	O
and	O
make	O
sure	O
she	O
still	O
enjoy	O
run	O
but	O
Richards	PERSON
say	O
she	O
must	O
avoid	O
more	O
emotional	O
target	O
such	O
redemption	O
	
you	O
can	O
change	O
history	O
warn	O
Richards	PERSON
	
only	O
one	NUMBER
person	O
can	O
win	O
the	O
marathon	O
but	O
lot	O
people	O
can	O
successful	O
	
Paula	PERSON
have	O
figure	O
out	Sports
what	O
sort	O
thing	O
will	O
she	O
feel	O
satisfied	O
achieve	O
the	O
end	O
the	O
race	O
the	O
course	O
from	O
Staten	LOCATION
island	O
Central	O
Park	O
renown	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
toughest	O
the	O
world	O
	
also	O
not	O
the	O
kind	O
fast	O
course	O
that	O
tend	O
suit	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
better	O
with	O
the	O
undulate	O
finish	O
through	O
the	O
park	O
testing	O
the	O
leg	O
final	O
reserve	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
have	O
never	O
race	O
there	O
before	O
and	O
will	O
enter	O
the	O
unknown	O
just	O
	
day	DURATION
after	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
marathon	O
	
	
suggest	O
after	O
major	O
marathon	O
you	O
take	O
full	O
month	DURATION
off	O
and	O
start	O
building	O
again	O
say	O
yell	O
herself	O
marathon	O
runner	O
	
but	O
that	O
only	O
for	O
long	Sports
term	O
health	O
and	O
fitness	O
	
when	O
you	O
finish	O
marathon	O
you	O
be	O
still	O
very	O
fit	O
and	O
can	O
recover	O
quickly	O
	
physically	O
	
possible	O
for	O
Paula	PERSON
Richards	PERSON
also	O
point	O
out	Sports
condition	O
New	O
York	PERSON
will	O
more	O
conducive	O
	
strong	O
physical	O
display	O
from	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
	
the	O
heat	O
stress	O
be	O
the	O
primary	O
factor	O
that	O
trip	O
she	O
	
Athens	LOCATION
	
say	O
	
and	O
that	O
just	O
isn	O
go	O
	
there	O
New	O
York	PERSON
that	O
be	O
take	O
out	Sports
the	O
equation	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
concede	O
she	O
will	O
probably	O
learn	O
lot	O
from	O
she	O
bad	O
experience	O
Athens	LOCATION
time	O
and	O
Richards	PERSON
and	O
yell	O
agree	O
she	O
could	O
turn	O
the	O
trauma	O
she	O
advantage	O
start	O
New	O
York	PERSON
	
how	O
you	O
respond	O
adversity	O
what	O
mark	O
you	O
out	Sports
elite	O
not	O
argue	O
Richards	PERSON
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
challenge	O
massive	O
set	O
back	O
how	O
you	O
turn	O
they	O
into	O
opportunity	O
and	O
yell	O
say	O
	
think	O
this	O
will	O
probably	O
make	O
Paula	PERSON
	
think	O
will	O
drive	Sports
she	O
and	O
she	O
come	O
out	Sports
	
better	O
athlete	O
Gatlin	PERSON
and	O
Hayes	PERSON
win	O
Owen	PERSON
award	O
American	MISC
Olympic	MISC
star	O
Justin	PERSON
Gatlin	PERSON
and	O
Joanna	PERSON
Hayes	PERSON
have	O
be	O
name	O
the	O
winner	O
the	O
	
	
Jesse	PERSON
Owens	PERSON
award	O
USA	LOCATION
Track	O
field	O
	
usatf	O
top	O
honour	O
Gatlin	PERSON
	
win	O
the	O
closest	O
	
m	O
final	O
Games	O
history	O
with	O
career	O
best	O
time	O
	
	
seconds	DURATION
Athens	LOCATION
	
also	O
win	O
bronze	O
the	O
	
m	O
and	O
silver	O
the	O
x	O
	
m	O
relay	O
become	O
the	O
only	O
male	O
athlete	O
win	O
three	NUMBER
athletics	O
medal	O
this	O
summer	DATE
Hayes	PERSON
	
set	O
Olympic	MISC
record	O
	
	
	
win	O
the	O
	
m	O
hurdle	O
establish	O
	
	
	
the	O
Jesse	PERSON
Owens	PERSON
award	O
name	O
honour	O
the	O
late	O
Olympic	MISC
great	O
who	O
win	O
four	NUMBER
gold	O
medal	O
the	O
	
	
Berlin	LOCATION
Games	O
be	O
present	DATE
annually	SET
the	O
outstanding	O
male	O
and	O
female	O
track	O
and	O
field	O
performer	O
the	O
	
	
award	O
will	O
present	DATE
	
December	DATE
conjunction	O
with	O
the	O
usatf	O
annual	SET
meeting	O
Portland	LOCATION
	
	
such	O
great	O
honour	O
win	O
the	O
Jesse	PERSON
Owens	PERSON
award	O
say	O
Gatlin	PERSON
	
	
one	NUMBER
the	O
biggest	O
honour	O
track	O
and	O
field	O
and	O
	
great	O
end	O
	
great	O
year	DURATION
	
Hayes	PERSON
say	O
know	O
some	O
the	O
great	O
people	O
who	O
have	O
win	O
this	O
award	O
before	O
and	O
know	O
what	O
represent	O
feel	O
sense	O
accomplishment	O
and	O
pride	O
which	O
let	O
know	O
that	O
everything	O
that	O
have	O
work	O
for	O
and	O
always	O
will	O
worth	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
enjoy	O
win	O
comeback	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
make	O
triumphant	O
return	O
competitive	O
run	O
with	O
victory	O
the	O
New	O
York	PERSON
Marathon	O
the	O
briton	O
run	O
for	O
the	O
first	ORDINAL
time	O
since	O
drop	O
out	Sports
the	O
Olympic	MISC
marathon	O
and	O
	
	
	
m	O
hold	O
off	O
kenyan	O
Susan	PERSON
Chepkemei	PERSON
	
thrilling	O
finish	O
the	O
pair	O
be	O
lock	O
together	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
few	O
mile	O
before	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
finally	O
sprint	O
clear	O
win	O
two	NUMBER
hour	DURATION
	
minute	DURATION
and	O
	
seconds	DURATION
	
	
	
good	O
way	O
end	O
the	O
year	DURATION
she	O
say	O
	
	
ready	O
for	O
good	O
rest	O
now	DATE
Radcliffe	PERSON
decide	O
only	O
recently	DATE
run	O
the	O
race	O
and	O
many	O
have	O
doubt	O
whether	O
she	O
have	O
sufficiently	O
recover	O
from	O
she	O
Olympic	MISC
ordeal	O
just	O
	
week	DURATION
ago	O
but	O
the	O
world	O
record	O
holder	O
be	O
prominent	O
the	O
head	O
the	O
field	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
race	O
she	O
rival	O
slowly	O
drop	O
off	O
the	O
pace	O
just	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
and	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
be	O
left	O
contention	O
the	O
race	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
final	O
few	O
mile	O
the	O
kenyan	O
put	O
several	O
burst	O
speed	O
throw	O
off	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
but	O
the	O
briton	O
manage	O
hang	O
	
both	O
runner	O
look	O
	
suffer	O
they	O
reach	O
the	O
final	O
mile	O
Central	O
Park	O
but	O
be	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
who	O
manage	O
dredge	O
	
final	O
sprint	O
see	O
off	O
Chepkemei	PERSON
the	O
closest	O
finish	O
the	O
race	O
history	O
and	O
the	O
process	O
make	O
huge	O
step	O
erase	O
the	O
disappointment	O
she	O
suffer	O
Athens	LOCATION
Collins	PERSON
name	O
Athletics	O
chief	O
	
Athletics	O
have	O
end	O
its	O
search	O
for	O
new	O
performance	O
director	O
appoint	O
psychologist	O
Dave	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
who	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
british	O
team	O
the	O
	
	
and	O
	
	
Olympics	MISC
take	O
over	O
from	O
Max	PERSON
Jones	PERSON
six	NUMBER
candidate	O
be	O
interview	O
for	O
the	O
job	O
include	O
Denise	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
coach	O
Charles	PERSON
van	O
commenee	O
and	O
former	O
british	O
triple	O
jumper	O
Keith	PERSON
Connor	PERSON
	
	
search	O
long	Sports
and	O
hard	O
ensure	O
have	O
find	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
say	O
UKA	O
chief	O
executive	O
David	PERSON
Moorcroft	PERSON
	
have	O
thoroughly	O
test	O
the	O
candidate	O
	
believe	O
David	PERSON
will	O
make	O
great	O
leader	O
and	O
have	O
great	O
faith	O
what	O
will	O
achieve	O
Collins	PERSON
say	O
	
	
great	O
challenge	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
few	O
month	DURATION
will	O
spend	O
time	O
listen	O
those	O
who	O
already	O
make	O
significant	O
contribution	O
athletics	O
and	O
other	O
elite	O
sport	O
the	O
	
Collins	PERSON
who	O
have	O
work	O
with	O
javelin	O
thrower	O
Steve	PERSON
backley	O
the	O
past	DATE
start	O
he	O
career	O
	
Royal	O
Marine	O
before	O
become	O
	
teacher	O
	
currently	DATE
professor	O
physical	O
education	O
and	O
sport	O
performance	O
Edinburgh	LOCATION
University	O
where	O
help	O
competitor	O
across	O
many	O
sport	O
include	O
rugby	O
athletics	O
judo	O
and	O
football	O
	
have	O
specialise	O
help	O
competitor	O
fulfil	O
they	O
potential	O
through	O
psychology	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
Great	O
Britain	LOCATION
woman	O
curl	O
team	O
who	O
win	O
gold	O
the	O
	
	
Winter	DATE
Olympics	MISC
Mark	PERSON
Lewis	PERSON
Francis	PERSON
seek	O
Collins	PERSON
advice	O
Athens	LOCATION
when	O
be	O
look	O
for	O
inspiration	O
before	O
run	O
the	O
final	O
leg	O
Britain	LOCATION
surprise	O
triumph	O
the	O
x	O
	
m	O
relay	O
Collins	PERSON
have	O
play	O
rugby	O
regional	O
level	O
be	O
captain	O
the	O
Great	O
Britain	LOCATION
American	MISC
football	O
team	O
and	O
compete	O
national	O
level	O
judo	O
and	O
karate	O
	
arrive	O
with	O
british	O
athletics	O
	
crossroads	O
despite	O
Kelly	PERSON
Holmes	PERSON
golden	O
double	O
and	O
the	O
success	O
the	O
sprint	O
relay	O
squad	O
the	O
team	O
fail	O
live	O
	
expectation	O
Athens	LOCATION
many	O
older	O
competitor	O
have	O
retire	O
be	O
come	O
the	O
end	O
they	O
career	O
and	O
Britain	LOCATION
fail	O
win	O
single	O
medal	O
the	O
world	O
junior	O
championship	O
Italy	LOCATION
this	O
year	DURATION
Collins	PERSON
will	O
not	O
have	O
day	DURATION
	
day	DURATION
coaching	O
contact	O
with	O
the	O
athlete	O
but	O
will	O
expect	O
make	O
change	O
the	O
system	O
and	O
coaching	O
set	O
	
order	O
secure	O
medal	O
the	O
Beijing	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
	
	
	
the	O
appointment	O
	
new	O
performance	O
director	O
be	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
main	O
recommendation	O
Sir	O
Andrew	PERSON
Foster	O
review	O
the	O
sport	O
which	O
be	O
publish	O
May	DATE
	
be	O
commission	O
	
Sport	O
and	O
Sport	O
England	LOCATION
which	O
want	O
Athletics	O
justify	O
funding	O
more	O
than	O
#	O
m	O
from	O
the	O
government	O
follow	O
the	O
failure	O
hang	O
	
the	O
	
	
World	O
championship	O
which	O
be	O
now	DATE
be	O
hold	O
Helsinki	LOCATION
Van	PERSON
commenee	O
drop	O
out	Sports
the	O
selection	O
process	O
take	O
the	O
same	O
role	O
with	O
the	O
Dutch	MISC
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
while	O
Connor	PERSON
application	O
be	O
reject	O
after	O
arduous	O
interview	O
process	O
Foster	O
however	O
declare	O
himself	O
satisfied	O
with	O
how	O
the	O
appointment	O
be	O
make	O
	
the	O
appointment	O
David	PERSON
Collins	PERSON
with	O
he	O
strong	O
mix	O
leadership	O
skill	O
and	O
managerial	O
experience	O
testament	O
the	O
professional	O
and	O
detail	O
recruitment	O
process	O
	
say	O
White	PERSON
admit	O
balco	O
drug	O
link	O
ban	O
American	MISC
sprinter	O
Kelli	PERSON
White	PERSON
say	O
she	O
knowingly	O
take	O
steroid	O
give	O
she	O
Bay	O
area	O
lab	O
	
operative	O
balco	O
president	O
Victor	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
face	O
federal	O
trial	O
next	O
year	DURATION
charge	O
distribute	O
steroid	O
and	O
tax	O
evasion	O
and	O
White	PERSON
say	O
first	ORDINAL
try	O
cover	O
what	O
be	O
do	O
	
	
the	O
one	NUMBER
who	O
tell	O
that	O
wasn	O
what	O
say	O
be	O
White	PERSON
say	O
the	O
San	O
Francisco	PERSON
Chronicle	O
but	O
she	O
add	O
	
be	O
decision	O
	
he	O
not	O
anybody	O
else	O
	
White	PERSON
say	O
Conte	PERSON
first	ORDINAL
tell	O
she	O
the	O
substance	O
be	O
flaxseed	O
oil	O
only	O
change	O
he	O
story	O
later	O
White	PERSON
fail	O
drug	O
test	O
after	O
win	O
the	O
	
m	O
and	O
	
m	O
title	O
the	O
	
	
world	O
athletics	O
championship	O
she	O
be	O
subsequently	O
handed	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
May	DATE
this	O
year	DURATION
and	O
have	O
admit	O
take	O
the	O
stimulant	O
modafinil	O
	
first	ORDINAL
White	PERSON
claim	O
she	O
take	O
the	O
drug	O
combat	O
narcolepsy	O
but	O
she	O
now	DATE
take	O
full	O
responsibility	O
for	O
she	O
action	O
	
	
whole	O
belief	O
about	O
Victor	PERSON
that	O
be	O
sell	O
product	O
White	PERSON
say	O
the	O
Times	O
	
whether	O
	
good	O
product	O
	
bad	O
product	O
be	O
sell	O
product	O
White	PERSON
be	O
introduce	O
Conte	PERSON
through	O
she	O
coach	O
Remy	PERSON
Korchemy	PERSON
who	O
also	O
defendant	O
the	O
balco	O
case	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
believe	O
doping	O
	
common	O
sport	O
she	O
feel	O
compel	O
cheat	O
herself	O
she	O
be	O
have	O
any	O
chance	O
win	O
	
have	O
clue	O
what	O
	
go	O
take	O
change	O
that	O
say	O
White	PERSON
	
would	O
say	O
make	O
mistake	O
and	O
would	O
never	O
ever	O
back	O
	
would	O
never	O
recommend	O
anyone	O
take	O
that	O
route	O
trial	O
date	O
set	O
for	O
balco	O
case	O
	
judge	O
have	O
set	O
preliminary	O
trial	O
date	O
for	O
the	O
balco	O
steroid	O
distribution	O
case	O
which	O
have	O
rock	O
athletics	O
	
district	O
court	O
judge	O
Susan	PERSON
ilston	O
reject	O
attempt	O
the	O
defence	O
team	O
have	O
the	O
case	O
dismiss	O
	
pre	O
trial	O
hearing	O
San	O
Francisco	PERSON
and	O
she	O
set	O
March	DATE
date	O
for	O
the	O
case	O
the	O
four	NUMBER
man	O
accuse	O
distribute	O
illegal	O
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
elite	O
athlete	O
	
hear	O
	
firm	O
decision	O
whether	O
the	O
trial	O
take	O
place	O
expect	O
January	DATE
the	O
judge	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
may	O
conduct	O
hearing	O
January	DATE
into	O
whether	O
federal	O
agent	O
illegally	O
search	O
the	O
balco	O
headquarters	O
and	O
wrongfully	O
obtain	O
statement	O
from	O
the	O
company	O
founder	O
Victor	PERSON
Conte	PERSON
and	O
its	O
vice	O
president	O
James	PERSON
Valente	PERSON
the	O
two	NUMBER
man	O
along	O
with	O
personal	O
trainer	O
Greg	PERSON
Anderson	PERSON
and	O
athletics	O
coach	O
Remy	PERSON
Korchemny	PERSON
be	O
all	O
indict	O
earlier	O
this	O
year	DURATION
but	O
have	O
plead	O
they	O
innocence	O
the	O
outcome	O
those	O
hearing	O
could	O
result	O
some	O
all	O
the	O
charge	O
be	O
dismiss	O
Conte	PERSON
say	O
that	O
would	O
tell	O
he	O
side	O
the	O
story	O
	
American	MISC
show	O
Friday	DATE
	
the	O
world	O
deserve	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
about	O
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
	
say	O
balco	O
the	O
Bay	O
area	O
laboratory	O
Cooperative	O
the	O
company	O
the	O
centre	O
the	O
scandal	O
the	O
company	O
have	O
be	O
accuse	O
the	O
United	O
States	O
anti	O
dope	O
Agency	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
be	O
the	O
source	O
the	O
ban	O
steroid	O
thg	O
and	O
modafinil	O
the	O
USADA	ORGANIZATION
claim	O
that	O
	
athlete	O
have	O
receive	O
sanction	O
for	O
testing	O
positive	O
for	O
thg	O
and	O
modafinil	O
Former	O
double	O
world	O
champion	O
Kelli	PERSON
White	PERSON
and	O
Olympic	MISC
relay	O
star	O
Alvin	PERSON
Harrison	PERSON
have	O
both	O
be	O
ban	O
the	O
basis	O
material	O
discover	O
during	O
the	O
balco	O
investigation	O
Britain	LOCATION
former	O
european	O
	
m	O
champion	O
Dwain	PERSON
chamber	O
currently	DATE
serve	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
after	O
testing	O
positive	O
for	O
thg	O
	
out	Sports
	
competition	O
test	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
eye	O
hard	O
line	O
drug	O
Paula	PERSON
Radcliffe	PERSON
have	O
call	O
for	O
all	O
athlete	O
find	O
guilty	O
drug	O
charge	O
	
treat	O
criminal	O
the	O
marathon	O
world	O
record	O
holder	O
believe	O
more	O
need	O
	
do	O
rid	O
athletics	O
the	O
suspicion	O
and	O
innuendo	O
which	O
greet	O
any	O
fast	O
time	O
	
dope	O
sport	O
	
criminal	O
offence	O
and	O
should	O
treat	O
such	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
tell	O
the	O
Sunday	DATE
Times	O
	
not	O
only	O
cheat	O
other	O
athlete	O
but	O
also	O
cheat	O
promoter	O
sponsor	O
and	O
the	O
general	O
public	O
Radcliffe	PERSON
comment	O
come	O
	
time	O
when	O
several	O
American	MISC
sport	O
star	O
be	O
under	O
suspicion	O
steroid	O
use	O
	
be	O
catch	Sports
possession	O
	
performance	O
enhance	O
drug	O
should	O
carry	O
penalty	O
she	O
add	O
	
the	O
current	DATE
system	O
do	O
not	O
detect	O
many	O
the	O
substance	O
be	O
abused	O
athlete	O
	
this	O
means	O
that	O
often	O
athlete	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
be	O
compete	O
	
level	O
play	O
field	O
they	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
sacrifice	O
be	O
trump	O
	
easier	O
scientific	O
route	O
	
often	O
when	O
athlete	O
put	O
	
good	O
performance	O
they	O
be	O
subject	O
suspicion	O
and	O
innuendo	O
instead	O
praise	O
	
have	O
be	O
the	O
receive	O
end	O
accusation	O
like	O
this	O
can	O
testify	O
	
how	O
much	O
this	O
hurt	O
Kenteris	PERSON
deny	O
fake	O
road	O
crash	O
greek	O
sprinter	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
have	O
deny	O
claim	O
that	O
fake	O
motorbike	O
crash	O
avoid	O
doping	O
test	O
day	DURATION
before	O
the	O
start	O
the	O
Olympics	MISC
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
fellow	O
sprinter	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
be	O
set	O
learn	O
they	O
will	O
face	O
criminal	O
charge	O
this	O
week	DURATION
part	O
the	O
investigation	O
have	O
centre	O
whether	O
they	O
stage	O
the	O
crash	O
Kenteris	PERSON
insist	O
the	O
accident	O
happen	O
	
go	O
crazy	O
when	O
find	O
out	Sports
have	O
supposedly	O
miss	O
test	O
and	O
want	O
rush	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
village	O
Kenteris	PERSON
speak	O
Greece	LOCATION
alter	O
television	O
station	O
also	O
claim	O
that	O
ask	O
	
test	O
for	O
ban	O
substance	O
hospital	O
after	O
the	O
crash	O
	
tell	O
the	O
hospital	O
which	O
be	O
Olympics	MISC
accredit	O
hospital	O
call	O
the	O
IOC	ORGANIZATION
and	O
have	O
test	O
the	O
spot	O
but	O
	
one	NUMBER
come	O
after	O
drama	O
which	O
dominate	O
newspaper	O
headline	O
Greece	LOCATION
Athens	LOCATION
prepared	O
for	O
the	O
start	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Games	O
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
eventually	O
withdraw	O
but	O
Kenteris	PERSON
have	O
continually	O
protest	O
he	O
innocence	O
and	O
Sunday	DATE
blame	O
greek	O
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
official	O
and	O
he	O
former	O
coach	O
Christos	PERSON
Tzekos	PERSON
for	O
fail	O
inform	O
he	O
the	O
test	O
the	O
	
year	DURATION
old	O
insist	O
will	O
happy	O
	
charge	O
	
can	O
clear	O
he	O
name	O
	
	
decision	O
take	O
have	O
charge	O
file	O
against	O
	
will	O
accept	O
gladly	O
	
prosecution	O
means	O
that	O
the	O
case	O
will	O
clear	O
	
	
want	O
	
the	O
end	O
and	O
then	O
	
see	O
who	O
right	O
and	O
who	O
isn	O
	
Kenteris	PERSON
greek	O
hero	O
after	O
win	O
gold	O
the	O
	
m	O
the	O
	
	
Olympics	MISC
Sydney	LOCATION
also	O
confirm	O
that	O
be	O
due	O
light	O
the	O
flame	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
open	O
ceremony	O
	
have	O
even	O
rehearse	O
lighting	O
the	O
cauldron	O
	
say	O
greek	O
pair	O
set	O
for	O
hearing	O
Kostas	PERSON
Kenteris	PERSON
and	O
Katerina	PERSON
Thanou	PERSON
will	O
fight	O
the	O
provisional	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
impose	O
they	O
the	O
iaaf	O
	
independent	O
tribunal	O
this	O
weekend	DATE
Athletics	O
ruling	O
body	O
take	O
action	O
against	O
the	O
pair	O
for	O
fail	O
take	O
drug	O
test	O
before	O
the	O
Athens	LOCATION
Olympics	MISC
	
independent	O
tribunal	O
the	O
greek	O
Track	O
and	O
field	O
Federation	O
will	O
meet	O
decide	O
whether	O
ratify	O
the	O
sanction	O
the	O
sprint	O
duo	O
face	O
charge	O
fail	O
give	O
information	O
they	O
location	O
and	O
refuse	O
submit	O
	
drug	O
test	O
Kenteris	PERSON
lawyer	O
Gregory	PERSON
Ioannidis	PERSON
tell	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
Sport	O
	
refute	O
both	O
charge	O
unsubstantiated	O
and	O
illogical	O
	
there	O
have	O
be	O
certain	O
breach	O
the	O
correct	O
application	O
the	O
rule	O
behalf	O
the	O
sport	O
authority	O
and	O
they	O
official	O
and	O
these	O
procedural	O
breach	O
have	O
also	O
violate	O
client	O
rights	O
	
there	O
also	O
evidence	O
that	O
prove	O
the	O
fact	O
that	O
client	O
have	O
be	O
persecute	O
Ioannidis	PERSON
who	O
	
law	O
lecturer	O
the	O
University	O
Buckingham	PERSON
add	O
one	NUMBER
the	O
important	O
rights	O
and	O
foundation	O
law	O
and	O
justice	O
that	O
the	O
accuse	O
should	O
presume	O
innocent	O
unless	O
prove	O
otherwise	O
have	O
be	O
tarnish	O
the	O
panel	O
will	O
also	O
decide	O
the	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
ban	O
impose	O
the	O
athlete	O
controversial	O
coach	O
Christos	PERSON
Tzekos	PERSON
the	O
iaaf	O
Kenteris	PERSON
the	O
	
	
Olympic	MISC
	
m	O
champion	O
and	O
Thanou	PERSON
the	O
woman	O
	
	
m	O
silver	O
medallist	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
Games	O
Sydney	LOCATION
quit	O
the	O
Olympics	MISC
	
August	DATE
after	O
fail	O
give	O
sample	O
the	O
eve	O
the	O
open	O
ceremony	O
tester	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
they	O
the	O
Olympic	MISC
village	O
and	O
the	O
duo	O
be	O
later	O
admit	O
hospital	O
after	O
claim	O
have	O
be	O
involve	O
	
motorcycle	O
accident	O
they	O
also	O
miss	O
test	O
Tel	PERSON
Aviv	PERSON
Chicago	LOCATION
and	O
Athens	LOCATION
before	O
the	O
Games	O
	
impose	O
two	NUMBER
year	DURATION
suspension	O
the	O
duo	O
	
December	DATE
the	O
iaaf	O
describe	O
they	O
explanation	O
for	O
miss	O
the	O
test	O
	
unacceptable	O
	
whatever	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
independent	O
tribunal	O
all	O
party	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
right	O
appeal	O
the	O
Court	O
arbitration	O
for	O
Sport	O
the	O
tribunal	O
hearing	O
will	O
take	O
place	O
the	O
hellenic	O
Olympic	MISC
Committee	O
building	O
	
will	O
start	O
	
	
GMT	MISC
Saturday	DATE
and	O
expect	O
finish	O
early	O
next	O
week	DURATION
the	O
tribunal	O
panel	O
will	O
consist	O
five	NUMBER
member	O
president	O
Konstantinos	PERSON
